<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><title>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair)</title><description>Key features:
WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity
5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><price>174.15</price><quantity>1</quantity><brand>Wharfedale</brand><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.webp</image_url><additional_images>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mGUAAeSwTFBp1kAI/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zN4AAeSw61hp1kAI/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUwAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l500.webp</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Home Audio &amp; HiFi&gt;Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><title>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</title><description>MADE IN THE UK. FAST COURIER DELIVERY DIRECTLY FROM CELLO
3 YEAR CELLO WARRANTY APPLIES TO THIS ITEM
50″ Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

50” 4K Ultra HD LED TV
LG’s Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
Download apps through the web browser
Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)  Specification
Screen Size	50″
Freeview Play	Yes
DVD Player	No
USB	Yes – playback only
Contrast Ratio	5000:1
Brightness	250
Max Resolution	3840 x 2160
Speakers	2 x 8W
Smart	Yes
Max Power	120W
Energy Rating	‘G – 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI	3
Inputs	RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs	Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA	200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand	W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand	W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight	9.1kg</description><price>445.5</price><quantity>1</quantity><brand>Cello</brand><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.webp</image_url><additional_images>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ISQAAOSwsINlaIbX/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gLAAAOSw2wRlaIXv/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ww0AAOSwPyxk5deE/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NU8AAOSwOCFk5esD/s-l500.webp</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Sound &amp; Vision&gt;TVs</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>5058048349204</sku><title>Espresso Machine Coffee Maker Cappuccino Milk Frother 20 Bar 1.8L</title><description>Product introduction：
✅ 20Bar High-Pressure Extraction
Equipped with a professional high-pressure water pump, it delivers a stable 20Bar extraction pressure to instantly penetrate coffee grounds, fully releasing the aroma and oils of coffee beans. It easily  restoring the rich flavor of authentic espresso—every sip rivals the quality of specialty café drinks.
✅ 1.8L Large-Capacity Removable Water Tank
No need for frequent refills; a full tank can make multiple cups for the whole family, easily handling daily use and small gatherings. The semi-transparent design lets you check water levels at a glance, and the detachable structure, paired with a separate drip tray, makes refilling and cleaning a breeze—saving time and effort.
✅ Food-Grade Stainless Steel Manufacturing
The body and core contact parts are made of food-grade stainless steel, which is corrosion-resistant, high-temperature resistant, and durable. It eliminates residual odors, ensuring every cup of coffee is pure and safe, balancing premium texture with practicality.
🛠️ All-Inclusive Accessories · Unlock Diverse Coffee Experiences
The machine comes with a complete set of professional accessories, so you can start your home barista journey right out of the box. It balances professionalism and convenience to suit 
☕ Scenario Adaptation · Perfect for Your Daily Moments
🌅 Morning Wake-Up: One-tap espresso, paired with milk for an energizing latte to chase away drowsiness and kickstart a productive day.
☕ Afternoon Relaxation: Brew a cup of freshly ground coffee with dessert, enjoying a moment of peaceful solitude and elevating your at-home ritual.
🥂 Friend Gatherings: Quick double-cup brewing and a variety of milk-based drinks let you host a cozy coffee party at home.
💼 Office Energy Boost: Fast capsule brewing eliminates waiting time, providing timely energy to enhance work efficiency.
📌 Product Specifications
Extraction Pressure: 20Bar high-pressure extraction
Water Tank Capacity: 1.8L large-capacity removable water tank</description><price>102.6</price><quantity>1</quantity><brand>Unbranded</brand><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IJsAAeSwtj1pr-Co/s-l1600.webp</image_url><additional_images>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gDIAAeSwv5Npr-Cq/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FdYAAeSwC0Jpr-Cv/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/E3sAAeSwfLxpr-Ct/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ty8AAeSwLkJpr-Cz/s-l500.webp</additional_images><category>Home &amp; Garden&gt;Appliances&gt;Coffee, Tea &amp; Espresso Makers&gt;Espresso &amp; Cappuccino Machines</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><title>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</title><description>About this item
👨‍👩‍👧【Portable and Magical】-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
👨‍👩‍👧【5 Hrs Battery Life】-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
👨‍👩‍👧【Protective and Gorgeous Screen】-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kids’ eyes.
👨‍👩‍👧【All Regions &amp; Multi Formats】-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CD±R/±RW,DVD±R/±RW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
👨‍👩‍👧【Dual Speakers &amp; Clear Sound】-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
👨‍👩‍👧【Easy Operation &amp; Seamless Viewing】-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
👨‍👩‍👧【Premium Service &amp; Quick Response】-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

★Eye-protection LCD screen★: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
★Super High Battery★: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
★Resume Play★: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
★Game Player★: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
★Multi-Media★: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270° rotation and 180° flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><price>63.45</price><quantity>1</quantity><brand>Unbranded</brand><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.webp</image_url><additional_images>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JmMAAeSwz5hpzi53/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eDcAAeSwjStpzi5x/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hOUAAeSwdJ9pzi51/s-l500.webp</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Sound &amp; Vision&gt;DVD, Blu-ray &amp; Home Cinema&gt;DVD &amp; Blu-ray Players</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>303847658374</sku><title>12S PRO Wifi Tablet Android 15 PC 8GB+64GB Tablets 10.1 Inch 6000mAh</title><description>🚀【2025 𝙇𝙖𝙩𝙚𝙨𝙩 𝘼𝙣𝙙𝙧𝙤𝙞𝙙 15 𝙏𝙖𝙗𝙡𝙚𝙩】
XGODY Android Tablet comes loaded with the "Android 15" operating system. Android 15 Tablet enhances privacy and security and improves the overall experience of using the device through personalization features, the ability to unlock the screen using facial recognition, and control over data accessed by apps. With a highly stable and secure network system, you can browse the web more smoothly and quickly with your Android 14 Tablet.
 
📊【𝙋𝙤𝙬𝙚𝙧𝙛𝙪𝙡 𝙎𝙩𝙤𝙧𝙖𝙜𝙚 8GB RAM+64GB ROM】
This 10-inch tablet features a powerful 8GB RAM and 64GB ROM. The large expandable memory provides a smoother experience, so you can launch apps quickly and enjoy them without worrying about running out of space. Our Android tablets also come with the Google Play Store pre-installed so you can download all the apps you want, such as Netflix/YouTube/Facebook/Twitter, and experience not only the stable Google services, but also the enhanced PC mode for a more convenient experience.
 
👁️【10.1-𝙞𝙣𝙘𝙝 𝙇𝘾𝘿 𝘿𝙞𝙨𝙥𝙡𝙖𝙮】
This Android tablet not only comes with a 10-inch HD IPS LCD display, but also features an ultra-high resolution of 1280x800 for a wide and bright field of view, which brings you truer colors and clearer images for perfect visual enjoyment while working, watching videos and playing games. The tablet also features a crisp 5MP front camera and 8MP rear camera for your daily needs, providing you great photos and clear video chats.
 
🛜【𝙒𝙞-𝙁𝙞 6 + 𝘽𝙡𝙪𝙚𝙩𝙤𝙤𝙩𝙝 5.0】
N02 PRO Android Tablet is equipped with a high-resolution 1280*800 LCD display with widescreen display and vibrant colors for a cinema-quality viewing experience with clearer and brighter images. This Android Tablet features 6th generation Wi-Fi technology, this 10-inch Android 14 tablet supports 5G and 2.4G dual-band Wi-Fi, which makes searching for networks fast and free, providing a better network connection with lower latency, stronger signal and faster speed.
 
🔋【6000mah 𝙇𝙖𝙧𝙜𝙚 𝘽𝙖𝙩𝙩𝙚𝙧𝙮 𝘾𝙖𝙥𝙖𝙘𝙞𝙩𝙮】
This Android 15 tablet is equipped with a 6000mAh ultra-large capacity battery, which provides plenty of energy for the tablet to run multiple programs.Jeazans Android tablet can be quickly charged through the Type-C connector, there's plenty of power is available for you to spend the entire day. Note: Battery life depends on device settings and application usage.
 
📦【𝑾𝒉𝒂𝒕'𝒔 𝒊𝒏 𝒕𝒉𝒆 𝑩𝒐𝒙】 𝑷𝒂𝒄𝒌𝒂𝒈𝒆 𝑪𝒐𝒎𝒆 𝒘𝒊𝒕𝒉 1* 10.1 𝒊𝒏𝒄𝒉 𝒂𝒏𝒅𝒓𝒐𝒊𝒅 15 𝒕𝒂𝒃𝒍𝒆𝒕,  1* 𝑪𝒂𝒃𝒍𝒆.
Best gift choice for elders, children, family or friends. In addition, this latest Android 14 tablet is also upgraded with face recognition, which effectively frees your hands. XGODY provides customers with a one-year warranty and 7-day after-sales service, if you are not satisfied with your purchase, please contact us in time, and we will help you solve the problem with our best endeavours.</description><price>94.5</price><quantity>1</quantity><brand>Xgody</brand><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zT8AAeSwFo9o7N2j/s-l1600.webp</image_url><additional_images>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VMsAAeSw7Uho7NyN/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yogAAeSw7H5o7NyQ/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/h0QAAeSwmENo7NyT/s-l500.webp, https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/cPEAAeSwQYRo7NyW/s-l500.webp</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking&gt;Tablets &amp; eBook Readers</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>404048284703</sku><title>Bluetooth Speaker Wireless, 300W Peak Power Party Speakers Wireless Bluetooth with Subwoofer, Portable Deep Bass Large Speaker Loud with Stereo Sound, LED Light Show for Party Outdoor Camping</title><description>About this item
🎵300W Peak Power - Equipped with 2 * 5.25" woofer and 2 * 2.0" tweeter, the 300W peak power bluetooth speaker with deep bass and clear treble, featuring the latest technologies in audio performance, faster processing algorithms from the technology to improve the sound quality assurance, is perfect for outdoor party, indoor gathering, home theater, or any event where music takes center stage.
🎵Supports TWS Stereo System - Pair 2 of TAMPROAD Q66 portable wireless speaker to get the TWS function and a fully immersive and spatial audio experience. Whether you're using it for karaoke, playing music, or home theater, the TWS stereo surround feature is sure to take your audio experience to the next high level.
🎵Dynamic LED Light Show - The partybox is crazy, have a unique disco lighting design. The lights can jump with the rhythm of the music, you can also switch to a variety of lighting effects for any party or gathering to create a cool dynamic atmosphere. You can enjoy the light show while listening to your favorite music, giving you an unforgettable experience. It light up the fiery party, and push the passion to a new level (You may also choose to switch off the light when you are using it.)
🎵Multiple Connections, Easy to Use: The speakers bluetooth wireless has many types of connections to play music. You can connect the speaker to your device via Bluetooth, USB drive (Supports Micro SD cards, but requires adapter) or AUX mode to play music. And it also supports microphone, and guitar input. Simply plug in your microphone, and it becomes a professional karaoke machine tailored just for you. You have the flexibility to choose your preferred playback mode, connect easily to enjoy music anytime, anywhere.
🎵Large Battery &amp; Plug-in Power Supply: Two power options let you choose freely based on different scenarios when using this loud bluetooth speaker. 83Wh ultra-high-capacity battery pack delivers up to 10 hours of continuous playback, meeting all your needs for camping, parties, BBQ and home theater entertainment. Plug-in power supply with wide voltage design, supporting 110-240V input voltage, provides uninterrupted operation, keeping your music playing nonstop.
🎵The built-in 11.1V battery packs deliver powerful energy to the 5.25-inch woofer, extending low frequencies down to 45Hz. Experience cinema-level impact with deep, resonant bass while enjoying crystal-clear vocals—say goodbye to muffled sound. And built-in professional EQ presets with one-touch switching to adapt to various music genres, delivering precise audio performance.
🎵12 Months Warranty Service - Enhance your party atmosphere with our portable bluetooth speaker. The package include: 1 X TAMPROAD Q66 300W bluetooth speaker, 1 X UK standard AC power cable, 1 X AUX cable, and 1 X user manual. Rest assured, all TAMPROAD products come with a 12-months warranty and 24-hours customer service.</description><price>242.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><brand>TAMPROAD</brand><image_url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81Bs-qxRv9L._AC_SX679_.jpg</image_url><additional_images>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81qUwlZL5NL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81XfkG7X6-L._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81eqf8yJwlL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81vCmXx9pYL._AC_SL1500_.jpg</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Home Audio &amp; HiFi&gt;Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>404972894603</sku><title>Portable Bluetooth Speaker Wireless Powerful Deep Bass Loud Stereo Sound Cute Fashion Style Vintage Decor Speakers with Subwoofer DSP Support TWS/USB/AUX for Home Desk Accessories Party Outdoor</title><description>About this item
【Bluetooth Speaker with Bass】The L10 bluetooth speakers is engineered with a dual-driver system (1x1'' Tweeter + 1x3'' Woofer) that delivers a full 40W(60W Peak) of rich, powerful audio and built_in DSP Technology can provide very deep bass and amazing surround stereo sound. This wireless speaker with subwoofer is very suitable for outdoor and indoor home party. it will bring you an unprecedented listening experience.
【Wireless and wired Quick Connect】The L10 portable speakers built-in advanced Bluetooth 5.3 for stable wireless transmission, working distance up to 100ft range, easily connectable all Bluetooth-enabled device, such as you cellphone, tablet, laptop, and all other bluetooth devices. The speaker also can support wired connect to play. you can use AUX cable connect to your TV, computer, MP3, MP4, or other non-Bluetooth devices via 3.5mm audio jack.
【Multi-function Party Speaker】The L10 portable bluetooth speaker support TWS, AUX input, U-disk music playback and TF card music playback. It's built-in 5000mAh rechargeable battery, providing up to 4~12 hours play time ( depends on playing volume). The top of this portable speaker has a hand-held pull belt that you can take the speaker anywhere. This loud bluetooth speaker is great for camping trips, barbecues and home pary, conferences etc.
【Intuitive Operation Controls &amp; HD Display】The L10 portable party speaker feature user-friendly physical buttons and a precise volume knob for easy operation, even without looking. The built-in clear digital display shows the playback mode and battery level at a glance. Built with a durable ABS shell to withstand the rigors of travel.
【TWS Features】The L10 bass speaker supports True Wireless Stereo (TWS) technology, you can pair two of our L10 Bluetooth speakers together get 80W(120W Peak) powerful loud surround stereo sound for your party. Experience crisp highs, deep bass, and clear mids for a truly surround sound experience whether indoors or outdoors.
【Ideal as a holiday gift】Our L10 bluetooth speaker is a great gift for people of all ages, Whether they enjoy music, parties, or just want to enjoy high-quality music at home. This is a multifunctional and practical gift that anyone will love it. Ideal as a birthday gift, Christmas gift, and holiday gift. ( NOTE: If you have any questions, please contact us, we will reply you within 7-24 hours to provide you with the best customer service ).</description><price>81.0</price><quantity>81</quantity><brand>TOMPROAD</brand><image_url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81VHmAQWfOL._AC_SX679_.jpg</image_url><additional_images>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71nZfiXfT2L._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71ujsT2y-aL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81TxjdqOHjL._AC_SX679_.jpg</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Home Audio &amp; HiFi&gt;Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>505738637400</sku><title>Portable Bluetooth Speakers 60W Big Powerful Wireless Loud Stereo Bass Sound Boombox Home Party Speaker with Subwoofer, FM Radio, LED Colorful Lights (Black)</title><description>About this item
【Bluetooth speaker with lights】 The party speaker is designed with RGB lights to light up every corner of the party space and has 9 flashing LED lights Mode, which colourful and vibrant can give your home party, beach, camping or outdoor travel an exciting atmospher. You can easily turn on and off the LED lights with long press one button.
【Advanced Bluetooth 5.0 and Wooden Speaker】 The A52 outdoor Speakers is built_in Bluetooth 5.0 Chip , working distance up to 100ft range, easily connectable all Bluetooth-enabled device, such as your smartphone, cellphone, tablet, MacBook, laptop, and all other bluetooth devices. This bluetooth speaker is designed with a wooden structure to give you better bass and clearer sound.
【Bluetooth Speaker with Subwoofer】 The A52 bluetooth speakers is big powerful portable stereo bass speaker, it have four 3-inch loudspeakers including two woofers, two tweeters and a rear heavy bass guide tube. Output Power 60W surround sound and amazing bass sound. This Portable speaker is very suitable for outdoor and indoor home party.
【Multifunctional Wireless Speaker】The A52 portable bluetooth speaker supports FM radio, AUX input, U-disk music playback, TF Card music playback, intelligent remote control and digital display. It's built-in 8000mAh rechargeable battery, providing up to 4~15 hours play time ( depends on playing volume). You can enjoy the carnival whether it is an indoor or outdoor dance party. This big bluetooth speaker is great for camping trips, barbecues and even singing karaoke, weddings, conferences etc.
【FM Radio and Remote Control】 The wireless speaker support FM radio Function, it can automatically search and save all available stations by long press pause button in FM mode . You can also manually input a radio station using the remote control . This remote control can control more speaker functions include Bluetooth, LED lights. The top of this portable bluetooth speaker has a hand-held pull ring that you can take the speaker anywhere and a stand holder that can support the standing of mobile phones, tablets, etc.
【Ideal as a holiday gift】 Our bluetooth speaker is a great gift for people of all ages, Whether they enjoy music, parties, or just want to enjoy high-quality music at home. This is a multifunctional and practical gift that anyone will love it. Ideal as a birthday gift, Christmas gift, and holiday gift. ( NOTE: If you have any questions, please contact us, we will reply you within 7-24 hours to provide you with the best customer service ).</description><price>58.5</price><quantity>5</quantity><brand>TOMPROAD</brand><image_url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61vyFrWBtHL._AC_SX679_.jpg</image_url><additional_images>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/41mrahOs2qL._AC_US40_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/518uzapehGL._AC_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81yHqM1WQDL._AC_SX679_.jpg</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;Home Audio &amp; HiFi&gt;Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>505023497900</sku><title>SIA CERH60BL 60cm Electric Ceramic Hob, 4 Zone with Touch Control, 9 Power Levels, Child Safety Lock, Black, 2 Years Parts &amp; Labour Guarantee</title><description>About this item
Customisable Cooking Power: With 9 power levels, this 60cm ceramic hob with 4 cooking zones gives you full control over cooking temperatures, allowing you to achieve perfect results for any dish with ease.
User-Friendly: Featuring side touch controls for a sleek, modern interface, this hob ensures effortless operation. The child safety lock and residual heat indicators provide added peace of mind for families.
Convenient &amp; Easy to Maintain: The frameless design and easy-wipe surface make cleaning a breeze, while the 99-minute timer doubles as a handy minute minder, keeping your cooking on track.
Advanced Safety Features: Equipped with auto shutdown protection, this ceramic hob offers an extra layer of security by automatically turning off when necessary, preventing accidents and ensuring your safety in the kitchen.
2 Years Parts &amp; Labour Guarantee. Product Dimensions (cm): W58 x D51 x H5.2.</description><price>101.24</price><quantity>5</quantity><brand>	SIA</brand><image_url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71txzjjto9L._AC_SL1500_.jpg</image_url><additional_images>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71txzjjto9L._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61eQJCw4CoL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71uh8k0C+RL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/515r+v+6Z+L._AC_SX679_.jpg</additional_images><category>Home &amp; Garden&gt;Kitchen&gt;Hobs</category><condition>New</condition></product><product><sku>404728645206</sku><title>Android TV Box 14.0, 2025 Smart TV Box Android 14 with 4GB RAM 32GB ROM Octa-core 64-bit CPU 1000M Ethernet WIFI6 4K 8K HD Android TV Boxes Dual-WiFi 2.4G/5.8G Bluetooth 5.0 USB 3.0 3D H.265 R69 Plus</title><description>About this item
[Android 14.0 OS + Powerful Processor]: This is the pioneering Android 14.0 TV box to enter the market. It is equipped with the Android 14.0 operating system and powered by the high-performance octa-core ARM Cortex A55 CPU. The upgraded Android 14.0 operating system significantly enhances the user-friendliness of the interface and the compatibility of applications. With this Android TV box, you can relish your favorite apps, games, and videos without any lag, offering a seamless entertainment experience.
【4GB RAM + 32GB ROM &amp; Expandable to 128GB TF Card or 1TB Hard Drive】: The Android TV box 14.0 provides 32GB of memory space and 4GB of RAM to guarantee the speed and stability of the operating system. It supports a smooth running speed without buffering or breakdowns. If you want to save all your beloved content without worrying about space limitations, you are welcome to expand the storage via a 128GB TF card or a 1TB hard drive.
【Superior Bluetooth, Wi-Fi &amp; Ethernet Functions】: The newest Android TV box supports 2.4G/5.8G Wi-Fi 6 and up to 1000M Ethernet. It also features the latest Bluetooth 6.0 for seamless and secure connectivity. This ensures a smooth enjoyment of movies, images, and games. With BT 5.0 and USB 3.0 connections, the Android TV box offers unrivaled convenience when connecting wireless or wired headphones, speakers, or game controllers.
【8K HDR10 &amp; H.265 Technology】The Android TV box supports 8K resolution and HDR10 technology, delivering stunning visuals with vivid colors and enhanced contrast. Enjoy 3D movies and shows for an immersive entertainment experience with your family. The H.265 image processing technology enables users to watch movies more smoothly with the same picture quality loaded. Now, users can freely watch ultra-high-definition movies at home at any time without having to go to the cinema.
【User-Friendly &amp; LED ambient lighting variations】The simplistic UI design makes the operation interface clearly visible at a glance. It offers a user-friendly interface and effortless navigation. With its compact size and stylish design, it can be easily placed anywhere. Whether you are watching movies, playing games, or browsing the web.The top of the product is installed with a superb sense of atmosphere light strip, you just need to enter the settings to turn on the correspond button, the color of this light strip will automatically change , adding a sense of life story!</description><price>78.29</price><quantity>5</quantity><brand>EASYTONE</brand><image_url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/51T6ELDJY5L._AC_SX679_.jpg</image_url><additional_images>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71IAf+jXnZL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71ELH6iTPIL._AC_SX679_.jpg, https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71X4N7exLyL._AC_SX679_.jpg</additional_images><category>Electronics&gt;TV Box&gt;TV Remote</category><condition>New</condition></product></products>