<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><product_name>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair) Walnut</product_name><description>Key features:

    WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
    Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
    Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
    Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
    Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity

5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included


            
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mGUAAeSwTFBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zN4AAeSw61hp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUwAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y7wAAeSwajBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vQ8AAeSwhIJp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Wharfedale</brand><category>Speakers</category><ean>505873497501</ean><condition>New</condition><price>180.6</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><product_name>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</product_name><description>50″ Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

    50” 4K Ultra HD LED TV
    LG’s Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
    Download apps through the web browser
    Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
    Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
    Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
    3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
    Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)


The built-in Smart platform, developed by LG, allows you to browse the web and download all your favourite entertainment apps, so you can stream directly to the TV. From Netflix, Prime Video and Disney Plus to YouTube and catch-up apps like BBC iPlayer and ITVx, a world of entertainment awaits.

With Freeview Play you can watch an impressive 60,000+ hours of TV and over 1,500 boxsets, across your favourite on-demand players. All for free.

With the built-in Bluetooth connectivity, you can add a Bluetooth soundbar to the TV. This means cinema sound can be enjoyed without the need for untidy cables. The built-in satellite tuner with Freesat provides access to over 170 channels with 100% channel coverage on a subscription-free basis. Plus, you’ll find your favourite on-demand players all in one place. You will just need to purchase and install your own satellite dish/cabling. The ultimate flat-screen TV with its super-slim bezel and lightweight design is ideal for wall mounting and easy maneuverability


Specification
Screen Size         50″
Freeview Play         Yes
DVD Player         No
USB         Yes – playback only
Contrast Ratio         5000:1
Brightness         250
Max Resolution         3840 x 2160
Speakers         2 x 8W
Smart         Yes
Max Power         120W
Energy Rating         ‘G – 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI         3
Inputs         RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs         Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA         200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand         W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand         W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight         9.1kg</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qawAAeSwShFppWtV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ztwAAOSwG3dm9EMH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EqAAAOSwNORlaIbE/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ISQAAOSwsINlaIbX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wfEAAOSw~FVlaIXe/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Cello</brand><category>Televisions</category><ean>504048423208</ean><condition>New</condition><price>461.99</price><quantity>7</quantity></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><product_name>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</product_name><description>About this item
👨‍👩‍👧【Portable and Magical】-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
👨‍👩‍👧【5 Hrs Battery Life】-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
👨‍👩‍👧【Protective and Gorgeous Screen】-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kids’ eyes.
👨‍👩‍👧【All Regions &amp; Multi Formats】-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CD±R/±RW,DVD±R/±RW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
👨‍👩‍👧【Dual Speakers &amp; Clear Sound】-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
👨‍👩‍👧【Easy Operation &amp; Seamless Viewing】-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
👨‍👩‍👧【Premium Service &amp; Quick Response】-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

★Eye-protection LCD screen★: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
★Super High Battery★: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
★Resume Play★: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
★Game Player★: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
★Multi-Media★: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270° rotation and 180° flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~aoAAeSw2Rtpzi5w/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eDcAAeSwjStpzi5x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AfoAAeSwXZ5pzi5z/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hOUAAeSwdJ9pzi51/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JmMAAeSwz5hpzi53/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>DVD &amp; Blu-ray Players</category><ean>4049023423478</ean><condition>New</condition><price>65.79</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092475</sku><product_name>Bluetooth FM Transmitter Car Kit MP3 Player USB Charger Handsfree Adapter UK</product_name><description>Upgrade your driving experience with this multifunctional Car Charger Bluetooth adapter. Combining hands-free calling, music streaming, and rapid charging, it’s the perfect companion for every journey. Designed with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology, it delivers high-speed charging while keeping your devices connected safely.


⭐ Key Features
Bluetooth 5.0 Connectivity: Stable, fast pairing with smartphones for calls, music, and navigation audio.
FM Transmitter Function: Stream your favorite playlists directly to your car stereo via FM radio.
Dual USB Fast Charging Ports: Supports rapid charging for multiple devices simultaneously.
MP3 Player Support: Play music from USB drives or SD cards effortlessly.
Hands-Free Calling: Clear audio with built-in microphone ensures safe driving.
Compact &amp; Universal Design: Fits all standard car cigarette lighter sockets and works with most vehicles.

📊 Technical Specs
Bluetooth Version: 5.0
Input: DC 12-24V
Output: 5V/2.4A per USB port
Frequency Range: 87.5–108MHz
Compatible Formats: MP3/WMA/WAV
LED Display: Shows FM frequency and device info

💡 Benefits
Charge your phone and other devices quickly with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology.
Enjoy seamless music streaming without tangled wires.
Stay safe with hands-free calling while driving.
Compact design keeps your dashboard neat and organized.

🎯 Ideal For
Daily commuters who need fast device charging and music on the go.
Road trips and long drives requiring hands-free calls and entertainment.
Anyone who wants to upgrade an older car stereo to Bluetooth functionality.
Drivers with multiple devices needing simultaneous fast charging.

🌐 Vast Applications
Cars, SUVs, trucks, and other vehicles with cigarette lighter sockets.
Listening to music or podcasts from smartphones, USB drives, or SD cards.
Hands-free calls during work commutes, rideshare driving, or family trips.
Charging smartphones, tablets, GPS devices, power banks, and other USB devices.
Enhancing older car stereos with FM broadcasting and Bluetooth connectivity.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2FkAAeSwnNZpbks~/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4QAAAeSwYPtpbktl/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/v18AAeSw40tpbkth/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1jgAAeSwTb5pbks9/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qZ0AAeSwLmtpbktK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Mx8AAeSwGJ5pbktO/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Car Accessories</category><ean>404834092475</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.59</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097401</sku><product_name>Mini Pocket Umbrella Folding Compact Rain Windproof Anti UV 5 Folding Travel UK</product_name><description>Stay protected in every season with this sleek and ultra-portable Mini Pocket Compact Fold Umbrella. Designed for modern lifestyles, it combines Rain Windproof durability with Anti UV protection, making it the perfect everyday travel essential.


⭐ Key Features
🌧 Rain Windproof Design – Strong frame for reliable performance in wind &amp; rain
☀️ Anti UV Protection – Helps block harmful sun rays on hot days
👜 Ultra Compact &amp; Pocket Size – Easy to carry anywhere, anytime
⚡ Quick Open &amp; Fold – Simple, hassle-free operation
🎒 Travel Case Included – Clean and convenient storage
💪 Durable Build – Premium materials for long-term use

📏 Technical Specifications
Type: 5-Fold Compact Umbrella
Material: Waterproof Fabric + Reinforced Metal Frame
Function: Rainproof, Windproof, Anti UV
Folded Size: Approx. 15–18 cm
Open Diameter: Approx. 90–95 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Included: Protective Travel Case

🌍 Ideal For
🌧 Rainy Days – Stay dry during sudden showers
☀️ Super Sunny Days – Reliable shade with Anti UV protection
🍂 Autumn &amp; Winter – Handles wet and windy conditions
🌸 Spring Showers – Perfect for unpredictable weather
🌞 Summer Heat – Use as a portable sunshade
🌦 All-Season Use – One umbrella for every condition

🔄 Vast Application of Usage
Designed to make your life easier, this umbrella is perfect for:

🚶 Daily Use – Commuting, school runs, office travel
🛍 Shopping Trips – Stay comfortable while out and about
✈️ Travel &amp; Holidays – Compact size fits easily in luggage
🚗 On-the-Go Protection – Keep in your car or bag for emergencies
🎉 Outdoor Events – Festivals, sports days, gatherings
🏕 Outdoor Activities – Walking, hiking, camping
👨‍👩‍👧 For Everyone – Suitable for men, women, and kids
👉 No confusion, no hassle — one simple solution for all your weather needs


🎯 Why Choose This Umbrella?
✔ Dual-purpose Rain Windproof &amp; Anti UV protection
✔ Compact, lightweight, and easy to carry
✔ Reliable in all weather conditions
✔ Practical design for everyday convenience

🚀 Benefits You’ll Love
Stay dry and protected anytime, anywhere
Enjoy peace of mind with all-in-one weather protection
Carry effortlessly without bulk
Dependable performance you can trust</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U-oAAeSwf8Fp43cb/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XGwAAeSwv5dp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YaQAAeSw8Zdp43cb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eIUAAeSwzmBp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NRgAAeSwo41p43cZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fYwAAeSwpHRp43ca/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Accessories Umbrellas</category><ean>404834097401</ean><condition>New</condition><price>18.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097418</sku><product_name>Bike Seat Cover Soft Gel Saddle Bicycle Padded Cushioned Extra Comfort UK</product_name><description>Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover Padded Cushion Saddle – Universal Fit for Maximum Comfort 🚴
Upgrade your cycling experience with this premium Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover, designed to deliver exceptional Padded Comfort on every ride. Whether commuting, exercising, or riding long distances, enjoy a smoother, pain-free journey.

⭐ Key Features
Soft Gel Padding – Advanced cushioning absorbs shock and reduces pressure
Padded Comfort Design – Extra-thick padding for long rides
Secure Anti-Slip Fit – Non-slip base with adjustable drawstring
Breathable Design – Airflow channel reduces heat and moisture
Water-Resistant – Protects from sweat and light rain
Universal Fit – Fits most standard bike saddles
💎 Premium Quality &amp; Material
High-grade soft gel with high-density memory foam
Premium Lycra fabric – breathable and stretchable
Reinforced stitching for durability
Anti-slip textured base for stability
Maintains shape after long-term use
📐 Technical Specifications
Material: Soft Gel + High-Density Foam + Lycra Fabric
Size: Approx. 27.5 x 17 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Compatibility: Fits most bike saddles
Installation: Easy slip-on with drawstring
🎯 Ideal For
Daily commuters and city cyclists
Long-distance and endurance riders
Indoor cycling and spin classes
Mountain and road biking
Beginners needing extra comfort
🌍 Vast Applications
Road bikes – long-distance comfort
Mountain bikes – shock absorption
City bikes – daily commuting
Exercise bikes – home workouts
Hybrid bikes – mixed terrain
Leisure cycling – casual rides
Travel &amp; touring – portable comfort
✅ Benefits
Ride longer without discomfort
Reduces pressure on sensitive areas
Improves performance and endurance
Quick installation – no tools needed</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/r~QAAeSwYytp4Och/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gOoAAeSweFVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WMIAAeSwcSpp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MF0AAeSw2rlp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/M7MAAeSwDeVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ob0AAeSwFbNp4Oci/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Cycling Bike Accessories Saddle Covers</category><ean>404834097418</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097500</sku><product_name>Anti Mosquito Insect &amp; Bug Repellent Bracelet Bands Silicone Wristband 1- 20 PK</product_name><description>⭐ Key Features
Effective Mosquito Protection – Helps repel mosquitoes and insects naturally
Safe &amp; DEET-Free – Infused with natural plant-based essential oils
Adjustable &amp; Flexible Fit – Comfortable silicone design for adults and children
Long-Lasting Use – Provides extended protection for hours
Portable &amp; Easy – Wear on wrist, ankle, or attach anywhere
Multiple Colors – Fun and vibrant options
Value Packs – Available in 1–20 PCS options
📊 Technical Specifications
Material: High-quality silicone
Active Ingredients: Natural essential oils (citronella, eucalyptus, etc.)
Size: One-size-fits-most (adjustable)
Usage Time: Several hours per band (varies by environment)
Application: Wrist, ankle, bags, strollers
Pack Options: 1, 5, 10, 15, or 20 pieces
✅ Benefits
No sprays, no skin irritation, no mess
Family-friendly for kids and adults
Lightweight, waterproof, and travel-ready
Great alternative to traditional repellents
🎯 Ideal For
Camping, hiking, fishing, and outdoor adventures
Travel, holidays, and picnics
Gardening, BBQs, and sports activities
Everyday use at home or school
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Outdoor: camping, trekking, cycling, beach trips
Home &amp; garden: backyard, lawn work, evening relaxation
Kids: school, playgrounds, daycare
Travel: airports, hotels, tropical destinations
Work: fishing, farming, construction, warehouses
Pet walks: parks, trails, wooded areas
Daily use: shopping, commuting, casual outings
🚚 Free Shipping
Fast &amp; reliable delivery
Secure packaging for safe arrival
No extra charges</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jS0AAeSwJyRp2OwQ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tpgAAeSw1rlp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3rAAAeSwFh9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AyQAAeSwe5tp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qOsAAeSwF7Vp2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1ZcAAeSw2L9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Camping &amp; Hiking Outdoor Survival Equipment Insect Nets</category><ean>404834097500</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097593</sku><product_name>10m Retractable Clothes Reel Double Washing Line Wall Mounted Outdoor</product_name><description>Key Features
10M Double Washing Line – Provides ample drying space for clothes, towels, and bedding
Retractable Design – Extends when needed and neatly retracts to save space
Wall Mounted Convenience – Easy to install on walls, fences, or posts
Durable &amp; Weather-Resistant – Built to withstand outdoor conditions
Secure Locking Mechanism – Keeps the line tight and prevents sagging
Compact Storage – Keeps spaces tidy and clutter-free
📊 Technical Specifications
Line Length: 10 meters (double line)
Type: Retractable Clothes Reel
Installation: Wall Mounted
Material: High-quality ABS casing + strong line cord
Usage: Indoor &amp; Outdoor
Color: Varies by stock
Mounting Accessories: Included
💡 Benefits
Saves space compared to traditional clotheslines
Keeps laundry neat and off the ground
Perfect for small spaces like balconies and patios
Helps reduce indoor moisture
Easy to use and maintain
🏡 Ideal For
Homes with limited outdoor space
Apartments, balconies, and patios
Gardens, garages, and laundry rooms
Everyday family laundry drying needs
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Drying clothes, towels, bedsheets, and delicates
Indoor drying during rainy seasons
Outdoor use in gardens or backyards
Camping, caravans, and temporary setups
Utility rooms and shared laundry areas</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PzEAAeSweFVp1mhN/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/B6UAAeSwSQRp1mhL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/D2EAAeSwmT1p1mhM/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C3UAAeSwQIpp1mhL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XhMAAeSwqBVp1mhM/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XGQAAeSwHQBp1mhL/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>404834097593</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340975905</sku><product_name>EMERGENCY HAMMER CAR WINDOW BREAKER SEATBELT CUTTER BREAK GLASS ESCAPE SAFETY UK</product_name><description>EMERGENCY HAMMER Car Window Breaker &amp; Seatbelt Cutter – Essential Vehicle Escape Safety Tool (UK Stock)

Be fully prepared for unexpected emergencies with this high‑quality EMERGENCY HAMMER featuring a WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER. Designed for rapid response, this compact yet durable tool can make a critical difference when seconds matter.


⭐ Key Features
✔ 2-in-1 Emergency Design – Heavy-duty window breaker &amp; seatbelt cutter in one compact tool
✔ Hardened Steel Hammer Head – Instantly shatters side windows in emergency situations
✔ Sharp Concealed Blade – Quickly cuts jammed or locked seatbelts
✔ Non-Slip Anti-Skid Handle – Firm grip for safe and controlled use
✔ High-Visibility Red Body – Easy to locate in stressful situations
✔ Protective Mounting Bracket – Secure and convenient storage within reach
✔ Compact &amp; Lightweight – Fits glove box, door pocket, or centre console

🔧 Technical Specifications
Material: High-carbon hardened steel hammer head
Handle: Durable ABS with anti-slip grip
Blade: Stainless steel concealed safety blade
Length: Approx. 17cm
Weight: Approx. 130–150g
Colour: Red
Condition: Brand New
Stock Location: UK

🌍 Vast Application of Usage
This EMERGENCY HAMMER is suitable for a wide range of vehicles and emergency situations:

🚗 Private cars &amp; family vehicles
🚕 Taxis, Uber &amp; ride-share vehicles
🚚 Vans, trucks &amp; delivery fleets
🚌 Buses &amp; minibuses
🚐 Motorhomes &amp; caravans
🚓 Emergency &amp; service vehicles
🚤 Boats &amp; marine vehicles
🏢 Workplace fleet vehicles
🎒 Travel safety kits &amp; roadside emergency kits
Perfect for emergencies involving:

Vehicle submersion in water
Electrical or central locking failure
Car fires
Severe collisions
Jammed doors after impact

🛡 Key Benefits
✔ Enables fast escape when doors cannot be opened
✔ Cuts seatbelts instantly to prevent entrapment
✔ Provides peace of mind for drivers and passengers
✔ A small investment for potentially life-saving protection

📦 Package Includes
1 × EMERGENCY HAMMER
1 × Mounting Bracket</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VkAAAeSw8Udp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rFoAAeSwxGxp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rJwAAeSwJQ1p0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/CcEAAeSw7mhp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vb4AAeSwAVRp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T8EAAeSwQHtp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>4048340975905</ean><condition>New</condition><price>6.23</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091102</sku><product_name>Hair Trap Shower Bath Plug Hole Waste Catcher Stopper Drain Sink Strainer UK</product_name><description>Hair Trap Shower Bath Plug Hole Waste Catcher – Stopper Drain Sink Strainer
Keep your drains clean and clog-free with this practical and efficient Plug Hole Waste Catcher. Designed to trap hair, food particles, and debris before they cause blockages, this versatile Stopper Drain Sink Strainer is a must-have for every home.


⭐ Key Features
Effective Hair &amp; Debris Trap – Catches hair, soap residue, and waste to prevent clogged drains
Dual Function Design – Works as both a Plug Hole Waste Catcher and a Stopper Drain Sink Strainer
Universal Fit – Suitable for most sinks, bathtubs, and shower plug holes
Durable &amp; Flexible Material – Made from high-quality silicone or TPR for long-lasting use
Easy to Clean – Simply remove, rinse, and reuse in seconds
Anti-Slip Design – Securely stays in place without shifting during use

📏 Technical Specifications
Material: Silicone / TPR (Thermoplastic Rubber)
Diameter: Approx. 10–11 cm (fits standard drains)
Design: Flat or dome-shaped with raised edges
Color Options: Varies (e.g., white, grey, blue, black)
Application: Bathroom, kitchen, laundry sinks

✅ Benefits
Prevents costly plumbing blockages
Maintains smooth water drainage
Saves time on cleaning and maintenance
Hygienic and reusable solution
Ideal for everyday household use

🎯 Ideal For
Showers and bathtubs
Bathroom and kitchen sinks
Laundry tubs
Homes with pets or long hair</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oPEAAeSwUl5pzTPy/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/CIcAAeSwXZ5pzTQJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lX8AAeSwGTppzTPx/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/A-IAAeSw9lFpzTQJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gA4AAeSwUEtpzTPy/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1xoAAeSwJE9pzTPw/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Bathroom Accessories Drain Stoppers &amp; Strainers</category><ean>404834091102</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091201</sku><product_name>Electric Portable Powered Drill Pump Oil Fluid Water Transfer Pumps Self Priming</product_name><description>Key Features
Drill Powered Design – Connects to most electric drills for fast pumping
Self Priming Function – Smooth operation without manual priming
Multi-Fluid Compatibility – Works with water, oil, diesel, and more
Durable Construction – Built for long-lasting use
Portable &amp; Lightweight – Easy to carry and store
Standard Hose Fit – Compatible with common hose sizes
📊 Technical Specifications
Type: Drill Pump (Self Priming)
Power Source: Electric Drill (not included)
Material: High-strength plastic + metal shaft
Flow Rate: Approx. 20–30 L/min
Inlet/Outlet: Approx. 16mm
Fluids: Water, oil, diesel, non-corrosive liquids
✅ Benefits
Saves time compared to manual transfer
No electricity needed—use your drill
Reduces mess with controlled flow
Ideal for emergencies and everyday tasks
🎯 Ideal For
Homeowners and DIY users
Garden irrigation tasks
Automotive fluid changes
Aquariums, pools, and tanks
Workshops and construction sites
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Automotive – oil, coolant, and fuel transfer
Home – draining water and tanks
Gardening – irrigation and water transfer
Aquariums – tank cleaning and water changes
Pools &amp; spas – draining and refilling
Workshops – handling light oils and fluids
Marine – boat water removal and fuel transfer
Construction – removing water from work areas
📦 Package Includes
1 × Electric Portable Drill Pump</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vf4AAeSwV3Rpy7Ab/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wYAAAeSwlBhpy6-X/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kPIAAeSwb5xpy6-X/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uMcAAeSwQKxpy6-Y/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YIoAAeSwgXdpy6-X/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/saAAAeSwEeppy6-X/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Garden &amp; Patio Ponds &amp; Water Features Pond &amp; Fountain Pumps</category><ean>404834091201</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.39</price><quantity>8</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091706</sku><product_name>2x Bicycle Handle Bar Grips Double Lock On BMX MTB Mountain Bike Cycle Grip UK</product_name><description>Description:


Color: Black, Red, White, Silver, Blue, Gold
Weight: 122g(About)
Application: Handlebars with an outer diameter of about 2.2cm
Material: Lock ring: Aluminum alloy; Grip: TPR rubber; Inner tube: High-strength plastic
Size: Length: 13cm; Outer diameter: 3cm; Inner diameter: 2.2cm


NOTE:Due to different lighting/camera conditions, there may be some color difference between the actual product and the picture. Please carefully understand before placing an order!


Features:
* Anti-skid design
* Ergonomic grip shape is molded to work with your body
* Comfort grip feeling, anti-slip design. Relieve your fatigue and hands pain for long distance cycling!
* Fast and accurately to remove and install
* Two screws fixed, easy to install.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V8QAAeSwqj5pyoPx/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XNsAAeSw-YFpyoPx/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XNoAAeSw-YFpyoPx/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/05kAAeSwIXFpyoPx/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YxEAAeSwlK5pyoPx/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/unQAAeSwxfNpyoPx/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Cycling Bike Components &amp; Parts Handlebar Grips, Tape &amp; Pads</category><ean>404834091706</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091805</sku><product_name>40 CD DVD Carry Case Disc Storage Holder CD Sleeve Wallet Ideal Car Lot</product_name><description>Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder

Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.

Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver
Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder
Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.
Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder

Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.

Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver

Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.
Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver
Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.
Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.




1 x DVD CD Storage Case</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YpYAAeSwoNZpynTn/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U1gAAeSwLDppynTm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RqkAAeSwOh5pynTm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZQwAAeSwiSJpynTm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/h08AAeSwyElpynTm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/h08AAeSwU4JpynTm/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Drives, Storage &amp; Blank Media Blank Media &amp; Accessories Media Cases, Sleeves &amp; Wallets</category><ean>404834091805</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091812</sku><product_name>130cm Leather Bag Strap – Replacement for Shoulder or Crossbody Bags</product_name><description>Description:

Item Type:Bag Belt
Material:Artificial PU Leather 
Width:1.8cm
Length :130cm Adjustable
Color: Black, Dark Blue, Coffee, Brown, Light brown, Red, Pink, White
Description:
100% brand new and high quality
Using PU leather made of material, feel are very good,
Strong and durable, work is also fine.
You can now make their own special hands-on bag.

Note:
Transition: 1cm=10mm=0.39inch
No retail package.
Please allow 1-2cm error due to manual measurement. pls make sure you do not mind before you bid.
Due to the difference between different monitors, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thank you!

Package includes:
1 x Shoulder strap(other accessories demo in the picture is not included.)</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Lx4AAeSwmFBpynDM/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uO8AAeSwnXZpynDL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/t8IAAeSw9A1pynDL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Le4AAeSwYZ9pynDL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/P2IAAeSwpFBpynDL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5PsAAeSwWtdpynDL/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Bags &amp; Handbags</category><ean>404834091812</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918209</sku><product_name>Reusable Lint Roller for Pet Hair Mini Portable Fur Remover for Clothes</product_name><description>Portable Lint Remover Pet Fur Clothes Fuzz Shaver – Reusable Jumper Trimmer Roller
Keep your clothes looking fresh, clean, and lint-free with this highly effective Portable Lint Remover. Designed for everyday convenience, this versatile tool works as both a Pet Fur Roller and a Shaver Jumper Trimmer, making it ideal for removing lint, fuzz, pet hair, and fabric pills in seconds.


⭐ Key Features
Dual Function Design – Combines a lint remover and Shaver Jumper Trimmer for efficient fabric care
Powerful Pet Hair Removal – Works as a reliable Pet Fur Roller to lift stubborn hair
Reusable &amp; Eco-Friendly – No sticky refills or batteries required
Safe on Fabrics – Gentle on wool, cotton, knitwear, and delicate garments
Portable &amp; Lightweight – Perfect for home, office, or travel use
Ergonomic Grip – Comfortable and easy to handle

📌 Technical Specifications
Material: Durable ABS plastic + metal blade
Power Source: Manual (no batteries required)
Size: Compact handheld design
Color: Varies (subject to availability)
Reusable: Yes – easy to clean

💡 Benefits
Instantly refreshes clothes and makes them look new
Saves money on disposable lint rollers
Perfect for pet owners dealing with fur
Quick and easy lint and fuzz removal
Maintains sweaters, coats, blankets, and upholstery

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Clothing Care: Sweaters, jackets, trousers, dresses
Pet Hair Removal: Clothes, pet beds, furniture
Home Furnishings: Sofas, cushions, curtains, carpets
Car Interior: Seats, mats, upholstery
Bedding &amp; Linens: Blankets, duvets, pillow covers
Office &amp; Travel: Quick touch-ups anywhere
Fabric Restoration: Removes bobbles from old garments
Multi-Surface Use: Wool, cotton, fleece, synthetics

🎯 Ideal For
Pet owners (cats &amp; dogs)
Sweaters, jumpers, and knitwear
Sofas, carpets, car seats, and bedding
Everyday clothing maintenance

⚠️ Where to Use Carefully
Delicate fabrics (silk, chiffon, lace) – use light pressure
Cashmere &amp; wool – gentle strokes only
Thin or worn clothing – avoid snagging
Printed or embroidered areas – avoid direct use
Loose threads or seams – do not pull
Upholstery – test on hidden area first
Synthetic fabrics – use gently

✅ Safe Usage Tips
Start with light pressure
Test on a hidden area first
Use on a flat surface
Clean regularly
Do not use on wet fabrics</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/e0MAAeSwbCppx8ws/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DxsAAeSwK6Jpx8wt/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/0y4AAeSw5ohpx8wt/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zZEAAeSwjAVpx8wt/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~zAAAeSwlONpx8wt/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DyEAAeSwK6Jpx8wt/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Laundry Supplies Lint Removers</category><ean>4048340918209</ean><condition>New</condition><price>4.89</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918278</sku><product_name>Welding Glue Metal Repair Paste AB Caster Glue Defect Repair Heat Resistant</product_name><description>Welding Glue Metal Repair Paste – AB Caster Glue, Heat Resistant &amp; Defect Repair ⚡
Fix, bond, and restore metal surfaces effortlessly with this premium Welding Glue Metal. Designed for durability and high performance, this AB caster paste repairs cracks, defects, and worn-out parts, providing a strong, heat-resistant solution for professionals and DIY enthusiasts alike.

⭐ Key Features
High Strength Bonding – Durable and reliable bond for metals, ceramics, and other hard surfaces
Defect Repair &amp; Restoration – Fills cracks, holes, and surface imperfections easily
Heat Resistant – Withstands temperatures up to 250°C (482°F)
Easy to Use – Two-component AB formula mixes smoothly for precise application
Rapid Setting &amp; Hardening – Quick curing saves time and delivers professional-quality results
Vast Applications – Works on metal, wood, ceramic, stone, and more
💡 Ideal For
Repairing metal machinery, automotive parts, and engine components
Fixing cracked pipes, housings, tools, and metal castings
DIY projects and household repairs requiring strong, heat-resistant bonds
Reinforcing structural parts, appliance components, or decorative items
🌐 Vast Applications of Usage
Industrial machinery maintenance and metal fabrication
Automotive repair: engines, radiators, exhaust systems
Household repairs: sinks, tiles, tools, metal furniture
Crafting and DIY projects with metal, ceramics, stone, and wood
Marine equipment, plumbing, and heating systems needing heat-resistant bonding
⚙️ Technical Specs
Type: AB Caster Welding Glue
Heat Resistance: Up to 250°C (482°F)
Color: Gray
Composition: Two-part epoxy resin
💎 Benefits
Extend the life of metal parts and machinery
Save costs on replacements
Professional-quality repair without welding equipment
Works on metal, wood, ceramics, and stone</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/O04AAeSwwRlptb1g/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/smEAAeSwbiZptb1h/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lfcAAeSwPU9ptb1h/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/g10AAeSwj4Fptb1f/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/N14AAeSw1adptb1g/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xyYAAeSwxxJptb1g/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Business, Office &amp; Industrial Adhesives, Sealants &amp; Tapes Glues, Epoxies &amp; Cements Liquid Glues &amp; Cements</category><ean>4048340918278</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918285</sku><product_name>New Digital Tire Pressure Gauge Backlight LCD Tyre Air Monitoring Meter 150PSI H</product_name><description>New Digital Tire Pressure Gauge – Backlight LCD Tyre Air Monitoring Meter 150PSI ⚡
Keep your vehicle safe and tires in perfect condition with this Digital Tire Pressure Gauge. This Tyre Air Monitoring Meter delivers fast, precise readings up to 150 PSI, helping maintain optimal tire pressure and extend tire life.

⭐ Key Features
High Accuracy Measurement – Precise tire pressure readings up to 150 PSI
Backlit LCD Display – Clear digital display, even in low light or at night
Wide Compatibility – Works with cars, motorcycles, bicycles, SUVs, and trucks
Compact &amp; Portable – Lightweight, fits in glove box or toolbox
Quick &amp; Easy Use – Instant readings, no setup required
Durable Construction – Built to withstand everyday use with long-lasting reliability
💡 Ideal For
Regular drivers maintaining proper tire pressure
Motorists improving fuel efficiency and tire lifespan
Mechanics, garages, and roadside assistance professionals
Cyclists and motorbike riders for on-the-go monitoring
Anyone wanting quick, accurate tire pressure checks
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Cars &amp; SUVs – Ensure safe driving and extend tire life
Motorcycles &amp; Scooters – Quick, precise checks before rides
Bicycles – Maintain optimal tire pressure
Trucks &amp; Vans – Essential for commercial vehicles
Outdoor &amp; Adventure Vehicles – ATVs, off-road vehicles, trailers
Workshops &amp; Garages – Professional tire maintenance and inspection
⚙️ Technical Specs
Measurement Range: 0–150 PSI
Display: Digital LCD with backlight
Units: PSI / BAR / KPA / KG/CM²
Power: 2 x AAA batteries (included or optional)
Material: High-quality ABS plastic &amp; stainless steel nozzle
🚚 Free Shipping
Fast &amp; reliable delivery
Secure packaging for safe arrival
No extra charges – what you see is what you pay</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XAkAAeSwpZxptbid/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/klUAAeSwR51ptbie/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/af0AAeSw1-Nptbie/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4WMAAeSwGjxptbid/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/b6YAAeSw~dxptbid/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dvEAAeSw551ptbid/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Wheels, Tyres &amp; Parts Wheel &amp; Tyre Accessories Other Tyre Accessories</category><ean>4048340918285</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.83</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091836</sku><product_name>Auto Mirror Adjustable Wide Angle Side Rear Mirror Blind Spot Convex Mirrors For</product_name><description>Features
Adjustable viewing angle for safe parking, it allows you to see clearly the rear wheel, thus it is easier to back up your car
Wide-angle convex design lets you see wider field of vision,removes blind spots, perfectly to new drivers
Can be installed either elow or above rear view mirrors. Easy installation with strong stickers.
Aerodynamic principle design,streamlined appearance, perfect match with your car


Material: ABS+glass

Weight: 50g (single piece)

Product packaging: 1pcs

Suitable for vehicle type: universal


Installation method:

Installation method on the reflector

1. Determine the position of the adhesive on the vehicle's rearview mirror and wipe it clean

2. Tear off the double-sided adhesive protective layer on the bottom bracket of the product and stick it on the cleaned mirror surface

Installation method of rearview mirror

1. Confirm the position of the rearview mirror on the vehicle and wipe it clean

2. Insert one end of the insert provided with the product onto the product, then tear off the double-sided adhesive protective layer on the other end and stick it to the desired installation area

3. After adjusting the angle, it can be used.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8kMAAeSwULhpsVGI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GIEAAeSwVqdpsVGI/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6R0AAeSw7vtpsVGI/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/W74AAeSw-6ZpsVGI/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/HDMAAeSwqihpsVGI/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/HhEAAeSwu6hpsVGI/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Exterior Parts &amp; Accessories Side View Mirrors Mirror Assemblies</category><ean>404834091836</ean><condition>New</condition><price>4.89</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091867</sku><product_name>Mini Shaver USB Rechargeable Pocket Sized Portable Electric Shaver Razor For Men</product_name><description>Mini Shaver USB Rechargeable – Pocket Sized Portable Electric Shaver for Men ⚡
Stay sharp wherever you go with this Pocket Sized and Portable Mini Electric Shaver. Designed for convenience, performance, and modern lifestyles, this compact grooming tool delivers a smooth shave anytime, anywhere – perfect for travel, work, or daily use.

⭐ Key Features
Pocket Sized Design – Ultra-compact and lightweight, easily fits in your pocket, bag, or car
Portable Convenience – Ideal for travel, business trips, gym, and on-the-go grooming
USB Rechargeable – Charge anywhere via power bank, laptop, or USB adapter
Precision Shaving – Sharp stainless steel blades ensure a clean, smooth shave
Easy to Clean – Detachable head for quick and hygienic cleaning
Quiet Operation – Low-noise motor for comfortable grooming experience
📊 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Electric Mini Shaver
Power Source: USB Rechargeable
Blade Material: Stainless Steel
Size: Pocket Sized / Compact Design
Charging Time: Approx. 1–2 hours
Usage Time: Up to 60 minutes (varies by use)
Suitable For: Face, Beard, Light Trimming
✅ Benefits
Stay groomed anytime with a portable shaving solution
Save time with quick and efficient shaving performance
Perfect backup shaver for emergencies or busy schedules
Travel-friendly design eliminates the need for bulky grooming kits
🎯 Ideal For
Daily quick touch-ups and clean shaving
Travel, holidays, and business trips
Office, car, or gym use
Last-minute grooming before meetings or events
Students, professionals, and frequent travellers
Keeping in your bag or car as an emergency shaver
🌍 Vast Application of Usage
Face shaving and beard maintenance
Trimming light stubble and sideburns
Quick clean-ups before dates, meetings, or video calls
Travel grooming kit essential
Use at home, office, car, or even outdoors
Ideal for campers, hikers, and frequent flyers
Backup shaver for emergencies or power outages
Suitable for maintaining a neat look during long workdays
Great for minimalist grooming routines
Can be used for light body grooming (arms, neckline, etc.)
📦 Package Includes
1 × Mini Electric Shaver
1 × USB Charging Cable
1 × Cleaning Brush</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/O1EAAeSwDzZprp4w/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5dMAAeSwomBprp4v/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4LkAAeSwjLdprp5h/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/M7IAAeSwtqRprp5u/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZNYAAeSwzNpprp4w/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Business, Office &amp; Industrial Healthcare, Lab &amp; Dental Medical &amp; Lab Equipment, Devices Other Medical &amp; Lab Equipm</category><ean>404834091867</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091874</sku><product_name>Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap - Hygienic Handheld Toilet Kit</product_name><description>Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap – Hygienic Handheld Toilet Kit (UK Stock)
Upgrade your bathroom hygiene with this Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap, designed for convenience, cleanliness, and durability. This practical Handheld Toilet Kit delivers a strong yet controlled water spray, providing a more hygienic and comfortable alternative to traditional cleaning methods. With a sleek chrome finish and easy installation, it is a perfect addition to any modern bathroom.


⭐ Key Features
Hygienic Cleaning Solution – Ensures effective and refreshing cleaning with a smooth, controlled water flow.
Premium Chrome Finish – Rust-resistant chrome coating adds durability and a modern bathroom look.
Ergonomic Handheld Design – Easy-grip Handheld Toilet Kit designed for comfort and simple operation.
Flexible Hose Included – Durable flexible hose allows extended reach and convenient use.
Leak-Resistant Construction – Built with high-quality materials for reliable and long-lasting performance.
Quick &amp; Easy Installation – Easily connects to most standard bathroom taps or water outlets.
Compact &amp; Space Saving – Wall-mounted design keeps your bathroom organised and clutter-free.

🌍 Vast Applications &amp; Multiple Uses
This versatile Bidet Spray Tap is designed for a wide range of everyday uses:

Personal hygiene and toilet cleaning
Muslim ablution (wudu) preparation
Washing baby cloth nappies / diapers
Cleaning the toilet bowl and bathroom floor
Rinsing reusable sanitary products
Pet bathing and washing small animals
Filling buckets or cleaning containers
Washing muddy shoes or slippers
Balcony or garden rinsing tasks
General household cleaning where controlled water spray is needed

🏆 Why This Bidet Spray Tap Is Better Than Others
Stronger &amp; Controlled Water Pressure – Efficient cleaning without excessive water usage.
High-Quality Chrome Finish – More durable and rust-resistant compared to standard plastic sprayers.
Ergonomic Trigger Design – Smooth press handle offers better control and comfortable use.
Multi-Purpose Functionality – Ideal for hygiene and many cleaning tasks around the home.
Durable Hose Construction – Reinforced hose prevents leaks, cracks, and wear over time.
Easy Universal Installation – Compatible with most standard bathroom plumbing fittings.
Long-Lasting Performance – Built for everyday use with reliable and sturdy materials.

📦 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Bidet Spray Tap / Handheld Toilet Kit
Material: ABS with Chrome Finish
Hose Material: Reinforced Stainless Steel / Flexible Hose
Colour: Chrome Silver
Installation Type: Wall Mounted / Tap Connection
Hose Length: Approx. 1.2 m – 1.5 m
Spray Control: Manual Trigger Operation
Compatibility: Fits most standard bathroom fittings

✅ Benefits
Improves personal hygiene and comfort
Eco-friendly alternative to excessive toilet paper use
Durable rust-resistant construction
Multi-purpose cleaning tool for home and bathroom
Convenient handheld control for precise water use

🏠 Ideal For
Home bathrooms
Muslim households for daily ablution needs
Apartments and rental properties
Elderly care and hygiene support
Hotels, guest houses, and rental accommodations

📦 Package Includes
1 × Chrome Bidet Spray Head
1 × Flexible Hose
1 × Wall Holder / Mount (if included)
Installation fittings</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U04AAeSwdBxpUoeO/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gQkAAeSwMX9pUoeR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZLAAAeSwgjRpUoeb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i~sAAeSwukVpUoea/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kUwAAeSwUzJpUoeN/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Yr4AAeSwHd1pUoeS/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Toilets &amp; Bidets Bidets</category><ean>404834091874</ean><condition>New</condition><price>11.19</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091898</sku><product_name>TWS Sports Wireless Bluetooth Earphones Headphones Ear Hook Running Bass Earbuds</product_name><description>TWS Sports Wireless Bluetooth Earphones Headphones Ear Hook Running Bass Earbuds


Item description from the seller:
Enjoy your workouts, runs, and daily life with total freedom. These TWS Sports Wireless Bluetooth Earphones are built for people who love to move. With a secure ear hook design, powerful sound, and waterproof protection, they’re made to keep up with your lifestyle—no wires, no limits.Whether you're running, working out, gaming, or relaxing with your favorite tunes, these earphones deliver crystal-clear sound and deep bass that make every beat feel alive.

Features
·         Seamless Bluetooth 5.3 Connection: Stable, fast, and easy pairing with your smartphone, tablet, or laptop for uninterrupted listening.

·         Comfortable Ear Hook Design: Stays firmly in place no matter how hard you train—perfect for running, gym, or outdoor use.

·         HiFi Stereo Sound: Crisp highs, rich mids, and powerful bass create a truly immersive audio experience.

·         Waterproof &amp; Sweatproof: Designed to handle sweat and rain so you can focus on your goals without worry.

·         Built-In Microphone: Enjoy hands-free calls and clear voice quality anywhere, anytime.

·         Smart LED Power Display: Stay informed about your battery level with a clear digital indicator on the charging case.

·         Long Battery Life: Enjoy hours of playtime on a single charge with the convenient charging case.

Specifications
·         Bluetooth Version: 5.3

·         Connection Type: Wireless

·         Vocal Principle: Dynamic

·         Control Button: Yes

·         Volume Control: No

·         Waterproof: Yes

·         Active Noise Cancellation: Yes

·         Microphone: Built-in

·         Charging Method: USB Cable

·         Style: In-ear with ear hook

·         Usage: Sport, Gym, Outdoor, Office, Gaming, Study, Travel

Package Includes
·         1 × Pair of Wireless Earphones

·         1 × Charging Case with LED Display

·         1 × USB Charging Cable

·         1 × User Manual</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aEcAAeSwqjNpp0sc/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ygIAAeSw779pp0sd/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/x3kAAeSw5WJpp0sc/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ykAAAeSwsO1pp0sb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xw0AAeSwAZNpp0sc/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aEgAAeSwqjNpp0sc/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Sound &amp; Vision Portable Audio &amp; Headphones Headphones</category><ean>404834091898</ean><condition>New</condition><price>10.21</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091904</sku><product_name>EXTRA SOFT SILICONE RUBBER WATCH BAND STRAP 10.15.16.18.20.21.22MM QUICK RELEASE</product_name><description>EXTRA SOFT SILICONE RUBBER WATCH BAND STRAP 10.15.16.18.20.21.22MM QUICK RELEASE

Item Description:
Looking for a strap that feels good all day and looks clean on any watch? This extra soft silicone watch band is made for comfort, flexibility, and everyday use. It’s lightweight on your wrist but strong enough for daily wear — whether you're at work, at the gym, or out with friends.The smooth silicone material sits comfortably on the skin and doesn’t feel stiff. The quick release pins make it easy to swap straps in seconds — no tools, no stress. Just click in and go.It fits most traditional watches and many smartwatches with a flat interface. Simple, practical, and ready for daily life.

Features:

Extra soft silicone rubber for all-day comfort
Flexible, durable, and sweat-resistant
Quick release spring bars – easy to install and remove
Stainless steel silver buckle for secure fit
Lightweight design, comfortable for sports and casual wear
Clean, modern look suitable for men and women
Multiple sizes available to fit most watches
Specifications:

Material: High quality silicone rubber
Buckle Material: Stainless steel (silver tone)
Available Widths: 14mm, 16mm, 18mm, 19mm, 20mm, 21mm, 22mm, 24mm
Length: Approx. 120mm + 75mm
Thickness: Approx. 3mm
Weight: Approx. 20g
Interface Type: Flat interface with quick release pins
Package Includes:

1 × Silicone Watch Band
Quick Release Pins (pre-installed)</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9YAAAeSw8jpppzi6/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/66UAAeSwBxdppzi6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9P0AAeSw3ylppzi7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AlAAAeSw~ZZppzi6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/glQAAeSwnQFppzi6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8TQAAeSw9s1ppzi6/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Jewellery &amp; Watches Watches, Parts &amp; Accessories Watch Accessories Wristwatch Straps</category><ean>404834091904</ean><condition>New</condition><price>17.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091911</sku><product_name>300ml Neti Pot Sinus Rinse Bottle | Nasal Irrigation Kit Nose Wash Cleaner UK</product_name><description>Description

Description:
100% brand new and high quality
Capacity 500/300ml, can be used for entire families
Standard wash nose, wash nose for adult/child

Features:

Nasal wash is based on human nasal internal physiological structure characteristic for product design, experts recommend regular cleaning of the nasal cavity within the nasal cavity to remove dirt, pollen, postoperative residue, dust, etc. have a good effect to help, an individual daily nasal care and care of practical product

Packaging: safety bubble bag

How to Use:

1. Pour a package of 4.5 /2.7g nasal wash salt into the water bottle ,then add warm water to the 500 /300ml mark.
2. Please make sure water temperature is around 37℃. It should feel lukewarm if touched by finger tips .Mix nasal wash salt thouroughly until completely dissolved ,and then tighten the cap.
3. Choose the correct nozzle :Be sure to select the child nasal wash tip for children .Children cannot use adult tip.
4. Correct posture :Have your upper body leaning forward , looking down ,and with head slightly leaning no side ,Hold bottle upside down ,and gently insert the tip into one nostril .Relax ,open mouth slightly and breath (through mouth ) .DO NOT hold your breath, DO NOT breath through nose .Press the valve button at the bottom of the water bottle (Figure 1),and the solution will automatically flow .DO NOT squeeze the water bottle . Rinse solution will enter the nostril and bathe the nose and sinus and exit the other nostril.When finishing washing one nostril ,release the button to stop the solution .Rotate to wash both nostrils.

Precautions:

Do not use water or regular salt instead of nasal wash sale
To avoid and discomfort ,mix nasal wash salt solution to the proper concentration by strictly following the instruction in this user guide
Do not use if one side of the nose plugs,or when having otitis media or other ear disease
Children 8 years or under should use this product under the guidance of the physician and parent
Wash the machine throuroughly before and after each use


The product should be stored in a cool ,dry ,well-ventilated place .Avoid direct sunlight ,and kept it away from corrosive liquid or gas
Note: Due to the difference between different monitors, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thank you!

Package List:

1 x 300ML/500ML Nasal Wash Bottle (As you choose)</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vQkAAeSwVftpole6/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uMoAAeSwIQhpole6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1fYAAeSwBvRpole5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MdAAAeSweK1pole6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/pkkAAeSwmsdpole6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Rg8AAeSwDAFpole6/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Business, Office &amp; Industrial Healthcare, Lab &amp; Dental Medical &amp; Lab Equipment, Devices Other Medical &amp; Lab Equipmen</category><ean>404834091911</ean><condition>New</condition><price>11.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091928</sku><product_name>75cm Long Reach Flexible Radiator Brush Heater Cleaner/Duster brush</product_name><description>class="extend--iframe--to7hHIV" data-spm-anchor-id="a2g0o.detail.0.i1.100cACfcACfcnW" data-spm-act-id="a2g0o.detail.0.i1.100cACfcACfcnW" style="box-sizing: border-box; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent; outline: 0px; margin: 0px; padding: 0px; height: 10808.1px; position: absolute; top: 0px; visibility: hidden; width: 1068.6px; z-index: -1;"&gt;</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VqYAAeSwEJxpntwp/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BYMAAeSwYJFpntmW/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RDAAAeSwAg9pntmW/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/S8wAAeSwm0dpntmV/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TbUAAeSwWPppntmV/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/72cAAeSwKpFpntmU/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Cleaning Tools Cleaning Brushes</category><ean>404834091928</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.69</price><quantity>9</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091942</sku><product_name>Cyperus Rotundus Oil 60ml For Hair Removal Reducing Body Hair Growth</product_name><description>Features:
1. Gentle Plant-Based Formula for Smooth and Caring Hair Removal

Infused with selected botanical extracts and modern skincare technology, this formula gently softens body hair and relaxes follicles for a smoother removal process. It significantly minimizes discomfort and physical irritation, offering a delicate and skin-friendly experience that cares for your sensitive skin.

2. Purify and Prep Skin to Prevent Irritation

The product cleanses and purifies the skin’s surface, helping to unclog hair follicles before hair removal. By reducing the risk of clogged pores, it prevents common issues like red spots and ingrown hairs—leaving your skin cleaner, healthier, and prepped for a flawless experience.

3. Deep Hydration to Soothe and Restore Skin

After hair removal, skin often feels dry and sensitive. Enriched with natural moisturizing ingredients, our product penetrates deeply to replenish moisture, calm irritation, and relieve tightness. It helps restore a hydrated, smooth texture—so you can say goodbye to post-wax dryness and roughness.

4. Daily Care for Long-Term Silky Skin

More than just a hair removal aid, it’s also a daily skincare essential. With regular use, it helps maintain follicle health, resulting in finer, softer, and sparser regrowth over time. Meanwhile, the nutrient-rich formula continuously nourishes the skin, improving its texture, elasticity, and overall radiance day by day.

How to use:

1. Before use, please thoroughly clean the area that needs hair removal and ensure that the skin is in a completely dry state.

2. Take an appropriate amount of essential oil in the palm of your hand, apply it evenly to the target area, and gently massage with fingertips in circular motions for 2-3 minutes until the skin feels slightly warm. This step can help essential oils penetrate, fully soften hair roots, moisturize surrounding skin, and prepare for hair removal.

3. When performing physical hair removal operations such as scraping or using hair removal devices, the lubricating layer formed by essential oils can effectively reduce the irritation caused by scraping. After depilation, a small amount of essential oil can be taken again and gently applied to the depilated area to soothe the skin, instantly hydrate, and relieve possible burning or dryness.

4. As a daily care, a small amount of essential oil can be taken and massaged on the desired area until absorbed. Long term use can continuously moisturize the skin, inhibit hair growth rate, make newly formed hair soft and fine, and help develop a long-lasting smooth and delicate skin feel.


Notice:
* Please store in a cool place to avoid high temperature and direct sunlight.

* Please keep this product out of the reach of  children.

* Actual color May be slightly different from the image due to different monitor and light effect.

* Please allow 1-3cm deviation due to manual measurement.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/64YAAeSwSSBpx2zH/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FPoAAeSwxbJpj2Lm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EYMAAeSwd0lpj2Lm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jxIAAeSwx~Fpj2Lm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7ksAAeSwERtpj2Lm/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6u4AAeSwdzRpj2Lm/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Natural &amp; Alternative Remedies Herbal Remedies &amp; Resins</category><ean>404834091942</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.73</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091959</sku><product_name>Wireless Ear Wax Removal Tool WiFi Otoscope Spoon Cleaner Camera Ear Pick Kit UK</product_name><description>Item Specifics
Material :	ABS
Brand :	Unbranded
Type :	Ear Wax Removal Kit
Features :	High-Precision,Washable,Portable,Reusable
MixColour :	Black,White
Compatibility :	Fit for iPhone, iPad, Android Phone/Tablet
LED Light :	6 LED
Input Current :	DC 5V/150mA
Pixel :	HD
Department :	Everyone
Charging Interface :	Type-C
Sight Angle :	100°
Lens Inner Diameter :	3.6mm
Focal Length :	15~20mm
Waterproof Grade :	IPX65</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8z0AAeSw0Ttpj174/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~tEAAeSwVjJpj11Q/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6-sAAeSwfX1pj11Q/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xhgAAeSw8s5pj11Q/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zQ8AAeSwzl1pj11R/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lrkAAeSwpttpj11Q/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Health Care Ear Care Ear Wax Removers</category><ean>404834091959</ean><condition>New</condition><price>15.99</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091966</sku><product_name>Wireless Car Charger Fast Charging Automatic Clamping 30W Mount Phone Holder UK</product_name><description>Wireless Car Charger Fast Charging Automatic Clamping 30W Mount Phone Holder (UK) ⚡🚗
Upgrade your driving experience with this Car Fast Charger featuring Automatic Clamping 30W technology. Designed for convenience, speed, and safety, this smart mount securely holds your phone while delivering rapid wireless charging on the go.


⭐ Key Features
30W Fast Wireless Charging – Delivers high-speed power for compatible devices
Automatic Clamping Technology – Intelligent sensors securely grip your phone
One-Hand Operation – Effortless mounting and release for safer driving
Strong &amp; Stable Mount – Keeps your device secure even on rough roads
360° Rotation – Adjustable viewing angle for navigation and hands-free use
Universal Compatibility – Works with most Qi-enabled smartphones
Smart Protection System – Prevents overcharging, overheating, and short circuits

🔧 Technical Specifications
Charging Power: Up to 30W Fast Charging
Input: USB-C
Mount Type: Air Vent / Dashboard
Material: ABS + PC Durable Build
Compatibility: Qi-enabled smartphones (4.7–6.9 inches approx.)
Rotation: 360° adjustable
Sensor Type: Infrared automatic clamping

✅ Benefits
Hands-free convenience for navigation, calls, and music
Fast charging while driving
Improved driving safety
Modern and sleek design

🎯 Ideal For
Daily commuters
Ride-share drivers (Uber, Bolt, etc.)
Long-distance travelers
Anyone needing reliable in-car charging

🔄 Wide Applications
GPS navigation while charging
Hands-free calling and video use
Music streaming during drives
Road trips and business travel
Suitable for cars, SUVs, and vans</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BOgAAeSwOIdpj2C0/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/20QAAeSw6~hpj2C0/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bqkAAeSwl8Vpj2C0/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~RkAAeSwMXtpj2C0/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3MgAAeSwhA5pj2Cx/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834091966</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.81</price><quantity>6</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091973</sku><product_name>Pack of 4 Luxury Quilted Zipped Pillow Protectors Soft Pillow Pairs White Cover</product_name><description>Key Features
Luxury Quilted Design – Soft, padded quilting adds extra comfort and a premium hotel-quality feel
Secure Zipped Closure – Fully enclosed zipper keeps pillows protected from dust, dirt, and allergens
Soft &amp; Breathable Fabric – Gentle on skin, ensuring a cool and comfortable night’s sleep
Durable &amp; Long-Lasting – High-quality stitching maintains shape and performance after multiple washes
Pack of 4 (2 Pairs) – Ideal Soft Pillow Pairs for complete bedding protection

📏 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Quilted Zipped Pillow Protector
Quantity: Pack of 4 (2 Pairs)
Color: White
Material: Soft microfiber/polycotton blend (breathable &amp; durable)
Closure Type: Zippered
Care Instructions: Machine washable &amp; quick drying
Fit: Standard size pillows (approx. 48 x 74 cm – may vary slightly)

💡 Why Choose These Pillow Protectors?
Extends the life of your pillows by protecting against spills, stains, and wear
Helps maintain a cleaner, more hygienic sleeping environment
Adds an extra layer of softness for improved comfort
Easy to remove and wash, making everyday care effortless
Ideal for homes, hotels, guest rooms, and rental properties

🛏️ What It Is Ideal For
Allergy Sufferers – Helps reduce exposure to dust mites and allergens
Families &amp; Kids – Protects pillows from spills, sweat, and everyday mess
Hotels &amp; Guest Rooms – Maintains cleanliness and extends pillow lifespan
Travel &amp; Temporary Stays – Adds a hygienic layer wherever you sleep
Pet Owners – Shields pillows from fur, dander, and odors
Anyone Seeking Extra Comfort – Adds a soft, quilted layer for better sleep quality

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Home Bedding – Perfect for daily use on all household pillows
Hospitality Industry – Ideal for hotels, Airbnb, guest houses, and serviced apartments
Healthcare Settings – Suitable for clinics, care homes, and recovery environments
Student Accommodation – Great for dorm rooms and shared living spaces
Travel &amp; Camping – Adds hygiene and comfort when using portable pillows
Rental Properties – Helps maintain cleanliness and reduce replacement costs
Seasonal Protection – Keeps pillows fresh during storage or off-season use
Decorative Pillows – Protects cushions used in living rooms and lounges
Workspaces &amp; Offices – Useful for nap pillows or relaxation areas</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oQkAAeSw-vppedGJ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Im0AAeSwoRFpedGJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/H~kAAeSwCZZpedGJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fF0AAeSw~85pedGK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LPIAAeSwQXhpedGJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oO4AAeSwAYFpedGK/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bedding Mattress &amp; Pillow Protectors</category><ean>404834091973</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092000</sku><product_name>Soft Padded Sleep 3D Mask Eye Blackout Luxurious Blindfold Travel Eye Cover UK</product_name><description>Key Features
• 3D Contoured Design – Provides a comfortable fit without pressure on eyes or eyelashes
• Complete Blackout – Blocks all light to improve sleep quality and promote relaxation
• Soft Padded Comfort – High-quality memory foam padding for gentle cushioning
• Adjustable Strap – One-size-fits-all with secure, flexible fit for any head size
• Lightweight &amp; Breathable – Keeps you cool and comfortable throughout the night
• Durable &amp; Easy to Clean – Long-lasting fabric that can be hand-washed

📏 Technical Specifications
Material: Memory Foam + Soft Fabric
Color: Black
Dimensions: Approx. 8.3 x 3.9 inches (21 x 10 cm)
Weight: 25g

💤 Ideal For
Nighttime sleep at home
Power naps or relaxation during the day
Travel: flights, trains, buses, or cars
Meditation and mindfulness sessions
Shift workers who need to sleep during daylight hours
Reducing eye strain and fatigue after screen use

🌟 Vast Applications of Usage
Sleep improvement for all ages – adults and teens
Relaxation during yoga, meditation, or spa treatments
Travel companion for business trips or vacations
Enhancing focus and calm during reading or screen breaks
Relief for migraines, headaches, and eye fatigue

💤 Benefits
Helps reduce eye strain and fatigue
Promotes deeper sleep and relaxation by blocking distractions
Supports better sleep quality and alertness during waking hours

✅ Why Choose This Mask?
Superior 3D blackout design ensures no light leaks
Soft padded memory foam provides unmatched comfort
Lightweight, durable, and easy to maintain</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FscAAeSwlfxpRqwR/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/S6kAAeSwRv9pRqwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/J4MAAeSwoYJpRqwH/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/x04AAeSwae5pRqwG/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/S04AAeSwm~NpRqwK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2KkAAeSwxcRpRqwL/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Luggage &amp; Travel Accessories Travel Accessories Eye Masks</category><ean>404834092000</ean><condition>New</condition><price>3.49</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092024</sku><product_name>Freeview Indoor TV Aerial 250 Mile Digital HDTV 0.5mm Ultra Thin Signal Booster</product_name><description>Key Features:
Ultra Thin Signal Booster: Enhances weak signals for sharper, clearer digital TV reception
Wide Coverage: Reliable reception up to 250 miles from the transmitter
Digital HDTV Ready: Optimized for Freeview, FreeSat, and other digital channels
Indoor Convenience: Compact and lightweight design for easy placement anywhere
Easy Installation: Plug-and-play setup with included cable; no professional help required
Durable Build: Premium materials ensure long-lasting performance

⚙️ Technical Specifications:
Frequency Range	47–862 MHz
Gain	Up to 20dB
Impedance	75Ω
Cable Length	1.5m (included)
Dimensions	30cm x 15cm x 0.5cm (Ultra Thin)

💡 Ideal For:
Apartments and flats without outdoor antenna access
Homes in urban or suburban areas with variable signal strength
Digital TV enthusiasts wanting a compact, stylish solution
Anyone seeking hassle-free, high-quality Freeview reception

🛠️ How to Use:
Connect the included cable from the aerial to your TV’s antenna input.
Position the aerial near a window or high up for optimal signal reception.
Turn on your TV and run the channel scan function to detect Freeview or digital channels.
Adjust the aerial placement slightly if needed for the clearest reception.
Enjoy stable, high-definition digital TV signals with minimal interference.

🌐 Vast Applications:
Living rooms, bedrooms, kitchens, and home offices
Apartments, flats, and small homes with limited outdoor antenna access
Works with Freeview, FreeSat, digital HDTV, and other compatible devices
Urban and rural areas, dorms, caravans, and holiday homes
Secondary TVs where installing an outdoor antenna is impractical

💡 Benefits:
Stable, crystal-clear TV reception without messy outdoor antennas
Compact, stylish design blends perfectly in any room
Strong signal even in areas with weak reception
Easy setup for anyone, regardless of technical experience</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sEMAAeSwN-ppcMJK/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Zt4AAeSw2edpcMJK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oDIAAeSwdwZpcMJK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/amUAAeSwshJpcMJJ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tlEAAeSwxChpcMJK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/o6wAAeSwGRlpcMJJ/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092024</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.73</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092031</sku><product_name>Microwave Food Cover Anti Splatter Transparent Plate Lid with Handle Kitchen UK</product_name><description>Key Features
Advanced Anti Splatter Design – Prevents sauce, oil, and food splashes from coating your microwave interior
Transparent Plate Lid – Clear visibility lets you monitor food without interrupting heating
Ergonomic Heat-Resistant Handle – Safe, comfortable grip for easy lifting and handling
Steam Vent System – Allows controlled steam release to prevent soggy food and pressure build-up
Even Heat Distribution – Helps food reheat faster and more evenly
Multi-Purpose Use – Ideal for reheating meals, leftovers, vegetables, rice, pasta, and more
Universal Fit – Compatible with most standard plates, bowls, and dishes

📐 Technical Specifications
Material: BPA-free, food-grade heat-resistant plastic
Colour: Transparent
Design: Ventilated dome lid with raised handle
Microwave Safe: Yes
Dishwasher Safe: Yes (top rack recommended)
Reusable &amp; Eco-Friendly: Yes

✅ Key Benefits
Keeps your microwave cleaner for longer, reducing maintenance and odors
Saves time by eliminating frequent microwave cleaning
Improves food texture by maintaining moisture while preventing overheating
Safer alternative to cling film or paper towels
Durable, lightweight, and easy to store
Perfect for homes, offices, student kitchens, and meal prep
🎯 Ideal For
Busy households needing quick and mess-free reheating
Office workers and students using shared microwaves
Families looking to keep appliances clean and hygienic
Meal prep enthusiasts reheating pre-cooked meals
Heating leftovers like curries, soups, pasta, and rice without splatter
Use in homes, dorm rooms, caravans, and workplace kitchens

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Reheating a wide variety of foods including rice, curries, soups, vegetables, and snacks
Covering dishes to retain moisture and prevent food from drying out
Protecting microwave interiors from grease, oil, and sauce splashes
Ideal for defrosting frozen food while minimizing mess
Useful as a temporary food cover to keep meals warm before serving
Perfect for use in shared kitchens to maintain cleanliness and hygiene
Suitable for daily cooking, meal prepping, and food storage routines

🏠 Why Choose This Microwave Cover?
This Anti Splatter Transparent Plate Lid is a must-have kitchen accessory for efficient, hygienic, and stress-free microwave cooking. Designed for daily use, it delivers long-lasting performance while protecting both your food and your appliance.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/a-0AAeSwdLRpQqKU/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/khsAAeSw0dZpQqKa/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T8gAAeSwtWZpQqKK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vFkAAeSwKu1pQqKe/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sucAAeSwIARpQqKK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BAIAAeSwRw5pQqKS/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Cookware, Dining &amp; Bar Kitchen Tools &amp; Gadgets Other Food Preparation &amp; Too</category><ean>404834092031</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.39</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092048</sku><product_name>3D Optical Illusion Cave Scenery Door Mat Non-Slip Washable for Home &amp; OutdoorUK</product_name><description>Key Features
3D Optical Illusion Design: High-resolution print creates a bold depth effect
Non-Slip Backing: Anti-skid base keeps the mat securely in place
Soft &amp; Absorbent Microfiber: Plush feel that absorbs moisture and dirt
Quick-Drying &amp; Hygienic: Breathable material helps prevent odors
Machine Washable: Easy to clean, fade-resistant, and durable

🎯 Ideal For
Bathrooms – Keeps floors dry and safe after showers
Bedrooms – Adds comfort beside your bed
Living Rooms – Stylish accent piece for modern décor
Entryways &amp; Hallways – Traps dirt and moisture from shoes
Kitchens – Soft support while standing and cooking
Yoga &amp; Workout Areas – Comfortable surface for light exercise
Offices &amp; Study Rooms – Enhances comfort and aesthetics
Travel &amp; Camping – Lightweight and easy to carry

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Home décor enhancement for modern and minimalist interiors
High-traffic areas to reduce slipping risks
Kids’ rooms and play areas for added softness and safety
Pet areas to absorb spills, water, and fur mess
Laundry rooms to keep floors dry and clean
Hotel rooms, guest houses, and Airbnb spaces
Salon, spa, and barbershop flooring for comfort and hygiene
Gym corners and fitness setups at home
Outdoor covered areas such as balconies or patios
Office entrances and reception areas for a professional look</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/cMUAAeSwoo1pQ7n6/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y7gAAeSwWvdpQ7n5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sY8AAeSwOjZpQ7n5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ff0AAeSwYo9pQ7n5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-t0AAeSwCrhpQ7n6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lxsAAeSwQyhpQ7px/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household Accessories &amp; Supplies Rugs &amp; Carpets Door Mats &amp; Floor Mats</category><ean>404834092048</ean><condition>New</condition><price>19.99</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092055</sku><product_name>Men &amp; Women Chest Pack Anti Theft Travel Bag Cross Body Bag Travel Waist 2024 UK</product_name><description>Anti-Theft Sling Backpack – 4-Way Wear Waterproof – Secure Travel Bag – UK Ready
Hidden Zips • Cut-Resistant Strap • IPX4 Waterproof • Lightweight • 4 Comfortable Wears

🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Travel smarter and safer with this 4-Way Wear Anti-Theft Sling Bag, designed for UK commuting, travel, and everyday adventures. Combining advanced security features, weather resistance, and a compact design, it keeps your essentials protected while staying comfortable on the move.

Perfect for busy cities, public transport, festivals, and travel, this sling bag provides hands-free convenience without compromising safety.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Advanced Anti-Theft Protection – Hidden zips, locking clasps, and reinforced cut-resistant strap
🔹 IPX4 Water-Resistant – Designed for UK rain and splashes – water-repellent fabric and sealed zippers
🔹 4-Way Wear Design – Wear as a chest bag, crossbody sling, shoulder bag, or waist pack
🔹 Slim &amp; Lightweight – Only 420g, perfect for daily commuting and travel
🔹 Anti-Slash Fabric – Heavy-duty 600D ripstop Oxford material with steel cable reinforced strap
🔹 Hidden Zipper Layout – Positions zips against your body to deter pickpockets
🔹 Chest Access Design – Quick visibility and access to your essentials
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Anti-Theft Sling Bag / Backpack
Size	31 × 23 × 10 cm (12.2″ × 9″ × 3.9″)
Capacity	6 Litres
Weight	420g (0.93 lbs) – lightweight
Material	600D Ripstop Oxford Fabric (anti-slash)
Water Resistance	IPX4 Rated – water-repellent + sealed zippers
Compartments	3 main + 2 hidden pockets
Strap Length	Adjustable 80–130 cm (31″–51″) – fits all body sizes
Max Load	3kg (6.6 lbs)
Wear Styles	Chest / Crossbody / Shoulder / Waist – 4 ways
📦 WHAT FITS INSIDE
📱 Large smartphones (iPhone Pro Max / Samsung Ultra)
👛 Wallet, cards, and keys
🕶️ Sunglasses with case
📘 Passport and small notebook
🔋 Power bank + cables
🎒 4 COMFORTABLE WAYS TO WEAR
🛡️ Chest Carry – Maximum security in busy areas (zips against your body)
↔️ Crossbody Sling – Balanced comfort for daily use
💼 Shoulder Bag – Casual quick access
👖 Waist Pack – Ideal for cycling, hiking, and travel
⚡ WHY CHOOSE THIS SLING BAG?
Feature	This Bag	Standard Sling
Anti-Theft Protection	✅ Hidden zips &amp; locking system	❌ Basic zips only
Water Resistance	✅ IPX4 Rated	❌ Limited protection
Wear Options	✅ 4-Way carry	❌ 1–2 options
Comfort	✅ Slim &amp; lightweight (420g)	❌ Bulky design
📌 IMPORTANT NOTES
⚠ Not suitable for heavy rain submersion – IPX4 is splash/rain resistant, not fully waterproof for swimming
⚠ Maximum recommended load: 3kg to maintain comfort and strap integrity
⚠ Colour may vary slightly due to monitor differences
⚠ Manual measurement – allow 1-2cm tolerance on dimensions
🎯 STAY SECURE. STAY MOBILE.
Move confidently through the city, travel, or attend events with a secure, waterproof, and versatile anti-theft sling bag designed for modern UK life.

UK Travel Tip: Wear the bag across your chest in crowded areas for maximum security and easy access.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/d3gAAeSwy3JpfhBy/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rsQAAeSwVktpOBOZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kN4AAeSwKUlpOBOX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/esYAAeSw2VFpOBOY/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yiUAAeSwr-VpOBOb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BkYAAeSwXtlpOBOb/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Accessories Bags</category><ean>404834092055</ean><condition>New</condition><price>16.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092062</sku><product_name>Heatless Curling Rod Headband Soft Hair Curlers Rollers for Women No Heat Wave</product_name><description>HEATLESS CURLING HEADBAND – OVERNIGHT BEACH WAVES | ZERO HEAT DAMAGE 💫
Overnight Hair Styling | No Heat Damage | Soft Natural Curls

Wake up with soft, salon-style curls without heat or damage using this Heatless Curling Headband. Designed for overnight styling, it creates effortless beach waves and natural curls while you sleep – perfect for busy lifestyles.

No heat, no electricity, and no hair breakage. Just wrap, sleep, and reveal beautiful curls in the morning.

🔥 Tired of Heat Damage to Your Hair?
💔 Split ends and dryness from heated styling tools
⏰ Time-consuming morning routines
⚡ High electricity use from curlers and straighteners
😖 Uncomfortable traditional rollers
🌧️ Curls dropping quickly in humid conditions
✅ The Heatless Curling Solution
💖 Zero Heat Damage – Healthier looking hair
💤 Sleep &amp; Style – Wake up with ready curls
🌱 No Electricity Needed – Eco friendly styling
🧠 Memory Foam Comfort – Sleep comfortably
⏳ Long Lasting Results – Curls can last 1–3 days
💤 Sleep Friendly Comfort Design
🧠 Memory foam core moulds to your head shape
🧸 Soft velvet exterior – gentle on hair and skin
🧷 Anti-slip fabric keeps it secure overnight
⚖️ Lightweight design (approx. 180g)
🔄 Flexible fit for most hair types
🚫 Tension free styling – no pulling or breakage
Designed for comfortable overnight wear and suitable even for side sleepers.

🌊 Salon Style Results – No Heat Required
Loose beach waves
Soft natural curls
Bouncy volume
Blow-dry effect without heat damage
Suitable for straight, wavy, thick, thin, long and medium hair types.

✨ 3 Simple Steps to Perfect Curls
1️⃣ Dampen Hair – Lightly mist with water or conditioner
2️⃣ Wrap &amp; Secure – Wrap hair around the band (approx. 5 minutes)
3️⃣ Sleep &amp; Reveal – Wake up and enjoy effortless curls
👩 Perfect For Everyday Use
💼 Working professionals
🎓 Students
👶 Busy parents
✈️ Travellers
📊 Why Buyers Love It
Feature	Heatless Headband	Heat Tools
Hair Damage	✅ None	❌ Heat damage
Time Required	✅ 5 mins + sleep	❌ 30+ mins styling
Cost	✅ One time purchase	❌ Tools + electricity
Travel Safe	✅ Yes	❌ Voltage issues
📦 What’s Included
1 × Heatless Curling Rod Headband
2 × Hair Ties
⚠️ Note: Hair clip not included with B-Pink colour option.

🎨 Available Colours
Black
Light Pink
Dark Pink
Brown
B-Pink</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/F34AAeSw8SFphY9R/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Cs4AAeSw6ZFpQCVY/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-1cAAeSw8hBpQCVa/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lB8AAeSwHj1pQCVW/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eP8AAeSw1HhpQCVk/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1ngAAeSwZDdpQCVm/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Hair Care &amp; Styling Hair Styling Devices Rollers &amp; Curlers</category><ean>404834092062</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092079</sku><product_name>Microwave Splatter Cover,Food Cover,Anti-Splatter Lid with Steam Vents 10 Inch</product_name><description>Microwave Food Cover Anti-Splatter – Transparent Plate Lid for Home Kitchen (UK Stock)
Keep your microwave clean and your food evenly heated with this Microwave Food Cover Anti-Splatter Transparent Plate Lid. Designed for everyday kitchen use, this practical Food Cover Anti-Splatter prevents messy spills and splashes while allowing steam to circulate for better heating results. Its clear design lets you easily monitor your food while cooking, making it a convenient and essential accessory for any kitchen.


⭐ Key Features
Anti-Splatter Protection – Prevents sauces, oils, and food from splashing inside your microwave.
Transparent Plate Lid Design – Clear cover allows you to check your food without removing the lid.
Steam Ventilation – Built-in vents help release steam to prevent soggy food and ensure even heating.
Durable &amp; Food-Safe Material – Made from high-quality BPA-free plastic for safe daily use.
Easy Grip Handle – Convenient top handle makes lifting the cover quick and safe.
Universal Fit – Suitable for most standard plates and bowls used in microwaves.

📦 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Microwave Food Cover Anti-Splatter
Material: BPA-Free Plastic
Colour: Transparent / Clear
Design: Transparent Plate Lid with Steam Vents
Diameter: Approx. 26–27 cm (fits most dinner plates)
Height: Approx. 8–9 cm
Use: Microwave food heating and splatter protection

🍽️ Vast Applications of Usage
Reheating leftovers such as rice, pasta, curry, soup, and vegetables
Heating ready meals and frozen foods safely in the microwave
Covering plates and bowls to prevent food splashes during heating
Protecting microwave interiors from oil, sauce, and food splatter
Keeping food warm for a short time after cooking
Covering fresh food like fruits, snacks, or meals on the kitchen counter
Suitable for home kitchens, offices, dorm rooms, and shared kitchens
Helpful for families, students, and busy households needing quick and clean meal preparation

✅ Why Choose This Food Cover?
Helps keep your microwave clean and hygienic
Allows even heating while protecting food from drying out
Reusable, lightweight, and easy to wash
A simple kitchen tool that saves cleaning time and effort</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/41AAAeSwRyxpQWH9/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/amcAAeSwF0RpQWH0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZLMAAeSwA1BpQWIX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/UtUAAeSw9hlpQnf4/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TYEAAeSwnfdpQWGd/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XskAAeSw7~hpQWHq/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092079</ean><condition>New</condition><price>10.43</price><quantity>9</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092086</sku><product_name>3D Mask Eye Blackout Soft Padded Sleep Luxurious Blindfold Travel Eye Cover UK</product_name><description>🌙 ULTRA-SOFT 3D CONTOUR SLEEP MASK – 100% LIGHT BLOCKING EYE COVER 🌙
Pressure-Free Comfort | Deep Sleep Support | Home &amp; Travel Essential

Experience deeper, uninterrupted sleep anytime and anywhere with this Ultra-Soft 3D Contour Sleep Mask. Designed to block 100% of light, it creates a perfectly dark environment while delivering all-night comfort whether at home or travelling.

The advanced 3D ergonomic contour design provides generous space around the eyes, eliminating pressure on eyelids and eyelashes so you can blink naturally and sleep comfortably.

Sleep deeper. Wake refreshed. Anywhere.

✨ Why You'll Love This Sleep Mask
🌑 Creates complete darkness for deeper sleep
😌 Zero pressure on eyes and eyelashes
🌬️ Breathable fabric prevents heat build-up
🛏️ Comfortable for overnight wear
😴 Advanced 3D Comfort Design
👁️ 3D Ergonomic Contour – Natural eye space for pressure-free comfort
🪶 Ultra-Soft Padding – Gentle on skin and eyelashes
🌡️ Breathable Fabric – Helps regulate temperature
🚫 No Compression – Ideal for side sleepers
🌿 Skin Friendly &amp; Safe Materials
Hypoallergenic and fragrance free
Soft irritation free fabric
No harmful chemicals
Suitable for sensitive skin
🎯 Adjustable &amp; Secure Fit
🔄 Adjustable elastic head strap
🧷 Secure fit without slipping
💇 No hair pulling or tangling
👫 Unisex design for men and women
🌙 Perfect For
🛏️ Night time sleep at home
✈️ Travel, flights and hotels
🌤️ Daytime naps and shift workers
🧘 Meditation and relaxation
🌍 Jet lag recovery</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8iYAAeSw9Ttpe314/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9MgAAeSwcxppRpWR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-CAAAeSwPGtpRpWP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/q08AAeSwpklpRpWR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MvEAAeSwyqZpRpWP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MwQAAeSwyqZpRpWR/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Luggage &amp; Travel Accessories Travel Accessories Eye Masks</category><ean>404834092086</ean><condition>New</condition><price>2.66</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092109</sku><product_name>12" Phone Screen Magnifier 3D HD Video Amplifier – Foldable Stand New Model UK</product_name><description>Portable 12" Phone Cinema Screen – Curved HD Magnifier Travel Movie Viewer
✅ 12" Magnified Screen | ✅ Curved HD Viewing | ✅ Foldable &amp; Portable | ✅ No Power Required

🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Turn your smartphone into a personal cinema anywhere with this 12 Inch Curved Phone Screen Magnifier. Designed to enlarge your mobile display up to 3x, it offers a bigger and more comfortable viewing experience for films, videos, gaming, and streaming.

No power, batteries, apps, or setup required – simply place your phone behind the screen and enjoy. Perfect for travel, home use, students, commuting, and family entertainment.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 12 Inch Magnified Screen – Enlarges smartphone display up to 3x
✅ Curved Viewing Design – Wider and more immersive cinema-style experience
✅ Eye Comfort Viewing – Helps reduce strain from small screens
✅ Portable &amp; Foldable – Lightweight and easy to carry
✅ No Power Required – No charging, batteries, or cables needed
✅ Universal Compatibility – Works with most iPhone &amp; Android phones
✅ Quick Setup – Use in seconds anywhere
✅ Great for Travel &amp; Home – Ideal for holidays, commuting, students
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Phone Screen Magnifier
Screen Size	12 Inch
Design	Curved HD Magnifier
Material	ABS + Lens Panel
Power Required	No
Foldable	Yes
Compatible Devices	Smartphones
Colour	Black / As Available
🎯 PERFECT FOR
✔ Watching Netflix / YouTube
✔ Train &amp; bus journeys
✔ Hotels &amp; travel
✔ Family car trips
✔ Students &amp; shared rooms
✔ Hands-free video viewing
📱 COMPATIBLE WITH
✔ iPhone models
✔ Samsung Galaxy
✔ Huawei
✔ Xiaomi
✔ Oppo / Vivo
✔ Most smartphones
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × 12" Phone Cinema Screen Magnifier
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VjMAAeSw1kNpi0Vn/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6BQAAeSwZTppSqdS/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6lwAAeSwH8tpSqds/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zyYAAeSwATBpSqdZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/0K0AAeSwbktpSqdX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4-QAAeSwzKppSqdX/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Mobile Phones &amp; Communication Mobile Phone Accessories Mounts &amp; Holders</category><ean>404834092109</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.73</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092116</sku><product_name>Extra Strong Windproof Auto Umbrella 24 Rods Foldable Large UV Rain Protection</product_name><description>XL 24-Rib Automatic Windproof Umbrella – Beaufort 7 Storm Resistant | Waterproof | UPF 50+
24 Reinforced Ribs • Automatic Open/Close • Storm Resistant • Waterproof • UPF 50+ Protection • UK Ready

🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Stay protected in all weather with this extra-strong 24-rib automatic umbrella, specially designed to handle strong winds, heavy rain, and bright sunshine. Built with a reinforced frame and waterproof pongee fabric, this umbrella is perfect for commuting, travel, and everyday outdoor use.

Featuring a fully automatic open and close system and a large protective canopy, this umbrella offers reliable protection and everyday convenience.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 24 Reinforced Ribs – Extra strong frame for superior wind resistance
✅ Beaufort Level 7 Windproof – Designed to handle strong gusts
✅ Fully Automatic System – One-button open and close function
✅ Extra Large 106cm Canopy – Large enough for two people
✅ Waterproof Fabric – 190T pongee with water repellent coating
✅ UPF 50+ Protection – Helps block UV rays
✅ Compact Folding Design – Easy to store in bags and backpacks
✅ Quick Dry Material – Shake dry within seconds
📏 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Automatic Folding Umbrella
Canopy Size	106 cm
Ribs	24 Reinforced Ribs
Frame Material	Fiberglass + Steel
Fabric	190T Waterproof Pongee
UV Protection	UPF 50+
Mechanism	Automatic Open / Close
Folded Length	Approx. 33 cm
Weight	Approx. 650g
Colour	....
🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Daily commuting
✔ Travel and holidays
✔ Students
✔ Shopping trips
✔ Dog walking
✔ Outdoor activities
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × 24 Rib Automatic Umbrella
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy 2 Save More
💰 Bulk discounts available
Check quantity discounts above</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/McwAAeSwip5pkwcX/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BesAAeSwzqlpTS4L/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OdcAAeSwGWlpTS4K/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/UMUAAeSwNOppTS4L/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ne4AAeSwZPJpTS4L/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/N1IAAeSwN4RpTS4M/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Accessories Umbrellas</category><ean>404834092116</ean><condition>New</condition><price>23.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092123</sku><product_name>Retractable Phone Lanyard – Anti-Theft Mobile Safety Tether Strap Secure UK</product_name><description>🔒 Retractable Anti-Theft Phone Holder – Secure, Lightweight &amp; Reliable
Protect your phone wherever you go with this Retractable Anti-Theft Phone Holder, expertly designed to prevent accidental drops, loss, and theft during daily use or outdoor adventures.

The strong retractable safety cord allows you to use your phone comfortably while keeping it securely attached. If your phone slips from your hand, the anti-drop harness instantly catches it — making it ideal for hiking, cycling, climbing, travelling, or busy city life.

Equipped with a durable carabiner clip, it easily attaches to belts, backpacks, bags, or trousers. Its lightweight and compact design provides peace of mind without restricting movement or comfort.

Compatible with most smartphones, this phone safety lanyard is an essential accessory for active users who want reliable protection on the go.

⭐ Why Buyers Love It
✔ Prevents Phone Drops, Loss &amp; Theft
✔ Retractable Cord – Use your phone freely
✔ Strong Carabiner Clip for secure attachment
✔ Lightweight &amp; Compact design
✔ Ideal for Hiking, Cycling, Climbing &amp; Travel
✔ Universal Fit for most smartphones
✔ No Batteries Required
📌 Specifications
Product Name: Anti-Theft Phone Holder
Type: Smartphone Safety Lanyard
Feature: Retractable Anti-Drop Harness
Style: Classical
Use: Outdoor, Sports, Travel, Daily Use
⏳ Why Buy Now
✔ Fast Dispatch
✔ Popular &amp; Trusted Safety Accessory
✔ Perfect for Outdoor &amp; Active Lifestyles
Secure Your Phone. Move Freely. Stay Protected.

📦 Package Options
Options Available:

1PC – Single item only
1 Set – Complete set as shown in images
👉 Please choose the correct option before checkout to ensure you receive the item you need.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ktQAAeSwAbRpTpEz/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C5YAAeSwi79pTpE2/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lN0AAeSwNn1pTpE8/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/a2UAAeSw3B5pTpE1/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GlQAAeSw3QdpTpE1/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9QgAAeSwWslpTpE0/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Mobile Phones &amp; Communication Mobile Phone Accessories Straps &amp; Charms</category><ean>404834092123</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092130</sku><product_name>Double Layer Cat Litter Mat – Non-Slip Washable Paw Clean Pad for Litter Box</product_name><description>🐱 EXTRA LARGE CAT LITTER MAT – HEAVY DUTY &amp; WATERPROOF
Heavy Duty • Waterproof • Anti-Slip • UK Homes
Designed to trap scattered litter, protect floors, and keep UK homes clean, tidy &amp; stress-free.

🌟 Key Features – Built for UK Pet Owners
🔶 Double-Layer Honeycomb Design – Soft EVA foam top layer gentle on paws, bottom layer traps litter neatly
🔶 100% Waterproof &amp; Urine-Proof – Protects carpets &amp; hardwood, mould-resistant, easy wipe or wash clean
🔶 Anti-Slip Safety Base – Strong grip prevents slipping on all UK floors, pet-safe, non-toxic
🔶 Easy Maintenance – Machine washable, quick-drying, durable EVA foam built to last
📏 Extra Large Size – Perfect for UK Homes
✅ Fits all standard UK litter boxes
✅ Covers 3x more area than standard mats
✅ Ideal for large cat breeds &amp; multi-cat households
✅ Keeps floors clean &amp; guest-ready
📦 Package Includes
1 × Extra Large Cat Litter Mat
👉 Please choose the correct size/option before checkout to ensure the right fit.

✅ Compatible with All UK Litter Types
Clumping litter
Silica gel
Wood pellets
Paper-based litter
Clay litter
Corn &amp; wheat litter
🏆 Why UK Pet Owners Love This Mat
✅ Saves time &amp; cleaning effort
✅ Protects expensive UK flooring
✅ Reduces stress &amp; mess
✅ Gentle on sensitive paws
✅ Ideal for multi-pet households
✅ Works perfectly in UK weather</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AZYAAeSwLLdpUlGo/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9r8AAeSwAAVpUlGo/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AogAAeSwpvZpUlGo/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AogAAeSwpvZpUlGo/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LocAAeSwuIRpUlGo/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GLIAAeSwq2xpUlGo/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Pet Supplies Cat Supplies Litter Trays</category><ean>404834092130</ean><condition>New</condition><price>25.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092147</sku><product_name>Outdoor Cat Winter Shelter – Insulated Waterproof Foldable Warm Feral Stray Tent</product_name><description>WATERPROOF INSULATED PET HOUSE – UK WINTER WEATHER PROOF
Keep your pets warm, dry, and safe through British winter weather. Designed specifically for UK conditions, this insulated outdoor pet house provides reliable protection from rain, wind, and cold nights.

Ideal for gardens, patios, balconies, sheds, and outdoor spaces, it’s suitable for cats and small to medium dogs needing year-round shelter.

❄️ Worried About Your Pets in UK Winter?
Cold rain, damp ground, and freezing nights can be dangerous for pets. Our 3-Layer Thermal Pet House creates a cosy, protected sanctuary that keeps warmth in and bad weather out.

🛡️ 3-Layer Weather Protection System
Outer Layer: Waterproof Oxford cloth – rain rolls straight off
Middle Layer: Foil thermal insulation – retains body heat
Inner Layer: Soft plush lining – warm, comfortable &amp; gentle
Keeps the interior above freezing even in cold UK conditions.

🌧️ Engineered for UK Conditions
💧 UK Rain Proof – Waterproof Oxford fabric handles heavy rain
💨 Coastal Wind Ready – Ground stakes included for stability
❄️ Winter Frost Defence – Insulated thermal lining
🏡 Garden Ready – Neutral design blends into UK outdoor spaces
🧼 Hygiene &amp; Easy Maintenance
Removable &amp; machine washable cover
Keeps pet area clean and fresh
Ideal for muddy paws &amp; wet fur
Hygienic for long-term outdoor use
Foldable design – Stores completely flat in seconds for garage or shed storage.

📏 Choose the Perfect UK Size
Size        Dimensions        Weight Capacity        Suitable For        UK Pet Examples
Small        33 × 33 × 33 cm        Up to 5kg        Cats, kittens, toy dogs        British Shorthair, Chihuahua, Yorkshire Terrier
Medium        36 × 36 × 36 cm        Up to 8kg        Medium cats, small dogs        Maine Coon, Beagle
Large        42 × 42 × 42 cm        Up to 12kg        Large cats, medium dogs        Cocker Spaniel
Size Tip: Measure your pet from nose to tail base and add 10–15cm. Pets prefer snug spaces to retain warmth.

🐾 Perfect For
✔ Outdoor cats
✔ Small dogs &amp; puppies
✔ Garden &amp; patio use
✔ Cold, wet &amp; windy weather
✔ Night-time shelter &amp; daytime naps
📋 Product Specifications
Item Type: Outdoor Pet House / Bed
Material: Plush + Waterproof Oxford Cloth
Base: Elevated plastic base (prevents damp)
Insulation: Foil thermal layer
Washable: Yes (removable cover)
Foldable: Yes
Use: Outdoor &amp; indoor
🇬🇧 UK Pet Specialist Service
🚚 Fast UK Shipping
📦 Tracking Provided
🔁 30-Day Easy Returns
🐶 Pet-friendly customer support
🏠 Give Your Pet a Warm, Dry Sanctuary Today
A cosy, weatherproof home your pet will love — built for real UK winter conditions.

✅ Waterproof  |  ✅ Insulated  |  ✅ Washable  |  ✅ Foldable  |  ✅ UK Weather Ready

UK Pet Winter Tip: Place the house against a wall or sheltered area. Add your pet’s favourite blanket to transfer familiar scents and encourage immediate use.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-nwAAeSwxWlpW5DH/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6toAAeSw8EhpW5DH/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RPsAAeSwUc1pW5DH/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8goAAeSwpAxpW5DH/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-mgAAeSwCiJpW5DH/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AV4AAeSw7ydpW5EC/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Pet Supplies Dog Supplies Dog Kennels</category><ean>404834092147</ean><condition>New</condition><price>54.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092154</sku><product_name>Toilet Brush And Holder Set Standing WC Bathroom Cleaning Brush Cherry Shaped UK</product_name><description>HEAVY DUTY TOILET BRUSH SET
Thick Bristles • Non-Slip Handle • Hygienic Holder • UK Bathroom Essential
Built for powerful cleaning, long-lasting durability, and improved hygiene in everyday UK bathrooms.

🔥 Stronger Cleaning. Better Hygiene.
Say goodbye to weak, bendy toilet brushes that slip, splash, and trap germs. This heavy-duty set tackles stains and limescale while keeping your bathroom fresh, dry, and odour-free.

Clean deeper. Dry faster. Last longer.

😤 Common Problems (Solved)
❌ Bristles bending after a few uses
❌ Slippery handles when wet
❌ Can’t reach under the rim
❌ Dirty water collecting in holders
❌ Lingering bad smells
✅ One strong, hygienic solution
🪥 Powerful High-Density Bristles
✔ Approx. 40% thicker than standard brushes
✔ Durable nylon removes stains &amp; limescale
✔ Curved head follows bowl shape
✔ Tapered tip reaches under rim &amp; corners
✔ Tough on grime, gentle on surfaces
🤲 Ergonomic Non-Slip Handle
Textured anti-slip grip — secure even when wet
38cm length keeps hands away from splashes
Comfortable grip size for all users
Integrated hanging hook for alternative storage
🏠 Hygienic Ventilated Holder
Airflow vents for faster drying
Drip-catching base prevents mess
Wide base for stability — no tipping
Smooth ABS plastic wipes clean in seconds
📐 Product Specifications
Feature        Specification
Total Length        38cm (15 inches)
Brush Head        13cm (W) × 8cm (H)
Material        ABS Plastic + Nylon Bristles
Weight        Approx. 200g
Holder        Ventilated with drip base
Storage        Floor-standing + Hanging Option
Colours        Wine Red / Red / Orange
🏆 Why UK Customers Choose This Brush
✅ Thick, durable bristles that don’t bend
✅ Secure non-slip grip
✅ Ventilated hygienic holder
✅ Built-in hook for flexible storage
✅ Strong ABS construction
❌ No flimsy plastics
❌ No dirty water build-up
❌ No unpleasant smells
🏠 Perfect For
🏡 Family Homes • 🏢 Rental Properties • 🏨 Airbnb &amp; Holiday Lets • 🏛️ Offices &amp; Businesses

📦 What’s Included
1 × Heavy Duty Toilet Brush
1 × Matching Ventilated Holder
Protective OPP Packaging</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/A6YAAeSw9zdpgZzP/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uZcAAeSwhYZpX4za/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Y4gAAeSwQfppX4zZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4hAAAeSweN9pX4zZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DQkAAeSwb39pX40D/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BckAAeSw9uhpX4z8/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Bathroom Accessories Toilet Brushes &amp; Holders</category><ean>404834092154</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092178</sku><product_name>DAB Radio FM Radio Antenna Aerial HIFI System Indoor 3M for Tuner Stereo Home UK</product_name><description>DAB &amp; FM Radio Antenna – Telescopic Indoor Aerial with 5dBi Signal Booster
Upgrade weak radio reception instantly with this Digital DAB &amp; FM Indoor Radio Antenna, designed to deliver clear, stable sound across UK homes.

Featuring a powerful 5dBi high-gain signal boost, an adjustable telescopic aerial, and a generous 3-metre cable, this antenna lets you position for the strongest possible signal — perfect for flats, houses, kitchens, bedrooms, and offices where built-in radio aerials struggle.

😤 Tired of Poor UK Radio Reception?
❌ Crackling sound and constant dropouts
❌ Missing BBC and digital-only stations
❌ Weak signal in bedrooms or kitchens
❌ Built-in radio aerial not powerful enough
❌ Endless retuning frustration
This antenna fixes it instantly.

✅ Why This DAB Antenna Works
✔ 5dBi signal gain boosts weak reception
✔ Telescopic aerial allows precise tuning
✔ 3-metre cable for ideal placement near windows
✔ 3 universal adapters fit almost all UK radios
✔ Compatible with DAB &amp; FM
✔ Plug &amp; play – no tools or setup required
✔ Portable for use in multiple rooms
📡 Enjoy Clear UK Radio Stations
📻 BBC Radio

BBC Radio 1, 2, 3 &amp; 4
BBC Radio 5 Live
BBC Local Radio Stations
🎵 Music Stations

Classic FM
Absolute Radio
Heart
Capital
Smooth
🗣️ Talk &amp; News

LBC
TalkRadio
Times Radio
🔧 30-Second UK Installation
Choose Adapter: Select the correct adapter (3 included) and attach it
Connect: Plug into your radio’s antenna socket (ANT / Aerial)
Adjust &amp; Tune: Extend antenna fully, place near a window, and retune
✔ That’s it — enjoy crystal-clear sound.

📍 Best Placement Tips (UK Homes)
✅ Best Locations

Near windows
Higher positions (shelves, cabinets)
Away from metal surfaces
🚫 Avoid

Behind TVs or monitors
Near routers or microwaves
Inside cupboards or metal cabinets
💡 Tip: Extend fully for DAB/FM, then fine-adjust during station scan.

🧱 Built for UK Homes
Flats with thick walls
Homes with poor roof aerial placement
Kitchens and bedrooms
Loft conversions and extensions
⚙️ Technical Specifications
Feature	Details
Frequency Range	88–108MHz (FM), 170–240MHz (DAB)
Signal Gain	5dBi
Impedance	75Ω
Polarisation	Vertical
Antenna Length	11.7cm collapsed / 40cm extended
Cable Type	RG174 Low-Loss Coaxial
Cable Length	3 Metres
Connectors	F-Type, Belling-Lee, Coaxial
Indoor Use	Yes
Returns	Yes
📦 What’s Included
📡 1 × Telescopic DAB+ / FM Radio Antenna
🔌 3 × Universal Adapters (UK radios)
📏 3m RG174 Coaxial Cable
📖 English UK Setup &amp; Tuning Guide</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MHsAAeSwjbBpbydv/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Q2MAAeSw0lNpbydv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T9cAAeSwgbdpbydv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FLYAAeSw6hJpbydv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/N7EAAeSwgadpbydv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ua0AAeSwZxNpbydv/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Sound &amp; Vision TV Reception &amp; Set-Top Boxes Signal Amplifiers &amp; Filters</category><ean>404834092178</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.39</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092185</sku><product_name>Backpack Rucksack Bag 18L Light Weight Foldable School Office Travel Camping 85G</product_name><description>Ultralight Foldable Backpack – 18L Pocket Size Travel Daypack (80g)
Meet the Ultralight Foldable Backpack – the smart UK travel essential that expands from pocket-size to a full 18L daypack in seconds. Perfect for budget airline travel, shopping, beach days, festivals, commuting, and everyday emergencies.

Weighing just 80g (lighter than an iPhone), this backpack adds virtually no weight to your luggage and folds small enough to fit in your pocket, glovebox, or office drawer until you need it.

😤 Tired of Bulky Daypacks on UK Travels?
❌ Ryanair &amp; EasyJet strict personal item limits
❌ Sudden shopping with no spare bag
❌ Beach days with wet clothes and towels
❌ UK festivals with bag checks
❌ Carrying empty backpacks all day
This foldable backpack solves it all.

🎩 The Magic Backpack That Fits in Your Pocket
Pocket Size	Full Backpack	Weight
10 × 8 × 4 cm
Smaller than a phone	38 × 26 × 12 cm
18L capacity (2 days of clothes)	80g only
Lighter than an iPhone
✔ Expands instantly                                 ✔ Adds no travel weight                                                               ✔ Packs down anywhere

💧 Built for UK Weather
✔ Water-resistant ripstop nylon
✔ Handles UK drizzle &amp; light showers
✔ Quick-drying fabric
🔧 Features
✔ 18L Capacity – ideal for day trips &amp; shopping
✔ Ultra-Lightweight – only 80g
✔ Self-Storing Design – folds into its own pouch
✔ YKK Zip – smooth &amp; reliable
✔ Breathable Mesh Straps – adjustable &amp; comfortable
✔ Smart Storage – 1 main compartment + side mesh bottle pocket
📏 Weight
Recommended Load: Up to 5kg
🎯 Perfect for UK Lifestyle
✈️ Budget Airline Travel
Ryanair / EasyJet personal item compliant
Carry extra shopping on return flights
🏖️ Beach Days
Towels, sunscreen &amp; swimwear
Separate wet clothes after swimming
🛍️ Urban Shopping
Emergency shopping bag
Folds away instantly after use
🚗 Emergency Backup
Ideal for glovebox or office drawer
Carry supplies, clothes, or first aid
🎪 Festivals &amp; Events
Lightweight and security-friendly
Easy to inspect and carry all day
🧳 What Fits in 18L? (UK Examples)
Beach Day: 2 towels, sunscreen, hat, water bottle, book
Shopping Trip: 3–4 clothing items, umbrella, snacks
Gym Session: Trainers, towel, toiletries, clothes
Day Hike: Lunch, water, waterproof jacket, first aid kit
🔄 10-Second Folding System
Empty and flatten the bag
Roll tightly from bottom up
Tuck into the built-in pouch
Ready for next use in seconds.

🎨 Available Colours
Lake Blue-Blue
Black
Grey</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dm4AAeSwaNVpfgJs/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JCEAAeSwPMdpcJg6/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y-IAAeSw19VpcJg5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/0EwAAeSwKpRpcJg5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/twoAAeSw3tdpcJg7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vNgAAeSwpr1pcJg6/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Camping &amp; Hiking Hiking Rucksacks &amp; Bags Rucksacks</category><ean>404834092185</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092208</sku><product_name>4x Pillow Protectors Washable Anti allergic Zipped Entry 75x50 cm 100% Cotton UK</product_name><description>Hypoallergenic Pillow Protectors – 4 Pack Zippered Quilted Dust Mite Proof Covers
✅ 4 Pack Value Set | ✅ Full Zipper Protection | ✅ Dust Mite Barrier | ✅ Soft Quilted Comfort

🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Protect your pillows and enjoy a cleaner, fresher night’s sleep with this 4 Pack Hypoallergenic Pillow Protector Set. Designed with a full zippered enclosure, these protectors help guard against dust mites, allergens, stains, sweat, and everyday wear while adding soft quilted comfort.

Ideal for UK homes, allergy sufferers, families, hotels, and Airbnb hosts. A practical solution for extending pillow life while improving everyday hygiene.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 4 Pack Value Set – Great for multiple beds or spare pillows
✅ Dust Mite &amp; Allergen Barrier – Helps reduce common pillow allergens
✅ Full Zipper Closure – 360° enclosed pillow protection
✅ Soft Quilted Comfort – Diamond stitched padded surface
✅ Breathable &amp; Silent Fabric – No noisy plastic feel
✅ Helps Prevent Stains – Protects from sweat and marks
✅ Machine Washable – Easy care and reusable
✅ Suitable All Year Round – Comfortable in all seasons
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Pillow Protectors
Quantity	4 Pieces
Size	UK Standard 50 × 75 cm
Colour	White
Material	Soft Microfibre
Filling	Hollow Fibre
Design	Quilted Diamond Stitch
Closure Type	Zippered Enclosure
Hypoallergenic	Yes
Machine Washable	Yes
🛏️ SUITABLE FOR
✔ Feather pillows
✔ Memory foam pillows
✔ Bamboo pillows
✔ Hollow fibre pillows
✔ Guest bedrooms
✔ Hotels / Airbnb
🧺 CARE INSTRUCTIONS
✔ Machine wash at 40–60°C
✔ Tumble dry low
✔ Do not bleach
✔ Do not iron
✔ Wash regularly for best hygiene results
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 4 × Pillow Protectors
✔ Care Instructions
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yTEAAeSwg0Zpeeuh/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yTEAAeSwg0Zpeeuh/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KUEAAeSwb9Fpeeuh/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TLkAAeSw6CRpeeuh/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wGcAAeSwF6Jpeeuh/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xwQAAeSwauBpeeuh/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bedding Mattress &amp; Pillow Protectors</category><ean>404834092208</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.59</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092215</sku><product_name>Mens Genuine Leather Belt – Real Leather New Buckle for Trouser Jeans Black Brow</product_name><description>👔 Men's Genuine Leather Dress Belt – 1.44" (36mm) Wide Classic Black Belt with Single Prong Buckle – Formal &amp; Casual Wear
Genuine Leather • Single Prong Buckle • Gift Box Included • 30-Day Refund • UK Ready

🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Elevate your wardrobe with this Men's Genuine Leather Dress Belt, designed for both formal and casual occasions. Made from durable, genuine leather and featuring a classic single prong buckle, this 1.44-inch (36mm) wide black belt complements any outfit – from suits to jeans. A timeless accessory that combines style, comfort, and durability for the modern man.

Perfect for office wear, formal events, or everyday use. The belt arrives in elegant gift packaging – ideal for birthdays, anniversaries, or any special occasion.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Genuine Leather Material – Durable, smooth, and long-lasting
🔹 Classic Single Prong Buckle – Polished zinc alloy – sleek and strong
🔹 1.44" (36mm) Width – Perfect balance for dress pants, jeans, and suits
🔹 Multiple Sizing Holes – Adjustable comfort for the perfect fit
🔹 Versatile Occasion Wear – Office, formal events, weddings, business meetings, or casual daily use
🔹 Elegant Gift Packaging – Comes in a gift box – ready to present
🔹 30-Day Refund/Replacement – Risk-free purchase with our satisfaction guarantee
🔹 Colour Options – Choose from Classic Black or Rich Brown (select your variant)
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Men's Dress Belt / Leather Belt
Material	Genuine Leather (smooth, durable)
Width	1.44 inches (36mm) – approximately 1.5."
Thickness	4mm (approx.) – sturdy everyday wear
Buckle Material	Polished Zinc Alloy – single prong
Colour Options	Classic Black / Rich Brown (select at checkout)
Fit	Multiple adjustment holes for comfort
Occasion	Formal, business, casual, office, wedding, everyday
Packaging	Elegant gift box (included)
Warranty/Returns	30-day refund or replacement
📏 SIZE GUIDE – CHOOSE YOUR WAIST SIZE
For best fit, order a belt size 2 inches (5cm) larger than your pant waist size.

Pant Waist Size (inches)	Recommended Belt Size (inches)
28-30	32
30-32	34
32-34	36
34-36	38
36-38	40
38-40	42
40-42	44
📌 IMPORTANT NOTES
⚠ Genuine leather may have natural grain variations – this is a sign of quality, not a defect
⚠ Colour may vary slightly due to monitor display differences – Classic Black is true black, Rich Brown is a warm brown
⚠ Avoid prolonged exposure to water or moisture to maintain leather quality
⚠ For best longevity, condition leather periodically with a suitable leather balm
🎁 PERFECT GIFT IDEA
This belt arrives in an elegant gift box, making it an ideal present for:

🎂 Birthdays
💍 Anniversaries
👔 Father's Day
🎄 Christmas
🎓 Graduations
💼 Promotions or new job gifts
🛡️ ORDER WITH CONFIDENCE
We are committed to your satisfaction with our men's belts. If you are unhappy with our product or service, please feel free to contact us. We offer a 30-day refund or replacement service to ensure a risk-free purchase.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V6sAAeSwPMFpgyv4/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/UiUAAeSwGH1pgyv3/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ApYAAeSw00hpgyv4/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BYgAAeSwIkZpgyv4/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ts8AAeSwjj5pgywM/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vM0AAeSwmhlpgywC/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Accessories Belts</category><ean>404834092215</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.99</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092222</sku><product_name>Inflatable Neck Pillow Travel Flight Rest Sleep Support Blow-Up Cushion Camping</product_name><description>FLOCKING INFLATABLE PORTABLE NECK PILLOW ✈️
Self-Filling • 5s Quick Release • Anti-Leak Valve • Adjustable Double Buckle • Ultra-Lightweight

Perfect for business trips, camping, flights, and commuting — this compact inflatable U-shape pillow delivers ergonomic neck support without the bulk of traditional foam pillows.

🌟 Built for Smart UK Travel
🪶   Soft flocking fabric – suede-like comfort
💨 5-second rapid air release
🔒 Anti-leak composite rubber valve
🔄 Adjustable double buckle for custom fit
🪶 Premium Flocking Fabric
✔ Soft, skin-friendly suede-like finish
✔ Breathable &amp; comfortable for long wear
✔ Gentle against neck and jawline
✔ Ideal for long-haul flights
Comfort without irritation — even on extended journeys.
💨 5-Second Quick Deflate System
Concealed air outlet valve allows rapid deflation and pack-down in seconds.

✔ Deflates in approx. 5 seconds
✔ No bulky protruding parts
✔ Perfect for busy travellers
✔ Easy storage immediately after landing
🔒 Advanced Anti-Leak Technology
Designed with composite pressed rubber sealing and reinforced joints for superior air retention.

✔ Built-in one-way air lock valve
✔ Strong seam bonding technology
✔ No mid-flight sagging
✔ Stays firm for 8+ hours
Reliable support from take-off to landing.
🔄 Adjustable Double Buckle – Custom Fit
✔ Free neck size adjustment
✔ Prevents slipping during sleep
✔ Keeps pillow securely positioned
✔ Suitable for all adults
✔ Quick-release removal
No more loose or shifting pillows while travelling.
⚖️ Why Choose Inflatable Over Foam?
Feature	This Inflatable Pillow	Standard Foam Pillow
Packed Size	Folds palm-sized	Bulky
Adjustable Firmness	Yes – control air level	Fixed firmness
Weight	Approx. 100g	300g+ heavier
Anti-Leak Valve	✅ Composite Seal	❌ Not applicable
Cleaning	Wipe clean	Machine wash required
Smart, lightweight travel support.
📋 Complete Specifications
Specification	Detail
Product Type	Portable Inflatable U-Shape Neck Pillow
Material	Flocking Fabric (Soft Suede Finish)
Inflation	Manual / Mouth Inflation – No Pump Required
Air Release	5-Second Rapid Deflation Valve
Sealing System	Composite Pressed Rubber + Reinforced Joints
Closure	Adjustable Double Buckle
Weight	Approx. 100g (Ultra-Lightweight)
Storage	Folds into Included Compact Pouch
Care	Wipe Clean Only
🌍 Perfect For Every Journey
✈️ Flights – Long-haul comfort
🚆 Trains &amp; Commutes – Travel naps
⛺ Camping – Lightweight &amp; compact
💼 Business Trips – Arrive refreshed
📦 What’s Included
🪶 1 × Inflatable U-Shape Neck Pillow
📘 Inflation Instructions
💤 Travel Smarter. Sleep Better.
Ultra-lightweight. Anti-leak secure. Adjustable comfort.
Designed for modern UK travellers.

✅ Self-Inflating Design   |   ✅ 5s Rapid Deflate   |   ✅ Anti-Leak Valve   |   ✅ Adjustable Fit   |   ✅ Compact Storage</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kJ0AAeSwNVVpoCT0/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lo4AAeSwYN5poCT0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jRIAAeSw9rVpoCT0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/p0oAAeSwKoFpoCT1/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rYkAAeSwk0ppoCT0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tZUAAeSwrclpoCT1/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Luggage &amp; Travel Accessories Travel Accessories Travel Pillows</category><ean>404834092222</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092239</sku><product_name>EMERGENCY CAR HAMMER WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER ESCAPE TOOL BREAK UK</product_name><description>EMERGENCY HAMMER Car Window Breaker &amp; Seatbelt Cutter – Essential Vehicle Escape Safety Tool (UK Stock)

Be fully prepared for unexpected emergencies with this high‑quality EMERGENCY HAMMER featuring a WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER. Designed for rapid response, this compact yet durable tool can make a critical difference when seconds matter.


⭐ Key Features
✔ 2-in-1 Emergency Design – Heavy-duty window breaker &amp; seatbelt cutter in one compact tool
✔ Hardened Steel Hammer Head – Instantly shatters side windows in emergency situations
✔ Sharp Concealed Blade – Quickly cuts jammed or locked seatbelts
✔ Non-Slip Anti-Skid Handle – Firm grip for safe and controlled use
✔ High-Visibility Red Body – Easy to locate in stressful situations
✔ Protective Mounting Bracket – Secure and convenient storage within reach
✔ Compact &amp; Lightweight – Fits glove box, door pocket, or centre console

🔧 Technical Specifications
Material: High-carbon hardened steel hammer head
Handle: Durable ABS with anti-slip grip
Blade: Stainless steel concealed safety blade
Length: Approx. 17cm
Weight: Approx. 130–150g
Colour: Red
Condition: Brand New
Stock Location: UK

🌍 Vast Application of Usage
This EMERGENCY HAMMER is suitable for a wide range of vehicles and emergency situations:

🚗 Private cars &amp; family vehicles
🚕 Taxis, Uber &amp; ride-share vehicles
🚚 Vans, trucks &amp; delivery fleets
🚌 Buses &amp; minibuses
🚐 Motorhomes &amp; caravans
🚓 Emergency &amp; service vehicles
🚤 Boats &amp; marine vehicles
🏢 Workplace fleet vehicles
🎒 Travel safety kits &amp; roadside emergency kits
Perfect for emergencies involving:

Vehicle submersion in water
Electrical or central locking failure
Car fires
Severe collisions
Jammed doors after impact

🛡 Key Benefits
✔ Enables fast escape when doors cannot be opened
✔ Cuts seatbelts instantly to prevent entrapment
✔ Provides peace of mind for drivers and passengers
✔ A small investment for potentially life-saving protection

📦 Package Includes
1 × EMERGENCY HAMMER
1 × Mounting Bracket</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3U4AAeSwGU9poo55/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kHIAAeSwqHhpoWq5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sE4AAeSwfzBpoWq3/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ieMAAeSwREFpoWq5/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sToAAeSwtF1poWq3/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rJ4AAeSweYFpoWq5/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Safety &amp; Security Accessories Safety Emergency Tools &amp; Tool Kits</category><ean>404834092239</ean><condition>New</condition><price>6.3</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092253</sku><product_name>Headlight Restoration Car Polish Headlamp Scratch Remover &amp; Oxidation Cleaner UK</product_name><description>Car Headlight Restoration Kit Polish Scratch Remover Oxidation Cleaner – UK Stock
Restore clarity, brightness, and safety to your vehicle’s headlights with this professional-grade Headlight Restoration Kit. Designed to effectively remove oxidation, yellowing, haze, and light scratches, this powerful Scratch Remover Oxidation Cleaner helps improve night-time visibility and enhances your car’s appearance — without costly replacements.


⭐ Key Features
Complete Headlight Restoration Kit – Everything needed to restore dull, cloudy, and oxidised headlights
Powerful Scratch Remover Oxidation Formula – Eliminates yellowing, haze, light scratches &amp; UV damage
Improves Night Visibility – Restores brightness for safer driving
Easy DIY Application – No professional tools required
Long-Lasting Protection – Helps prevent future oxidation and fading

🔧 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Headlight Restoration Kit
Function: Polish, Scratch Remover Oxidation Cleaner
Suitable For: Plastic headlight lenses
Application: Manual (Hand Polish)
Compatibility: Universal – Cars, Vans, SUVs, Motorbikes
Condition: Brand New
Stock: UK

🎯 Ideal For
Foggy, yellowed, or oxidised headlights
Vehicles preparing for MOT tests
Older cars with faded lenses
Removing light scratches and surface haze
DIY car maintenance at home
Improving night-time driving safety

🔄 Vast Applications of Usage
✔ Headlights – Restores clarity and brightness
✔ Tail lights &amp; indicator lenses – Removes dullness and oxidation
✔ Fog lights – Improves light output and visibility
✔ Plastic trim &amp; clear plastic covers – Revives faded surfaces
✔ Motorbike light covers – Restores shine and transparency
✔ Caravan &amp; trailer light lenses – Enhances road safety

🌟 Why Customers Recommend It
✔ Noticeable Results – Visibly clearer, brighter lights
✔ Easy to Use – Straightforward application with quick results
✔ Cost-Effective Solution – Saves money compared to replacements
✔ Durable Finish – Helps maintain clarity for longer
✔ Professional Results at Home – Workshop-quality restoration without the cost

🚚 Shipping &amp; Returns
Free UK Shipping – Fast &amp; reliable dispatch
30 Days Return Policy – Buy with confidence and peace of mind

✅ Key Benefits
Save money compared to replacing headlights
Enhance vehicle appearance instantly
Improve MOT readiness
Increase road safety with clearer headlights
Quick and effective results at home
Order today and restore your headlights to like-new clarity!</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AXQAAeSwkXJpqSnw/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jwwAAeSwYxRppTrR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bRYAAeSwB7ZppTrQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/UicAAeSwwhpppTrR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YdQAAeSwjdJppTrQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i0cAAeSwoipppTrR/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Car Care, Utility &amp; Trailers Car Care &amp; Cleaning Other Car Care &amp; Cleaning</category><ean>404834092253</ean><condition>New</condition><price>6.37</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092260</sku><product_name>8 Colour Magnetic White Board Marker Pens Pen Dry Eraser Easy Wipe Whiteboard UK</product_name><description>8 Colour Magnetic White Board Marker Pens – Dry Eraser Easy Wipe Whiteboard Markers (UK Stock)
Keep your presentations, notes, and teaching sessions clear and colourful with this 8 Colour Magnetic White Board Marker Set. Designed for convenience and performance, each Magnetic White Board Marker features a built-in eraser and magnetic cap, making it easy to store directly on your whiteboard and always within reach. The Dry Eraser Easy Wipe ink ensures smooth writing and effortless cleaning without leaving stains or ghost marks.


⭐ Key Features
✔ 8 Vibrant Colours Included – Perfect for colour-coding notes, planning, teaching, and presentations
✔ Magnetic Caps – Easily attach the marker to any magnetic whiteboard for quick access
✔ Built-In Dry Eraser – Each pen includes a convenient eraser on the cap for instant corrections
✔ Dry Eraser Easy Wipe Ink – Smooth writing with ink that wipes cleanly without residue
✔ Fine Bullet Tip – Clear and precise lines ideal for writing, drawing, and diagrams
✔ Low Odour Ink – Comfortable for classrooms, offices, and home environments

📋 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Magnetic White Board Marker Set
Quantity: 8 Markers
Colours: 8 Assorted Colours
Tip Type: Fine Bullet Tip
Eraser: Built-in Cap Eraser
Cap Feature: Magnetic for Easy Whiteboard Storage
Ink Type: Dry Eraser Easy Wipe Ink (Low Odour)
Compatibility: Suitable for Whiteboards, Glass Boards &amp; Dry Erase Surfaces

🎯 Ideal For
✔ Teachers &amp; Students – Classroom teaching, homework explanations, and learning activities
✔ Office Professionals – Meetings, presentations, brainstorming sessions, and planning
✔ Home Organisation – Weekly planners, reminders, chore charts, and to-do lists
✔ Training &amp; Coaching – Workshops, seminars, and strategy boards
✔ Children's Learning – Drawing, practicing writing, and creative activities
✔ Business Planning Boards – Task management, scheduling, and productivity planning

🌍 Vast Applications &amp; Usage
✔ Classrooms &amp; Schools – Teaching lessons, diagrams, and visual learning
✔ Offices &amp; Meeting Rooms – Brainstorming, presentations, and project planning
✔ Home &amp; Study Rooms – Study notes, reminders, and family planners
✔ Training Sessions &amp; Workshops – Professional demonstrations and teaching
✔ Kids Learning &amp; Creativity – Drawing, practicing writing, and activities
✔ Planning &amp; Organisation – Calendars, schedules, and task boards
✔ Coaching &amp; Sports Boards – Drawing tactics and game strategies

✨ Convenient &amp; Easy to Use
✔ Magnetic design keeps markers organised directly on your whiteboard
✔ Built-in mini eraser allows quick corrections anytime
✔ Comfortable lightweight grip for long writing sessions
✔ Quick-dry ink prevents smudging and keeps writing clear
✔ Easy wipe formula cleans the board instantly without marks

💡 Benefits
✔ Keeps markers organised and within easy reach
✔ Makes presentations, teaching, and planning visually engaging
✔ Integrated eraser allows quick corrections
✔ Easy wipe ink saves time when cleaning the board
✔ Suitable for professional, educational, and home use

📦 Package Includes
8 × Magnetic White Board Marker Pens (Assorted Colours)</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i7EAAeSwxbxpqqYe/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WToAAeSwePBpqqYe/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tO8AAeSw8AZpqqYe/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kbEAAeSwle9pqqYe/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/S4cAAeSwMzhpqqYd/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ff4AAeSwQvppqqYe/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Business, Office &amp; Industrial Office Equipment &amp; Supplies Office Supplies &amp; Stationery Pens &amp; Writing Instruments</category><ean>404834092260</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092277</sku><product_name>Freeview Indoor TV Aerial 250 Mile Digital HDTV 0.5mm Ultra Thin Signal Booster</product_name><description>Freeview Indoor TV Aerial – 250 Mile Digital HDTV Ultra Thin Antenna with Signal Booster (UK Stock)
Upgrade your home entertainment with this powerful Freeview Indoor TV Aerial, designed to deliver crystal-clear reception for your favourite channels. With an advanced 250 Mile Digital HDTV range and built-in Signal Booster, this ultra-thin antenna ensures stable and high-quality viewing without expensive cable or satellite subscriptions.

Perfect for modern homes, the sleek 0.5mm ultra-thin design allows easy placement on walls, windows, or behind TVs while maintaining strong signal performance.


⭐ Key Features
250 Mile Digital HDTV Reception – Extended range antenna captures more Freeview channels with improved signal stability
Built-in Signal Booster – Amplifies weak signals for clearer picture quality and fewer interruptions
0.5mm Ultra-Thin Design – Discreet and lightweight antenna that blends easily with any home setup
Full HD &amp; 4K Support – Enjoy crisp visuals and high-definition broadcast quality
Easy Plug &amp; Play Installation – Simply connect to your TV and scan for channels in minutes
Flexible Placement Options – Mount on walls, windows, behind the TV, or place on a table for optimal reception
Long Cable for Convenient Setup – Easily position the aerial where signal strength is strongest

📊 Technical Specifications
Reception Range: Up to 250 Miles
Technology: 250 Mile Digital HDTV Indoor Antenna
Amplifier: Built-in Signal Booster
Thickness: 0.5mm Ultra Thin Design
Compatibility: HDTV, 4K TV, Smart TV, DVB-T / Freeview Compatible TVs
Installation: Indoor – Wall, Window, or Desktop Placement
Cable Length: Approx. 3–5m (depending on batch)
Colour: Black

🎯 Benefits
Access free over-the-air HD channels without monthly fees
Enjoy stable reception and improved picture clarity
Compact design that doesn’t clutter your living space
Ideal solution for secondary TVs or portable setups

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Living Rooms &amp; Bedrooms – Perfect for main or secondary televisions
Apartments &amp; Rental Homes – Ideal where satellite dishes or outdoor antennas are not allowed
Caravans &amp; Motorhomes – Great for watching TV while travelling or camping
Student Accommodation – A simple and affordable way to access free channels
Offices &amp; Workspaces – Keep up with news, sports, and live broadcasts
Holiday Homes &amp; Cabins – Reliable TV reception without installing permanent systems
Portable TV Setups – Lightweight design makes it easy to move and install anywhere

🏠 What It Is Ideal For
Watching Freeview HD channels without expensive subscriptions
Improving TV signal reception in indoor environments
Homes where outdoor aerial installation is not possible
Small spaces such as flats, dorm rooms, or studios
Users who want a simple plug-and-play TV antenna solution
Travellers needing a portable TV signal solution</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qNgAAeSw705pq~Jg/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qNgAAeSw705pq~Jg/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Sound &amp; Vision TV Reception &amp; Set-Top Boxes Aerials</category><ean>404834092277</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.95</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092284</sku><product_name>4 Pcs Wall Mounted Electric Toothbrush Holder Traceless Bathroom Organizer Stand</product_name><description>4 Pcs Wall Mounted Electric Toothbrush Holder – Traceless Bathroom Organizer Stand (UK Stock)
Keep your bathroom neat, hygienic, and well-organised with this 4 Pcs Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holder Set. Designed for convenience and modern living, this Bathroom Organizer Stand securely holds electric or manual toothbrushes while saving valuable counter space. The traceless adhesive installation means no drilling, no wall damage, and easy setup in seconds.


⭐ Key Features
Wall Mounted Space-Saving Design – Keeps toothbrushes stored off the countertop, maintaining a clean and clutter-free bathroom.
Strong Traceless Adhesive – Easy installation without drilling. The strong adhesive sticks firmly to smooth surfaces and removes without leaving marks.
Suitable for Electric &amp; Manual Toothbrushes – Designed to securely hold most electric toothbrush handles and standard toothbrushes.
Hygienic Ventilated Design – Open structure allows quick drying and better airflow, helping keep toothbrushes clean and sanitary.
Durable &amp; Waterproof Material – Made from high-quality ABS plastic that is moisture-resistant and ideal for humid bathroom environments.
4 Piece Value Pack – Perfect for families so each member can have their own toothbrush holder.

📊 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holder
Quantity: 4 Pieces
Material: Durable ABS Plastic
Installation: Traceless Adhesive (No drilling required)
Mounting Type: Wall Mounted
Colour: Neutral / Modern Bathroom Style
Suitable For: Electric &amp; Manual Toothbrushes
Waterproof: Yes

✔ Benefits
Keeps bathroom counters tidy and organised
Quick and damage-free installation
Hygienic storage with improved airflow
Ideal for small bathrooms and shared households
Durable design built for everyday use

🏠 Ideal For
Home bathrooms
Family households
Student accommodation
Hotels &amp; guest bathrooms
Apartments and small spaces
Organising electric and manual toothbrushes neatly

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Holding electric and manual toothbrushes
Storing toothpaste tubes and dental accessories
Organising razors, facial brushes, and grooming tools
Keeping bathroom essentials tidy in family bathrooms
Ideal for homes, hotels, hostels, dormitories, and guest houses
Suitable for bathrooms, washrooms, shower areas, and vanity spaces
Perfect for travel accommodations, rental properties, and shared living spaces
Can be installed on tiles, glass, mirrors, metal surfaces, and smooth cabinets

📦 What’s Included
4 × Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holders</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Zq8AAeSwHq9prpoX/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Zq8AAeSwHq9prpoX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xSgAAeSwAHNprpwj/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tZ8AAeSwQmpprpwq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OcsAAeSwUztprpwz/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Bathroom Accessories Tumblers &amp; Toothbrush Holder</category><ean>404834092284</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092291</sku><product_name>360 Magnetic Car Phone Holder Foldable Suction Cup Mount for Car UK</product_name><description>STRONG MAGNETIC PHONE HOLDER – 360° ADJUSTABLE 🚗
Foldable Design | Powerful Magnetic Hold | Vacuum Suction Mount

Keep your phone secure and within easy reach while driving with this Strong Magnetic Car Phone Holder. Designed with a powerful vacuum suction base and strong magnetic grip, it keeps your device firmly in place even on bumpy roads. The 360° adjustable rotation and foldable design allow you to position your phone at the perfect viewing angle for navigation, calls, or media.

Perfect for use on car dashboards, windshields, desks, kitchens, bathrooms, or any smooth surface.

⭐ Key Features
🔹 Strong Magnetic Hold – Powerful magnets keep your phone firmly in place
🔹 360° Adjustable Rotation – Rotate your phone to any viewing angle
🔹 Foldable &amp; Compact Design – Easy to fold and store when not in use
🔹 Strong Vacuum Suction Base – Secure grip on dashboards, windshields, desks and tiles
🔹 Universal Compatibility – Works with most smartphones including iPhone, Samsung, Huawei, Xiaomi and more
🔹 Multi-Purpose Use – Perfect for car, office desk, kitchen, bathroom or bedside table
📦 Available Pack Options
1 × Magnetic Phone Holder
Ideal for daily use in your car or around the home and office.

📋 Product Specifications
Specification	Detail
Product Type	Magnetic Phone Holder
Rotation	360° Adjustable
Mount Type	Vacuum Suction Base
Design	Foldable &amp; Compact
Compatibility	Universal – Works with most smartphones
Use	Car Dashboard, Windshield, Desk, Kitchen, Bathroom
🚚 Shipping &amp; Returns
✅ FREE UK Shipping
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ 30-Day Easy Returns
✅ Safe &amp; Secure Packaging
Drive safer and keep your phone perfectly positioned every journey.

✅ Strong Magnetic Hold | ✅ 360° Adjustable | ✅ Universal Smartphone Compatibility</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sGgAAeSw4v9prqxS/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GwsAAeSwq0tprqw9/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/q50AAeSwnQFprqw7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RV0AAeSw7S9prqw7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/88wAAeSwxxJprqw7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G1IAAeSwZYpprqw7/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Mobile Phones &amp; Communication Mobile Phone Accessories Mounts &amp; Holders</category><ean>404834092291</ean><condition>New</condition><price>10.0</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092307</sku><product_name>Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap Hygienic Handheld Toilet Kit UK</product_name><description>Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap – Hygienic Handheld Toilet Kit (UK Stock)
Upgrade your bathroom hygiene with this Chrome Muslim Shower Head &amp; Hose Bidet Spray Tap, designed for convenience, cleanliness, and durability. This practical Handheld Toilet Kit delivers a strong yet controlled water spray, providing a more hygienic and comfortable alternative to traditional cleaning methods. With a sleek chrome finish and easy installation, it is a perfect addition to any modern bathroom.


⭐ Key Features
Hygienic Cleaning Solution – Ensures effective and refreshing cleaning with a smooth, controlled water flow.
Premium Chrome Finish – Rust-resistant chrome coating adds durability and a modern bathroom look.
Ergonomic Handheld Design – Easy-grip Handheld Toilet Kit designed for comfort and simple operation.
Flexible Hose Included – Durable flexible hose allows extended reach and convenient use.
Leak-Resistant Construction – Built with high-quality materials for reliable and long-lasting performance.
Quick &amp; Easy Installation – Easily connects to most standard bathroom taps or water outlets.
Compact &amp; Space Saving – Wall-mounted design keeps your bathroom organised and clutter-free.

🌍 Vast Applications &amp; Multiple Uses
This versatile Bidet Spray Tap is designed for a wide range of everyday uses:

Personal hygiene and toilet cleaning
Muslim ablution (wudu) preparation
Washing baby cloth nappies / diapers
Cleaning the toilet bowl and bathroom floor
Rinsing reusable sanitary products
Pet bathing and washing small animals
Filling buckets or cleaning containers
Washing muddy shoes or slippers
Balcony or garden rinsing tasks
General household cleaning where controlled water spray is needed

🏆 Why This Bidet Spray Tap Is Better Than Others
Stronger &amp; Controlled Water Pressure – Efficient cleaning without excessive water usage.
High-Quality Chrome Finish – More durable and rust-resistant compared to standard plastic sprayers.
Ergonomic Trigger Design – Smooth press handle offers better control and comfortable use.
Multi-Purpose Functionality – Ideal for hygiene and many cleaning tasks around the home.
Durable Hose Construction – Reinforced hose prevents leaks, cracks, and wear over time.
Easy Universal Installation – Compatible with most standard bathroom plumbing fittings.
Long-Lasting Performance – Built for everyday use with reliable and sturdy materials.

📦 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Bidet Spray Tap / Handheld Toilet Kit
Material: ABS with Chrome Finish
Hose Material: Reinforced Stainless Steel / Flexible Hose
Colour: Chrome Silver
Installation Type: Wall Mounted / Tap Connection
Hose Length: Approx. 1.2 m – 1.5 m
Spray Control: Manual Trigger Operation
Compatibility: Fits most standard bathroom fittings

✅ Benefits
Improves personal hygiene and comfort
Eco-friendly alternative to excessive toilet paper use
Durable rust-resistant construction
Multi-purpose cleaning tool for home and bathroom
Convenient handheld control for precise water use

🏠 Ideal For
Home bathrooms
Muslim households for daily ablution needs
Apartments and rental properties
Elderly care and hygiene support
Hotels, guest houses, and rental accommodations

📦 Package Includes
1 × Chrome Bidet Spray Head
1 × Flexible Hose
1 × Wall Holder / Mount (if included)
Installation fittings</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-y8AAeSwq~1prqKn/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9woAAeSwRbRprqKo/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T7cAAeSwSsJprqKp/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8t8AAeSwu6hprqKo/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Toilets &amp; Bidets Bidets</category><ean>404834092307</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.59</price><quantity>10</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092321</sku><product_name>iPhone 11 13 - 17 Pro Max Screen Protector Tempered Glass HD Clear Full Cover UK</product_name><description>📱 SCREEN PROTECTOR TEMPERED GLASS – iPHONE 13 / 14 / 15 / 16 / 17 SERIES
HD Clear Protection | Anti-Scratch | Bubble Free Installation

Protect your phone with this Premium Tempered Glass Screen Protector designed to guard against scratches, drops, and everyday wear. Featuring HD clarity, smooth touch response, and strong shatter resistance, it helps keep your device looking like new.

The precision cut design ensures excellent coverage while maintaining full touch sensitivity and display brightness.

⭐ Key Features
🔹 Premium Tempered Glass – Strong protection from scratches and minor drops
🔹 Anti-Scratch &amp; Anti-Shatter – Helps protect against keys, coins and impacts
🔹 HD Clear Transparency – Maintains original display brightness and clarity
🔹 Smooth Touch Response – Ultra-thin design preserves touch sensitivity
🔹 Easy Installation – Bubble-free adhesive for simple application
🔹 Case Friendly Design – Compatible with most protective cases
🔹 Fingerprint Resistant – Helps reduce smudges and marks
📋 Compatible Models
iPhone 13 / 13 Pro / 13 Pro Max
iPhone 14 / 14 Pro / 14 Pro Max
iPhone 15 / 15 Pro / 15 Pro Max
iPhone 16 Series
iPhone 17 Series
(Please select your correct model from the variation menu before purchase)

📦 Package Includes
3 × Tempered Glass Screen Protectors
📋 Product Specifications
Specification	Detail
Material	Tempered Glass
Features	Anti-Scratch, Anti-Shatter
Transparency	HD Clear
Touch Sensitivity	High Response
Installation	Easy Bubble Free Application
🚚 Shipping &amp; Returns
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Next Day Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ 30 Day Returns</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bxoAAeSwIgJp18lj/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/huYAAeSwfJZpso3B/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1k0AAeSw3Fxpso3B/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YgEAAeSw4v9pso3A/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Mobile Phones &amp; Communication Mobile Phone Accessories Screen Protectors</category><ean>404834092321</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092338</sku><product_name>Stylus Pen for Apple Model iPad Pen / Pencil / Stylus With Palm Rejection - UK</product_name><description>✏️ Stylus Pen for Apple iPad – Pencil Stylus with Palm Rejection (UK Stock)

Upgrade your digital writing and drawing experience with this Stylus Pen for iPad, designed for precision, comfort, and smooth performance. Whether you are taking notes, sketching ideas, editing photos, or navigating your device, this stylus delivers excellent control and responsiveness. With advanced Palm Rejection technology, you can rest your hand naturally on the screen while writing—just like using a traditional pen on paper.


⭐ Key Features
Advanced Palm Rejection – Write or draw comfortably with your palm resting on the screen without accidental touches.
High Precision Tip – Ultra-fine tip provides accurate writing, drawing, and editing.
Smooth &amp; Lag-Free Performance – Natural writing experience similar to a real pencil.
One-Touch Operation – Easy activation with a simple button, no complicated pairing required.
Lightweight &amp; Portable – Slim design makes it easy to carry with your iPad anywhere.
Rechargeable Battery – Long-lasting battery supports hours of continuous usage.

📱 Technical Specifications
Product Type: Stylus Pen for iPad
Feature: Palm Rejection Technology
Charging: USB Charging
Tip Type: High-precision fine tip
Material: Durable aluminium alloy body
Colour: White
Condition: Brand New
Stock: UK Stock – Fast Dispatch

📲 Compatibility
iPad 6th Generation
iPad 7th Generation
iPad 8th Generation
iPad 9th Generation
iPad 10th Generation
iPad Mini 5
iPad Mini 6
iPad Air 3
iPad Air 4
iPad Air 5
iPad Pro 3
iPad Pro 4
iPad Pro 5
iPad Pro 6

💡 Why Choose This Stylus Pen?
Designed for students, professionals, artists, and everyday iPad users
Reliable Palm Rejection allows comfortable and natural writing
Smooth, accurate performance for both productivity and creativity
Affordable alternative with excellent precision and usability

🎯 Ideal For
Digital note-taking during meetings and lectures
Drawing, sketching, and digital illustration
Online learning, studying, and document annotation
Photo editing and graphic design
Office tasks like signing documents and marking PDFs
Everyday iPad navigation with improved accuracy

🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Education: Perfect for students for note-taking, homework, and studying on iPad apps
Business &amp; Office Work: Sign documents, mark PDFs, and take meeting notes
Digital Art &amp; Design: Great for sketching, illustrating, and creative projects
Graphic &amp; Photo Editing: Enables detailed adjustments and precise control
Online Teaching &amp; Presentations: Teachers can annotate slides and explain concepts clearly
Gaming &amp; App Navigation: Provides better control in touch-based apps and games
Everyday Tablet Use: Scroll, tap, and interact with your iPad more comfortably

📦 Package Includes
1 × Stylus Pen for iPad
1 × Charging Cable
2 × Spare Nibs

📦 FREE SHIPPING
Fast &amp; Reliable UK Delivery
Secure Packaging
Quick Dispatch from UK Stock
No Extra Delivery Charges

🔄 30 DAYS RETURN POLICY
30-Day Hassle-Free Returns
Buy with Confidence
Full Customer Support
Easy Refund or Replacement if Needed</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/udsAAeSwH4RpspdU/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7JEAAeSwh6hpspdU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jJUAAeSwDDJpspdV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1SwAAeSwO61pspdV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aPsAAeSwOJBpspdU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7JMAAeSwh6hpspdV/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Tablet &amp; eBook Reader Accs Styluses</category><ean>404834092338</ean><condition>New</condition><price>10.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092345</sku><product_name>Stainless Steel Bowl With Lid For Instant Noodles Sealed And Portable Drain Bowl</product_name><description>🍜 STAINLESS STEEL NOODLE BOWL WITH LID – PORTABLE FOOD CONTAINER 🍜
Portable Meal Bowl | Built-In Strainer | Insulated Food Container

Enjoy hot meals anywhere with this Portable Stainless Steel Noodle Bowl with Lid. Designed with a convenient draining system, insulation layer, and carry handle, it is perfect for quick meals at home, office, school, or travel.

The sealed lid helps retain heat while the built-in drain holes allow easy water removal, making it ideal for noodles, pasta, soups, fruit, and snacks.

⭐ Key Features
🔹 Premium Stainless Steel – Durable, rust-resistant and food-safe material
🔹 Built-In Draining System – Drain water easily without a separate strainer
🔹 Double Layer Insulation – Helps maintain food temperature longer
🔹 Portable Handle Design – Easy to carry to work, school or travel
🔹 Sealed Lid – Helps prevent spills and protects food
🔹 Multi-Purpose Use – Perfect for noodles, pasta, soup, salad, fruit and snacks
🔹 Easy To Clean – Smooth surface allows quick and simple washing
📋 Product Specifications
Specification	Detail
Product Type	Portable Food / Noodle Bowl
Material	Stainless Steel + Metal Alloy
Capacity	Approx. 1000ml
Shape	Round
Colours Available	Black / Blue / Green
Features	Portable, Drain Design, Insulated, Lid
Use	Home, Office, School, Travel
🏠 Perfect For
🏫 Students and school meals
💼 Office lunches
🚆 Travel and commuting
🏠 Quick meals at home
🏕️ Camping and outdoor trips
📦 Package Includes
1 × Stainless Steel Bowl
1 × Sealed Lid
🚚 Shipping &amp; Returns
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ 30 Day Returns</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/brEAAeSwx0VptTk6/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/asYAAeSwYOVptTk6/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/cH4AAeSwX6tptTk7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Jt0AAeSwnExptTk6/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fksAAeSwdRtptTk6/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZMMAAeSwFAlptTk6/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Cookware, Dining &amp; Bar Tableware &amp; Serving Bowls</category><ean>404834092345</ean><condition>New</condition><price>15.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092352</sku><product_name>Display Port DP Male To HDMI Female Adapter Converter 4K HD 1080P For HDTV PC UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Connect your laptop, PC, or other Mini DisplayPort devices to HDMI monitors, TVs, or projectors with this Mini DisplayPort to HDMI Adapter. Supports crisp 4K resolution and high-quality audio, perfect for work, entertainment, or presentations.

Compact, lightweight, and easy to carry, this adapter is ideal for home, office, or travel use. No drivers or external power are required — simply plug and play.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 4K Ultra HD Support – Resolutions up to 3840×2160 for sharp images
🔹 Video &amp; Audio Transmission – Transfers sound and video simultaneously
🔹 Stable Signal – No flicker, lag, or interference
🔹 Gold Plated Connector – Improves conductivity and durability
🔹 Plug &amp; Play – No drivers or external power needed
🔹 Compact &amp; Portable – Easy to carry for office or travel
🔹 Wide Compatibility – Works with laptops, desktops, monitors, TVs, and projectors
📋 IMPORTANT NOTE
⚠ Only supports Mini DisplayPort → HDMI connection
❌ Not compatible with HDMI → DisplayPort conversion
⚠ HDMI cable required (not included)
📋 TECHNICAL SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Mini DisplayPort to HDMI Adapter
Input	Mini DisplayPort (Male)
Output	HDMI (Female)
Resolution Support	Up to 4K (3840×2160)
Material	PVC + Gold Plated Connector
Size	Approx. 50mm × 25mm
Weight	Approx. 10g
Power Supply	Not required (Plug &amp; Play)
📦 WHAT’S INCLUDED
1 × Mini DisplayPort to HDMI Adapter
🎯 IDEAL FOR
🏠 Home entertainment
🏢 Office and presentations
🖥️ Connecting laptops or PCs to monitors &amp; TVs
🎁 Gifts for tech users
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ Free UK delivery
✅ Fast dispatch
✅ 30-day returns
✅ UK-based customer support</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dI8AAeSwy8FptpJE/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bzUAAeSwchFptpJF/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YukAAeSwZyJptpJE/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TZMAAeSwj4FptpJF/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/arIAAeSwFYZptpJE/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/HNoAAeSw3FNptpJE/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Computer Cables &amp; Connectors Monitor/AV Cables &amp; Adapters</category><ean>404834092352</ean><condition>New</condition><price>2.79</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092369</sku><product_name>Reusable Silicone Icing Piping Bag Set with Stainless Steel Nozzles Cake Decorat</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Create beautiful cake designs like a professional with this Reusable Silicone Piping Bag and Nozzle Set. Perfect for decorating cakes, cupcakes, cookies, and desserts, this practical baking kit is ideal for both beginners and experienced bakers.

Made with durable stainless steel decorating tips and a flexible reusable silicone piping bag, this set is designed for easy use, cleaning, and long-term baking projects.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Complete Decorating Kit – Includes piping bag and decorating nozzles
🔹 Reusable Silicone Bag – Strong, flexible and easy to wash
🔹 Stainless Steel Nozzles – Rust-resistant and durable
🔹 Easy To Use – Suitable for beginners and professionals
🔹 Multi Purpose – Ideal for cakes, cupcakes, cookies and pastries
🔹 Easy Cleaning – Washable and reusable design
🔹 DIY Baking Essential – Perfect for home baking and celebrations
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Cake Decorating Kit
Material	430 Stainless Steel + PP Plastic + Silicone (EVA)
Bag Type	Reusable Silicone Piping Bag
Nozzle Material	Stainless Steel
Use	Cake Decorating / Baking / Dessert Making
Suitable For	Home Bakers &amp; Professionals
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
Reusable Silicone Piping Bag
Stainless Steel Nozzles
Coupler (Mounting Tip)
(Contents may vary depending on selected option)
🎯 IDEAL FOR
🎂 Cake decorating
🧁 Cupcake designs
🍪 Cookie icing
🎉 Birthday &amp; celebration cakes
🏠 Home baking projects
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ 30 Day Returns</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VS8AAeSwSxxpt-YT/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/pnUAAeSwvwZpt-ZI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Yr8AAeSwCxZpt-YU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G9sAAeSwnc1pt-YU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/naQAAeSwUotpt-YU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MIUAAeSwnNBpt-Yj/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Baking Accs. &amp; Cake Decorating Decorating Tools Icing Nozzles</category><ean>404834092369</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092376</sku><product_name>Cushion Seat Pillow Orthopaedic Coccyx Back Pain Relief Memory Foam Office Chair</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Improve your sitting comfort with this U-Shape Memory Foam Seat Cushion, designed to provide support and pressure relief during long sitting hours. Ideal for office workers, drivers, students, and home use.

Made with high-density memory foam and breathable mesh fabric, this ergonomic cushion provides lasting comfort while maintaining its shape over time.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Ergonomic U-Shape Design – Helps reduce pressure on the tailbone
🔹 Memory Foam Support – Adapts to body shape for better comfort
🔹 Breathable Mesh Cover – Promotes airflow and reduces heat
🔹 Removable Washable Cover – Easy cleaning for better hygiene
🔹 Anti-Slip Base – Keeps cushion securely in place
🔹 Multi-Purpose Use – Suitable for office chairs, cars, and home seating
🔹 Portable Design – Lightweight and travel friendly
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Seat Cushion
Shape	U-Shape Ergonomic Design
Material	Memory Foam (Polyurethane)
Cover Material	100% Polyester Mesh
Base	Anti-Slip PVC Fabric
Size	Approx. 45 × 36 × 6 cm
Colour	Black
Suitable For	Adults
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
1 × Memory Foam Seat Cushion
📌 CARE INSTRUCTIONS
Cover is removable and washable
Do not wash memory foam inner core
Allow cushion to fully expand after opening
Air dry foam only (do not machine wash)
🎯 IDEAL FOR
💼 Office chairs
🚗 Car seats and drivers
🏠 Home seating
♿ Wheelchairs
🎓 Students and study chairs
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ 30 Day Returns</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/weYAAeSwdWNpuTwB/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/k6QAAeSwi~JpuTwC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NR4AAeSwSn9puTwB/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iUkAAeSwlYJpuTwC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uYcAAeSwRbRpuTwC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/s5cAAeSwVRppuTwC/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>404834092376</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.13</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092383</sku><product_name>Rotating HD Rear View Car Camera Reversing Parking CAM Waterproof Night Vision</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Make parking safer and easier with this HD Car Reverse Camera. Designed for both front and rear installation, this waterproof camera provides a wide-angle view and clear night vision to help you avoid obstacles while reversing or parking.

Compatible with most vehicle monitors using an RCA video connection, making it a universal and practical safety upgrade for your car.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 HD Clear Image Quality – CMOS sensor delivers sharp video output
🔹 Wide Viewing Angle – 120°–170° lens helps reduce blind spots
🔹 Night Vision Support – Clear visibility in low light conditions
🔹 Waterproof Design – IP68/IP69 rated for all weather use
🔹 Front or Rear Installation – Flexible mounting options
🔹 Universal Compatibility – Works with most RCA monitors
🔹 Automatic Image Adjustment – Auto white balance, AGC and BLC
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Car Reverse Camera
Sensor	PC7440 1/4" Colour CMOS
Resolution	800 TV Lines (HD Output)
Effective Pixels	1080 × 720
Viewing Angle	120° – 170°
Video Output	RCA (1.0Vp-p, 75Ω)
Signal System	NTSC
Waterproof Rating	IP68 / IP69
Minimum Illumination	0.2 Lux (0 Lux with LED)
Power Supply	DC 12V
Current Consumption	≤300mA
Operating Temperature	-30°C to +65°C
Storage Temperature	-40°C to +75°C
Colour	Black
Weight	Approx. 160g
📌 IMPORTANT NOTES
⚠ Monitor not included
⚠ Requires RCA compatible display
⚠ Professional installation recommended
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ 30 Day Returns</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/M6MAAeSw1NJpu9~~/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZgEAAeSwuSppu9~~/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jmUAAeSwW3Rpu9~~/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZbIAAeSwa~1pu9~~/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YagAAeSwtoNpu9~~/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KfUAAeSwBiFpu9~8/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories Motors Advanced Driver Assistance Systems Parking Assistance Parking Cameras</category><ean>404834092383</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.57</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092406</sku><product_name>120 Pack Thick Melamine Foam Sponge Magic Eraser Dirt Cleaning 10x6x2CM Sponges</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Make cleaning easier with these Magic Melamine Cleaning Sponges. Designed to remove stubborn stains using only water, these powerful cleaning pads are perfect for kitchens, bathrooms, walls, appliances, and more.

These eco-friendly cleaning sponges work like an eraser to remove dirt, grease, and marks without the need for harsh chemicals.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 120PCS Value Pack – Ideal for home and professional cleaning
🔹 Strong Cleaning Power – Removes grease, marks, and stubborn stains
🔹 Multi Surface Cleaning – Suitable for kitchen, bathroom, and appliances
🔹 Eco-Friendly Material – Clean without harsh chemicals
🔹 Easy To Cut – Can be trimmed to the required size
🔹 Lightweight &amp; Practical – Simple everyday cleaning solution
⭐ SUITABLE FOR CLEANING
✔ Kitchen surfaces &amp; appliances
✔ Bathroom tiles &amp; sinks
✔ Walls &amp; doors
✔ Shoes &amp; sports equipment
✔ Car interior surfaces
✔ Office equipment
✔ Furniture &amp; household items
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Magic Cleaning Sponge
Material	Melamine Foam
Colour	White
Size	Approx. 100 × 60 × 20 mm
Quantity	120 Pieces
Use	Multi-purpose Cleaning
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
120 × Magic Cleaning Sponges
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eVkAAeSw-cBpxTAr/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iOEAAeSw8JdpxTAq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qLUAAeSw3GdpxTAr/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/azgAAeSwSqlpxTAs/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Vh0AAeSw6o1pxTAn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/axsAAeSwSqlpxTAp/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Cleaning Tools Sponges &amp; Scourers</category><ean>404834092406</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.59</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092420</sku><product_name>Women Lady Bikini Cover Up Sarong Beach Long Dress Swimwear Swimsuit Plus Size</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Stay stylish and comfortable with this Women’s Summer Strap Dress, perfect for beach days, holidays, casual outings, and everyday summer wear. Designed with a relaxed fit and lightweight fabric, this dress delivers both comfort and effortless fashion.

The backless crossover strap design adds a modern and elegant touch, making it ideal for casual wear, holidays, or summer occasions.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Lightweight Summer Fabric – Soft cotton and polyester blend for breathable comfort
🔹 Stylish Strap Design – Spaghetti straps with fashionable backless crossover style
🔹 Loose Comfortable Fit – Relaxed design for all-day wear
🔹 Knee Length Style – Perfect balance between casual and elegant
🔹 Sleeveless Design – Ideal for warm summer weather
🔹 Versatile Wear – Suitable for beach, holidays, casual outings, and parties
🔹 Easy To Style – Matches well with sandals, trainers, or heels
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women’s Summer Dress
Material	Cotton + Polyester
Fit Type	Loose Fit
Length	Knee Length
Sleeve Type	Sleeveless
Neckline	Strap / Round (varies by style)
Elasticity	Medium Stretch
Season	Summer
Colours	Available in variations
Sizes	Multiple size options available
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
1 × Women’s Summer Dress
📦 AVAILABLE OPTIONS
Multiple sizes available
Multiple colours available
Please select your preferred option from the variation menu
🚚 UK SHIPPING &amp; SUPPORT
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-zQAAeSwNOtpynFk/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6HAAAeSwWtdpynFj/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/a-UAAeSwU4JpynFi/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ObAAAeSwLydpynFj/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PvcAAeSwJHtpynFj/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8eUAAeSwdJ9pynFk/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Clothing Swimwear</category><ean>404834092420</ean><condition>New</condition><price>1499.0</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092437</sku><product_name>Handheld Shattaf Bidet Sprayer Toilet Muslim Hygienic Jet Spray Shower Hose Kit</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Improve your bathroom hygiene with this Handheld Shattaf Bidet Sprayer Kit, designed for durability, comfort, and everyday convenience. This hygienic spray is ideal for personal cleaning, Muslim shower use, baby care, pet washing, and general bathroom cleaning.

Made from high-quality ABS material, this bidet sprayer is lightweight, rust-resistant, and easy to install with a universal G1/2 connection compatible with most toilets and shower systems.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Hygienic Cleaning Solution – Ideal for personal hygiene
✅ Ergonomic Handheld Design – Comfortable grip and easy operation
✅ Trigger Control System – Press to spray, release to stop water
✅ Durable ABS Material – Rust resistant and long lasting
✅ Flexible 1.5M Hose – Provides easy movement and convenience
✅ Universal Connection – Fits most standard toilet and shower systems
✅ Multi-Purpose Use – Suitable for toilet cleaning, baby care, pet washing, floor cleaning and gardening
✅ Easy Installation – Wall mounting bracket included
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Handheld Bidet Sprayer Kit
Material	ABS Plastic
Colour	Black
Sprayer Length	12.8 cm
Hose Length	1.5 metres
Hose Outer Diameter	2.2 cm
Hose Inner Diameter	1.9 cm
Connector	Standard G1/2
Weight	Approx. 308g
Installation	Wall Mount
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Bidet Spray Gun
✔ 1 × Flexible Hose
✔ 1 × Wall Holder Bracket
✔ 2 × Screws
✔ 2 × Wall Plugs
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Special discounts on multiple quantities
Check offer section above for latest deals
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WKsAAeSwk4ppz6Lu/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ErkAAeSwpuxpz6Lu/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WdQAAeSwebtpz6Lw/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RAkAAeSwin9pz65D/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4lMAAeSwin9pz6Lu/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NPEAAeSwgetpz6Lv/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Toilets &amp; Bidets Bidets</category><ean>404834092437</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.11</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092444</sku><product_name>1x Mechanical Clicker Hand Tally Counter 4 Digit Manual Number Counter Tool UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Make counting simple and accurate with this Mechanical Hand Tally Counter, ideal for inventory management, sports training, events, and crowd counting. Built with a strong stainless steel body, this manual clicker counter is reliable, durable, and requires no batteries.

Its compact and lightweight design makes it easy to carry and operate with one hand, making it a practical tool for professional and everyday use.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 4 Digit Mechanical Counter – Counts from 0000 to 9999
✅ No Batteries Required – Manual operation ensures reliability
✅ Durable Metal Body – Stainless steel construction resists rust
✅ Smooth Click Mechanism – Accurate counting with each press
✅ Reset Knob Included – Easy reset back to zero
✅ Portable &amp; Lightweight – Comfortable finger grip design
✅ Optional Base Design – Stable desk placement (base model only)
✅ Multi-Purpose Use – Suitable for inventory, sports, events and people counting
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Hand Tally Counter
Material	Stainless Steel
Counting Range	0 – 9999
Operation	Manual Click
Power Supply	Not Required
Type Options	With Base / Without Base
Colour	Silver
Design	Compact Handheld Size
🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Warehouse inventory counting
✔ Golf and sports training
✔ Event attendance counting
✔ School and laboratory use
✔ Workshop production counting
✔ Passenger counting
✔ Stitching and knitting counting
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Mechanical Hand Tally Counter
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/myoAAeSwuC9p0TAB/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/F6MAAeSwEllp0TAC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/F6AAAeSwEllp0TAC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JFgAAeSw58xp0TAB/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WKcAAeSwnLRp0TAC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vPYAAeSwEOBp0TAB/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Business, Office &amp; Industrial PLCs &amp; HMIs PLC Peripheral Modules Counter Modules</category><ean>404834092444</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092451</sku><product_name>Women's Fishnet Thigh-High Stockings Tights Suspender Pantyhose Stocking Hosiery</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Add elegance and style to your outfit with these women’s lace garter stockings, designed with a sheer fishnet finish and decorative floral lace top. Made from a soft nylon and polyester blend, these stockings provide comfort, flexibility, and a fashionable look.

Perfect for pairing with dresses, skirts, costumes, or evening outfits, these thigh-high stockings add a stylish finishing touch to any wardrobe.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Soft Stretch Material – Comfortable nylon and polyester blend
✅ Elegant Lace Top – Stylish floral pattern design
✅ Sheer Fishnet Style – Modern fashionable appearance
✅ One Size Fit – Flexible stretch design fits most
✅ Lightweight &amp; Breathable – Comfortable for extended wear
✅ Over Knee Length – Classic thigh high styling
✅ Multiple Styles Available – Choose your preferred design
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women’s Stockings
Material	Nylon / Polyester
Size	One Size (Stretch Fit)
Length	Approx. 80–110 cm
Pattern	Floral Lace
Thickness	Standard
Gender	Women
Quantity	1 Pair
Style	Fashion Hosiery
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔  1 x Pantyhose（Does not contain thong underwear）
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Discreet Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EWAAAeSwk2dp08uK/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FlcAAeSwjX1p08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/l2UAAeSwnLRp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y6IAAeSwU4Jp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1H4AAeSwCoRp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sHcAAeSw-2Bp08uJ/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women's Clothing Hosiery &amp; Socks Tights</category><ean>404834092451</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340975103</sku><product_name>2 Pack Tea Ball Strainer Stainless Steel Mesh Infuser for Loose Leaf Tea &amp; Her</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Enjoy perfectly brewed tea with this 2 Pack Stainless Steel Tea Infuser Set, ideal for loose leaf tea, herbs, and spices. Made from premium 304 food-grade stainless steel, these tea balls are durable, rust-resistant, and safe for everyday use.

The fine mesh design keeps tea leaves securely inside while allowing full flavour infusion for a smooth and enjoyable drink. Perfect for tea lovers at home, in the office, or while travelling.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 2 Pack Value Set – Perfect for home, office, or travel use
✅ 304 Stainless Steel – Food grade, rust resistant material
✅ Fine Mesh Filter – Prevents tea leaves escaping into your drink
✅ Chain &amp; Hook Design – Easily attaches to mugs, cups, and teapots
✅ Multi-Purpose Use – Suitable for tea, herbs, spices, and soups
✅ Easy To Clean – Simply rinse or place in dishwasher
✅ Reusable &amp; Eco Friendly – Reduce disposable tea bag waste
✅ Compact Design – Easy storage and portable size
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Tea Ball Infuser
Material	304 Stainless Steel
Quantity	2 Pieces
Colour	Silver
Design	Mesh Ball with Chain Hook
Use	Loose Tea / Herbs / Spices
Features	Reusable / Washable
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 2 × Stainless Steel Tea Ball Infusers
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LnIAAeSwn8tp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MocAAeSwamJp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Q64AAeSwN8dp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/P9IAAeSw0Plp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ra4AAeSwK4lp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XPkAAeSwLGBp1mqQ/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Accessories</category><ean>4048340975103</ean><condition>New</condition><price>4.97</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092277</sku><product_name>Hold Ups stockings elasticated lace top thigh high Sheer Many colours very sexy</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Add elegance and style to your outfit with these Women’s Sheer Lace Stay-Up Thigh High Stockings. Designed with soft stretch fabric and a beautiful lace trim, these stockings provide a secure yet comfortable fit while enhancing your fashion look.

Perfect for evening wear, parties, special occasions, or everyday styling, these fashionable hold-up stockings are a must-have addition to any wardrobe.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Elegant Lace Top – Stylish floral lace trim design
✅ Stay-Up Hold Design – Elastic band helps stockings stay securely in place
✅ Soft Sheer Fabric – Lightweight and breathable material
✅ Stretch Fit Material – Flexible design for comfortable wear
✅ Thigh High Length – Modern fashionable style
✅ Multiple Colours Available – Choose your preferred style
✅ Perfect For Many Occasions – Ideal for parties, evenings, and fashion outfits
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women’s Stockings
Style	Stay-Up / Hold-Ups
Material	Nylon / Spandex
Size	One Size (Stretch Fit – fits most)
Length	Thigh High
Pattern	Solid with Lace Top
Thickness	Thin / Sheer
Colours	Black, White, Red, Purple, Pink, Brown
Department	Women
Condition	New 
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Pair Women’s Lace Stockings
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check the offer section above for latest deals
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Discreet Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5v8AAeSwiJ5p16Vm/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6HEAAeSwwtlp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IFUAAeSwZ81p16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EcsAAeSwhHJp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1fwAAeSwamJp16Vq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TOYAAeSwJVdp16Vn/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women's Clothing Hosiery &amp; Socks Stockings &amp; Hold-ups Item description from the seller</category><ean>404834092277</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092482</sku><product_name>Men's Leather Cross Body Messenger Shoulder Bag Handbag Travel Work Business Bag</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Upgrade your everyday style with this Rugged Vintage Texture Shoulder Bag, designed for daily use, work, travel, and casual outings. Made from high-quality PU leather, this bag offers durability with a classic vintage finish.

Featuring a lightweight build and adjustable shoulder strap, it can be worn comfortably as a shoulder bag or crossbody bag. Perfect for keeping your essentials organised while maintaining a stylish look.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Vintage Leather Look – Stylish rugged design for everyday wear
✅ Lightweight &amp; Comfortable – Ideal for long-term use
✅ Adjustable Strap – Wear as shoulder or crossbody bag
✅ Durable PU Leather – Strong and long-lasting material
✅ Spacious Storage – Fits phone, wallet, keys, and essentials
✅ Internal Pockets – Keeps items organised
✅ Multi-Purpose Use – Perfect for work, travel, school, and daily use
✅ Unisex Design – Suitable for men and women
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Shoulder / Crossbody Bag
Style	Casual / Business / Vintage
Material	PU Leather
Lining Material	Polyester
Closure Type	Zip (varies by model)
Strap Type	Adjustable
Colours Available	Black, Brown, Khaki
Gender	Unisex
Occasion	Work / Travel / Daily Use
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Shoulder Crossbody Bag
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals
🚚 UK SHIPPING
✅ FREE UK Delivery
✅ Fast Dispatch
✅ Secure Packaging
✅ Tracking Available</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V4sAAeSwOqpp2RX4/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jZMAAeSw4u1p2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ALQAAeSwKRRp2RX5/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VaAAAeSwpFxp2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5x0AAeSwFd5p2RX4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GEMAAeSwf5Np2RX5/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Accessories Bags</category><ean>404834092482</ean><condition>New</condition><price>19.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092499</sku><product_name>Strong Vacuum Suction Cup Hook Shower Towel-Holder Hooks for Bathroom Kitchen UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Organise your space easily with these Vacuum Suction Cup Hooks, designed to provide a strong hold without drilling or damaging your walls. Made from premium 304 stainless steel, these hooks are perfect for bathrooms, kitchens, and home organisation.

With powerful suction grip and a modern design, they securely hold towels, bags, and accessories on smooth surfaces while keeping your space neat and clutter-free.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ No Drilling Required – Easy installation without tools or wall damage
✅ Strong Suction Power – Holds up to approx. 15 lbs (6.8 kg)
✅ Waterproof &amp; Rustproof – Ideal for bathroom and kitchen use
✅ Durable Stainless Steel – Corrosion-resistant and long-lasting
✅ Modern Design – Matches any home décor style
✅ Reusable &amp; Removable – Easy to reposition without marks
✅ Anti-Slip Hook – Secure grip for hanging items safely
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Suction Cup Hook
Material	304 Stainless Steel
Installation	Vacuum Suction (No Drill)
Load Capacity	Up to 15 lbs (approx.)
Colour Options	Silver, Black, Gold, White
Use	Bathroom, Kitchen, Home Organisation
🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Towels &amp; bath accessories
✔ Kitchen utensils
✔ Handbags &amp; keys
✔ Clothes &amp; hats
✔ Shower accessories
📦 PACKAGE OPTIONS
✔ 1 × Hook
✔ 2 × Hooks (Value Pack)
⚠️ INSTALLATION TIPS
Suitable for smooth surfaces only (tiles, glass, metal, wood)
Not suitable for painted or rough walls
Press firmly and wait 24 hours before use
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AH0AAeSwhHJp3luF/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LO0AAeSwQOlp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sWwAAeSwYOtp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VpwAAeSw7T5p3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KxoAAeSwKuRp3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/foQAAeSwibJp3luG/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household Accessories &amp; Supplies Storage Solutions Wall Hooks &amp; Door Hangers</category><ean>404834092499</ean><condition>New</condition><price>22.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092505</sku><product_name>Mens Body Shaper Compression Vest Slimming Shirt Tank Chest Belly Men's Waist UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a more confident look instantly with this Men’s Slimming Compression Vest, designed to shape your chest, flatten your stomach, and support better posture. Made from a breathable stretch fabric, this vest provides firm compression while remaining comfortable for all-day wear.

Perfect for daily wear, gym workouts, or under clothing for a slimmer appearance. Lightweight, flexible, and discreet under shirts for everyday confidence.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Instant Slimming Effect – Flattens belly and shapes chest
✅ Compression Fit Design – Supports posture and core
✅ Breathable Fabric – Comfortable for all-day wear
✅ Seamless Under Clothing – Invisible under shirts
✅ High Elastic Material – Flexible body-contouring fit
✅ Lightweight &amp; Comfortable – Ideal for daily or sports use
✅ Multi-Purpose Wear – Gym, running, work, or casual wear
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Men’s Compression Vest / Body Shaper
Material	Polyester
Fabric Type	Breathable Stretch
Style	Sleeveless Vest
Fit	Slim Compression Fit
Colours	Black, White
Sizes	M, L, XL, XXL
Pattern	Solid
Care	Machine Washable
Condition	New 
📌 SIZE TIP
Choose one size up for a more comfortable fit.

🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Daily wear under shirts
✔ Gym &amp; fitness training
✔ Running, cycling, workouts
✔ Body shaping &amp; posture support
✔ Confidence boosting appearance
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Men’s Compression Vest
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rCoAAeSwmlFp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1hUAAeSwT05p4QUL/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jHwAAeSweM9p4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FWcAAeSwvsRp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iPwAAeSwLqJp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TP0AAeSwqZVp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Clothing Underwear</category><ean>404834092505</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092512</sku><product_name>5 Pack Womens Sexy Knickers Underwear Ladies Lace Panties Seamless Briefs Pants</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Refresh your essentials with this 5 Pack Women’s Cotton Lace Briefs Set, designed for everyday comfort with a stylish feminine touch. Made from a soft cotton-rich stretch fabric, these knickers offer breathable comfort, flexible fit, and delicate lace trim.

Perfect for daily wear, work, travel, or casual comfort, these briefs combine practicality with elegant style while providing a smooth and comfortable fit under clothing.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 5 Pack Value Set – Includes 5 assorted colours/styles
✅ Soft Cotton Rich Fabric – Comfortable and breathable feel
✅ 100% Cotton Crotch Lining – Extra freshness and hygiene
✅ Low Waist Design – Modern flattering fit
✅ Stretch Material – Flexible comfort for all-day wear
✅ Lace Trim Finish – Elegant, feminine detail
✅ Lightweight &amp; Breathable – Ideal for everyday use
✅ Comfort Fit Brief Style – Smooth under clothing
🎨 COLOUR OPTIONS
🌈 Mixed Colour Packs Available

📌 Due to monitor and lighting differences, actual colours may vary slightly from images.

📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women’s Knickers / Briefs
Style	Low Waist Briefs
Material	95% Cotton / 5% Spandex
Crotch Fabric	100% Cotton
Decoration	Lace Trim
Pattern	Solid Colours
Fit	Regular Stretch Fit
Sizes Available	M, L, XL
Quantity	5 Pieces Set
📏 SIZE GUIDE
📌 Asian sizing may run smaller than UK/EU sizes. Please consider choosing one size up for best comfort.

M – Suitable for Small
L – Suitable for Medium
XL – Suitable for Large
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 5 × Women’s Cotton Lace Briefs (Mixed / Selected Colours)
🎯 PERFECT FOR
✔ Everyday wear
✔ Work &amp; office use
✔ Travel
✔ Comfortable daily essentials
✔ Gift idea
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C4EAAeSwE2Fp421f/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L6QAAeSwyXBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G2AAAeSwPw9p421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WsMAAeSwXCBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FoIAAeSwrHRp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/snkAAeSwX9xp421h/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women's Clothing Lingerie &amp; Nightwear Knickers</category><ean>404834092512</ean><condition>New</condition><price>16.99</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918261</sku><product_name>Laptop Sleeve Case NoteBook Pouch Bag for Macbook Air Pro 11" 13" 14" 15" UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Keep your laptop safe and stylish with this Black Laptop Sleeve Bag, designed for everyday protection and portability. Suitable for many popular laptop brands including Lenovo, Dell, HP, Xiaomi, Asus, Acer, MacBook Air &amp; MacBook Pro.

Featuring a soft padded interior, secure zip closure, and slim lightweight design, this laptop case is ideal for work, travel, school, commuting, or daily use.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Multi-Size Options Available – Fits 11", 13", 14", 15", 15.6" laptops
✅ Protective Padded Design – Helps protect against scratches and bumps
✅ Smooth Zip Closure – Secure and easy access
✅ Slim Lightweight Sleeve – Easy to carry alone or inside backpack
✅ Soft Interior Lining – Gentle on laptop surfaces
✅ Classic Black Colour – Professional modern look
✅ Unisex Design – Suitable for men and women
✅ Perfect for Travel &amp; Work – Great for office, college, commuting
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Laptop Sleeve / Carry Case
Colour	Multi
Material	Cotton / Soft Fabric
Closure Type	Zipper
Style	Slim Sleeve Case
Gender	Unisex
Pattern	Solid
📏 INTERNAL SIZE GUIDE
📌 Please ensure your laptop dimensions are smaller than internal measurements.

11 / 12 Inch: 300 × 205 × 20 mm
13 Inch: 320 × 235 × 20 mm
14 / 15 Inch: 340 × 250 × 20 mm
15.6 Inch: 360 × 280 × 20 mm
💻 COMPATIBLE WITH
✔ MacBook Air / Pro
✔ Lenovo Laptops
✔ Dell Notebooks
✔ HP Laptops
✔ Xiaomi Notebooks
✔ Asus / Acer / Many Others
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Black Laptop Sleeve Bag
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PsAAAeSwaENp4534/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZWYAAeSw7ztp4534/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XPEAAeSwJVdp4534/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5xYAAeSwPY9p4534/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/f-kAAeSwmR5p4532/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DsAAAeSwQzRp4533/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Laptop &amp; Desktop Accessories Laptop Cases &amp; Bags</category><ean>4048340918261</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918254</sku><product_name>Push to Open System Damper Buffer Cabinet Drawer Hinge Heavier Catch Heavy Duty</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Upgrade your cabinets and drawers with this Push to Open Magnetic Catch Set. Simply press the door to latch or unlatch – no handles or knobs required. Creates a clean, seamless, modern look for your kitchen, wardrobe, or furniture.

Built-in magnet ensures a secure, tight close, preventing doors from drifting open. The adjustable 1/4" stroke makes installation easy and forgiving.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Push to Open Design – One-touch open/close, no knobs or handles needed
🔹 Magnetic Holding Force – Keeps doors tightly closed, prevents drifting
🔹 Adjustable Stroke (1/4 inch) – Easier installation with alignment tolerance
🔹 Soft Closer Rebound – Smooth, quiet operation
🔹 Universal Fit – Works for cabinets, drawers, wardrobes, cupboards, and furniture doors
🔹 Durable Construction – High-quality materials for long-lasting use
🔹 Multiple Quantities – Choose from 3, 5, or 10 pieces per set
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Push to Open Magnetic Catch / Damper
Function	Push-to-open &amp; soft close rebound
Magnetic Force	Built-in magnet for secure closing
Adjustable Stroke	Approx. 1/4 inch (6-7mm)
Application	Cabinet doors, drawers, wardrobes, cupboards, furniture
Colour	As shown in pictures (typically silver/black/white – check your variant)
Size	As shown in pictures (standard cabinet catch size)
Package Options	3pcs, 5pcs, or 10pcs per set</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9PAAAeSwfqVp52vi/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YZsAAeSwzmBp52vg/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JEIAAeSw88dp52vi/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5G4AAeSwvb1p52vi/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/q9MAAeSwJSpp52vh/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fbIAAeSwi0Vp52vi/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden DIY Materials Cabinet Hardware Cabinet Catches &amp; Latches</category><ean>4048340918254</ean><condition>New</condition><price>23.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091829</sku><product_name>Portable Zipper Eye Glasses Hard Case Sunglass Reading Cover Box Protector Gift</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Keep your glasses safe and stylish with this Fashion Denim Fabric Glasses Case. Made from high-quality cotton denim, this soft-shell case features a smooth zipper closure and a trendy patchwork pattern. Perfect for sunglasses, reading glasses, or prescription eyewear.

The lightweight yet protective design prevents scratches, dust, and damage while you're on the go. A must-have accessory for anyone who wants to keep their glasses organized and protected.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Premium Denim Fabric – High-quality cotton, soft yet durable
🔹 Zipper Closure – Secure, smooth-gliding zipper keeps glasses safely inside
🔹 Scratch Protection – Soft interior lining prevents lens scratches
🔹 Fashion Patchwork Design – Trendy and unisex style for men and women
🔹 Universal Size – Fits most sunglasses, reading glasses, and prescription eyewear
🔹 Lightweight &amp; Portable – Easy to carry in purse, backpack, or pocket
🔹 Great Gift Idea – Perfect for glasses wearers, travelers, or fashion lovers
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Soft Shell Eyeglasses Case / Sunglasses Pouch
Material	Denim Fabric (Cotton) – No high-concerned chemicals
Closure	Zipper
Pattern Type	Patchwork
Dimensions (approx.)	Length: 16cm (6.3″), Width: 6cm (2.4″), Height: 3.5cm (1.4″)
Weight	Approx. 106g (3.7 oz)
Gender	Unisex
Brand	UNBRANDED
Origin	China
Package Included	1 × Eyeglasses Box / Case</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y90AAeSwKuRp55JU/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/D28AAeSwkJNp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yS4AAeSwAnFp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BREAAeSwrclp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5-4AAeSw7LFp55JU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Bz8AAeSwkXBp55JU/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Vision Care Glasses Cases &amp; Storage</category><ean>404834091829</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340918230</sku><product_name>2X Clay Bar Cloth Clay Cloth Washing Towel For Car Paint Detailing Cleaning UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Transform your car detailing routine with this Magic Clay Towel. Unlike traditional clay bars, this dual-sided cleaning cloth covers a wider area and cleans faster – using only clean water or foam. The microfiber side lifts dirt while the clay side removes bonded contaminants like oxidation, water spots, ferrous powder, light rust, brake dust, and bird droppings.

Save up to 70% of your detailing time. Reusable multiple times – simply rinse with water and store in a cool, dry place. Will not damage your car's paint or shine.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Only Requires Clean Water – No soaps or chemicals needed for most jobs
🔹 Dual-Sided Design – Microfiber side for general wiping, clay side for stubborn contamination
🔹 Removes Tough Stains – Heavy oxidation, rainwater stains, ferrous powder, light rust, brake dust,etc
🔹 Wider Coverage – Cleans a larger area faster than a traditional clay bar
🔹 Saves 70% Time &amp; Effort – Complete car detailing in as little as 10 minutes
🔹 Reusable Multiple Times – Rinse with water after use – won't melt or deteriorate
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Magic Clay Towel / Car Decontamination Cloth
Special Features	Car cleaning – removes oxidation, water spots, brake dust, bird droppings
Material	Microfiber + Polymer clay composite
Model Options	Fine clay towel (gentle) / Medium clay towel (more aggressive)
Colour	Blue
Size	Approx. 30 × 30 cm (11.81 × 11.81 inches)
Weight	Approx. 130g (4.6 oz)
Package Included	1 × Clay Towel</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5w4AAeSwcM9p6OnK/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MhIAAeSwyMZp6OnG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/z4EAAeSw4ABp6OnG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RcoAAeSwZeRp6OnG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RcoAAeSwZeRp6OnG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yZ4AAeSwAxBp6OnH/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Cleaning Tools Cleaning Towels &amp; Cloths</category><ean>4048340918230</ean><condition>New</condition><price>10.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340922845</sku><product_name>Army Military Style Baseball Cadet Cap Hat Cadet Combat Fishing-Baseball-Cap UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Step out in retro style with this Washed Denim Flat Top Hat. Inspired by vintage military and fishing caps, this hat features an old-wash jeans look, a firm flat top (bib style), and a comfortable fit for both men and women. The tatting weaving craft adds durability and texture, while the 360° brim offers excellent sun protection for outdoor adventures.

Perfect for fishing, hiking, gardening, travel, or daily casual wear. Designed to fit larger heads comfortably, with a unisex European-inspired silhouette.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Retro Washed Denim Look – Old wash jeans style with a vintage, casual vibe
🔹 Flat Top (Bib) Design – Classic military/fishing hat silhouette – holds its shape
🔹 Sun Protection – Full brim helps shield face and neck from UV rays
🔹 Tatting Weaving Craft – Durable, textured fabric for long-lasting wear
🔹 Unisex &amp; Big Head Friendly – Comfortable fit for men and women, accommodates larger head sizes
🔹 Four Seasons Use – Breathable cotton/polyester blend suitable for spring, summer, autumn, winter
🔹 European Trend Style – Fashion-forward accessory for outdoor or city wear
🔹 Easy Care – Do not machine wash, bleach, or iron – spot clean only
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Item Type	Military Style Hat / Flat Top Cap / Fishing Hat
Material	Cotton / Polyester blend (as per style)
Craft of Weaving	Tatting
Feature	Sun protection
Applicable Scene	Outdoor, casual, fishing, travel, daily wear
Applicable Season	Four seasons (spring, summer, autumn, winter)
Gender	Men (unisex – also fits women)
Department Name	Adult unisex
Colour	Multicolored (washed denim effect – as pictured)
Style	Casual, Retro, European Trend
Size (approx.)	28 × 18 × 11 cm (11″ × 7″ × 4.3″)
Number of pieces	1 hat
Care Instructions	Do not machine wash / Do not bleach / Do not iron – spot clean only</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~HIAAeSwjCJp6hNW/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Wt0AAeSw2Cpp6hNW/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zqkAAeSw5Ahp6hNV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/D4YAAeSw5vBp6hNW/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/azIAAeSwsL5p6hNX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EKQAAeSwN-lp6hNW/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Accessories Hats</category><ean>4048340922845</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091843</sku><product_name>Heavy Duty Waterproof Garden Patio Furniture Cover for Rattan Table Cube Outdoor</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Protect your outdoor furniture from sun, rain, dust, and dirt with this High-Quality Outdoor Furniture Cover. Crafted from durable polyester and cotton, this cover offers reliable UV protection and weather resistance, keeping your terrace, garden chairs, and tables looking like new.

Available in over 200 sizes – find the perfect fit for your garden furniture. The modern, sleek design adds a touch of elegance to your outdoor space while providing heavy-duty protection.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 UV Protection – Shields furniture from harmful sun rays, preventing fading and cracking
🔹 Dust Barrier – Keeps outdoor furniture clean and ready to use at any moment
🔹 Water-Resistant Material – Polyester/cotton blend repels light rain and moisture
🔹 Customizable Fit – Available in over 200 sizes (see full list below)
🔹 Modern Style – Sleek, elegant design complements any terrace or garden
🔹 Durable Construction – Crafted for longevity and resistance to weather elements
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Outdoor Furniture Cover – Garden Chair/Table Protector
Material	Polyester / Cotton blend
Features	UV, dust, water-resistant (light rain)
Status	Eco-friendly
Style	Modern, sleek, elegant
Available Sizes	200+ options (see dropdown/variations)
Colour	As pictured
📏 AVAILABLE SIZES (SELECT YOUR FIT)
Choose from the following dimensions (Length × Width × Height in cm):

40×40×40	80×80×80	85×85×80	90×90×90
68×68×120	110×110×70	120×90×76	120×120×74
120×120×140	120×60×90	120×95×75	123×123×74
123×61×72	126×126×74	130×70×70	130×130×75
135×135×75	140×140×140	140×90×60	145×85×80
145×90×105	150×150×75	152×104×71	154×90×76
155×95×68	160×160×80	170×94×70	180×120×74
180×150×80	190×125×80	190×66×89	200×160×70
200×160×80	200×200×120	200×200×85	205×90×60</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RqQAAeSwPIZp7NLP/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Uv0AAeSwFO1p7NLQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/B20AAeSwFbNp7NLQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V94AAeSwKuRp7NLQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PW4AAeSwAxtp7NLQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7tQAAeSwe5tp7NLQ/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Garden &amp; Patio Garden &amp; Patio Furniture Outdoor Furniture Covers</category><ean>404834091843</ean><condition>New</condition><price>47.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834091980</sku><product_name>Womens Magic High Waist Slimming Underwear Knickers Briefs Firm Tummy Control UK</product_name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a smooth, sculpted silhouette with these Seamless High Waist Shaping Panties. Designed for all-day comfort, they offer tummy control, butt lifting, and a breathable fit – perfect for daily wear, postpartum recovery, or special occasions. The seamless knit construction prevents visible panty lines, while the nylon/elastane blend moves with your body.

Antibacterial and moisture-absorbing fabric keeps you fresh, and the high-waist design provides gentle compression without discomfort. Available in multiple sizes from XS to 4XL.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 High Waist Tummy Control – Firm but gentle shaping for a flatter stomach
🔹 Butt Lifter Design – Lifts and shapes your peach buttock naturally
🔹 Seamless Knit Fabric – No visible panty lines under tight clothing
🔹 Breathable &amp; Comfortable – Nylon/elastane blend for all-day wear
🔹 Antibacterial + Moisture-Absorbing – Keeps you dry and fresh
🔹 Maternity &amp; Postpartum Friendly – Gentle support for new mums
🔹 Easy to Wash – Machine washable, durable fabric
🔹 Multiple Sizes – XS-S, M-L, XL-XXL, 3XL, 4XL (see size chart)
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Item Type	High Waist Shaping Panties / Body Shaper
Material	Nylon + Elastane (knitted, seamless)
Colour	---
Abdominal Support	Yes – high waist compression
Butt Lifting	Yes – shapes the peach buttock
Special Features	Antibacterial, moisture-absorbing, seamless, breathable
Season	All seasons
Gender	Women / Maternity
Age Range	12+ years, maternity
Model Number	1102</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jsoAAeSwDeVp740B/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qpUAAeSwxahp740D/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vGUAAeSw7LFp740D/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4xkAAeSw0rNp74z~/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hHUAAeSw4u1p740H/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PvIAAeSwx-9p740E/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women's Clothing Lingerie &amp; Nightwear Shapewear</category><ean>404834091980</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.49</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045160</sku><product_name>Soft Padded Sleep 3D Eye Mask-Luxurious Blackout Blindfold-Travel Eye Cover UK</product_name><description>Experience deeper, uninterrupted sleep whether you are at home, traveling, or just taking a quick nap. This sleep mask is engineered for superior comfort and performance.

Key Features:

Ultra-Soft &amp; Breathable Memory Foam: 
The mask is crafted from premium memory foam that gently conforms to the contours of your face without putting pressure on your eyes, ensuring maximum comfort throughout the night.

3D Contoured Sleep Mask 100% Light Blocking Eye Mask Ultra-Soft Skin-Friendly Mask 

The ergonomic 3D design fits all face shapes without pressure on the eyes, making it perfect for both men women.

100% Light Blocking: Promotes deep, uninterrupted sleep.

Ultra-Soft Material: Gentle on all skin types.

Ergonomic 3D Fit: Contoured shape prevents eye pressure.

Breathable Design: Ventilated construction for all-night comfort.

Adjustable Fit: One size fits all – lightweight, and travel-friendly.

Multi-Use: Great for rest, meditation, flights, and shift work.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gJ8AAeSwr7tpAbai/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XIIAAeSwGBZpAbaj/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bHwAAeSwAXppAbai/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Zj0AAeSwLSdpAbaj/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fL4AAeSwvthpAbai/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V3cAAeSwDB5pAbai/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Luggage &amp; Travel Accessories Travel Accessories Eye Masks</category><ean>194343045160</ean><condition>New</condition><price>2.95</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045191</sku><product_name>UK Cycling Mountain Bike MTB Front &amp; Rear Ride Fender Mud Guard New Accessories</product_name><description>Stay protected in all weather conditions with this Mountain Bike Front &amp; Rear Mudguard Set, designed for reliable defence against mud, rainwater, and road debris. Ideal for MTB riders, commuters, and trail cyclists, this practical fender set is perfectly suited to unpredictable UK riding conditions.

🛡️ Effective Mud &amp; Splash Protection
Engineered to protect both front and rear wheels, these MTB mudguards help minimise dirty spray from reaching your clothing, bike frame, and essential components. Perfect for wet roads, muddy tracks, forest trails, and gravel paths.

🚵 Designed for Mountain &amp; Trail Riding
Specially developed for mountain bikes and hybrid bikes, this mud guard set performs efficiently on off-road terrain and urban commutes alike. Maintain visibility and comfort while riding through challenging conditions.

🔧 Durable &amp; Lightweight Construction
Crafted from strong yet lightweight materials, this MTB fender set is built for durability without adding unnecessary weight. Designed to handle everyday riding and debris impact while maintaining bike performance.

⚙️ Easy Installation &amp; Secure Fit
Quick and simple to install, the secure mounting system ensures the mudguards remain stable even on rough or uneven terrain. Compatible with most standard MTB frames and common wheel sizes.

🎯 Universal Compatibility
Suitable for a wide range of mountain bikes, hybrid bikes, and trail bikes, making it a versatile upgrade for both beginners and experienced cyclists.

🌧️ Perfect for UK Weather
Built for year-round cycling, this front and rear bike mudguard set provides dependable coverage during rainy and muddy UK rides.

🚴 Key Features:
✔ Front and rear wheel protection
✔ Reduces mud, dirt and water spray
✔ Lightweight and durable design
✔ Ideal for MTB, trail and hybrid bikes
✔ Quick and easy installation
✔ Enhances rider comfort and bike cleanliness</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aZYAAeSwAM9ppTLv/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VxgAAeSwAuNppTLv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FOkAAeSwiqlppTLv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L4oAAeSwdNtppTLv/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WeoAAeSwfzBppTLw/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Jn0AAeSwL5BppTLv/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Cycling Bike Accessories Mudguards</category><ean>194343045191</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045207</sku><product_name>Texture Comb Root Volumizing Tool Wide-Tooth Hair Styling Accessory-SeamCovering</product_name><description>Elevate your hairstyle with the Volumizing Wide-Tooth Hair Styling Comb, the ultimate tool for creating natural volume, soft curls, and textured looks. Designed for everyday styling, this comb lifts hair at the roots without tugging or causing damage, making it suitable for all hair types. Perfect for men who want effortless style and healthy hair.

Key Features

Wide-Tooth Design for Effortless Styling

The comb’s wide-tooth structure helps separate strands gently, reducing hair breakage and pulling. Achieve fuller, bouncy hair with minimal effort.

Volumizing &amp; Curl-Enhancing Tool

Shape and define your curls while adding root lift and texture. This versatile comb enhances natural waves and helps you achieve a soft, fluffy look.

Gentle on Hair

Crafted with smooth, durable plastic teeth, it glides easily through your hair, ensuring styling is comfortable and snag-free.

Lightweight &amp; Long-Lasting

Made with premium materials, this comb is durable yet lightweight, perfect for daily use and travel-friendly styling.

Universal Use

Ideal for men and suitable for all hair types, including normal hair. A must-have tool for creating stylish, effortless looks.

Product Specifications

Comb Type: Wide-tooth

Hair Style: All hair types

Bristle Material: Plastic

Handle Material: ABS Plastic

Package Includes

1 × Wide-Tooth Hair Styling Comb</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eOQAAeSwF2dppV5Y/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sDoAAeSwj3JppV5Y/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rgEAAeSwvlJppV5Z/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iWcAAeSwgxxppV5Y/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1EMAAeSw8z5ppV5Y/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sEkAAeSw2x1ppV5Z/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Hair Care &amp; Styling Brushes &amp; Combs</category><ean>194343045207</ean><condition>New</condition><price>2.69</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045245</sku><product_name>Plastic Scraper Tool Glass Window Cleaning Paint,Dirt,Sticker &amp; Grease Remover</product_name><description>Make cleaning and surface preparation easier with this Plastic Small Scraper Cleaning Tool, a versatile and durable tool designed for automotive film application and household cleaning tasks. Compact, lightweight, and easy to handle, this scraper is perfect for both professionals and DIY enthusiasts.

Key Features:

✅ Versatile &amp; Multipurpose Use
Ideal for paint removal, glue removal, glass cleaning, and scraping floors and tiles. This scraper is perfect for removing vinyl, decals, stickers, labels, grease, debris, and adhesive residue from glass, windows, walls, appliances, metal surfaces, cooktops, ovens, tiles, and more.

✅ Scratch-Proof &amp; Safe Design
Made from high-quality hot injection molded plastic, this windshield sticker remover performs like a metal scraper while reducing the risk of scratches and accidental injuries. Safe for use on delicate surfaces.

✅ Durable Construction
Built from premium-grade plastic for long-lasting performance. Strong enough for tough scraping jobs yet safe for everyday household and automotive use.

✅ Ergonomic &amp; Comfortable Grip
Features a curved ergonomic handle designed for maximum comfort and control. The thumb dent on the handle provides enhanced grip and precision, allowing you to complete tasks with minimal effort.

✅ Pocket-Sized &amp; Portable
Measuring approximately 3.93 inches in length and 1.49 inches in width, this lightweight mini scraper is easy to carry, store, and keep on hand for quick jobs at home, in the garage, or on the go.

✅ Easy to Use
Simple replacement system and lightweight design make this tool convenient for both professional detailers and DIY users.

📦 Product Details
Product Name: Plastic Small Scraper Cleaning Tool

Color: Blue

Size: 3.93 in (L) x 1.49 in (W)

Material: High-Quality Plastic

Packaging Includes: 1 × Scraper + 10 × Replacement</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RRMAAeSwEXNpppeB/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KegAAeSwYYxpppeB/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/P4sAAeSwdbZpppeB/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MNUAAeSwWatpppeB/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LrIAAeSwGa9pppeB/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/O5oAAeSweoZpppeB/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden DIY Tools &amp; Workshop Equipment Hand Tools Putty Knives &amp; Scrapers</category><ean>194343045245</ean><condition>New</condition><price>2.93</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045252</sku><product_name>Portable Lymphatic Contour Face Brush-New Lymphatic Drainage Face Brushs.</product_name><description>Enhance your skincare routine with this lymphatic face brush set. Designed for reducing puffiness, promoting lymphatic drainage, and contouring your facial features naturally. Ideal for daily use on all skin types.

⭐ Key Benefits
✔ Supports Lymphatic Drainage – Helps reduce swelling, promotes healthy blood circulation, and rejuvenates tired skin.
✔ Ergonomic Contour Design – Perfectly fits jawline, cheeks, and forehead for smooth, targeted facial massage.
✔ Ultra-Soft Bristles – Gentle on sensitive skin, suitable for daily use and all skin types.
✔ Lightweight &amp; Travel Friendly – Compact design fits easily in your purse or travel bag for on-the-go care.
✔ Durable &amp; Reusable – Made with high-quality materials for long-term use.
✔ Value Pack Set – Keep one at home and one for travel, ensuring consistent facial care anytime.
💆 Ideal For
Daily skincare routine
Facial massage &amp; contouring
Reducing puffiness &amp; facial tension
Use with cleanser, serum, or facial oil
📦 Package Includes
1 × Facial Contour Massage Brush Without Cover
1 x Facial Contour Massage Brush With Cover
2 × Facial Contour Massage Brushes Without Cover
2 x Facial Contour Massage Brushes With Cover</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1sQAAeSwCGppqAA0/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/B6wAAeSwwRlpqAA0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FKAAAeSwRzRpqAAz/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/D5YAAeSwOJBpqAAz/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/B5kAAeSw8AZpqAA0/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AcYAAeSwH1RpqAAz/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Massage Other Massage</category><ean>194343045252</ean><condition>New</condition><price>11.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045269</sku><product_name>4Pcs Bathroom Basin Sink Overflow Ring Chrome Hole Cover Cap Inserts Round |New</product_name><description>Upgrade your bathroom sink with these premium chrome basin overflow rings. Designed to fit most standard wash basin overflow holes, these durable plastic electroplated covers provide a clean, modern finish while helping prevent water overflow and maintaining proper drainage. Ideal for bathroom sinks, vanity basins, and washbasins in homes, hotels, or commercial spaces.



Key Features
Universal Fit: Suitable for most sink overflow holes with 22–24mm diameter, ensuring wide compatibility with standard bathroom basins.
Secure Clip Design: Built with a strong buckle structure for stable installation. The ring stays firmly in place and resists loosening after long-term use.
Quick &amp; Easy Installation: Replace old or broken overflow rings effortlessly. Simply remove the existing cover and insert the new ring for a perfect fit.
Smooth Chrome Finish: Polished electroplated surface provides a bright chrome appearance that enhances the look of your bathroom sink.
Practical Home Upgrade: Helps keep sinks tidy by covering overflow holes neatly while maintaining proper water drainage.

Product Specifications
Product Name	Sink Overflow Ring
Material	High Quality Plastic (PP)
Colour	Chrome Silver
Surface Process	Electroplated Finish
Compatible Hole Size	22mm – 24mm Basin Overflow Hole

Package Includes
4 × Bathroom Sink Overflow Rings</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1DYAAeSw6~tpqSrZ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Cf0AAeSwWK1pqSrY/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2uYAAeSwtCRpqSrb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yxQAAeSw4JZpqSrc/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5JkAAeSwKL1pqSrc/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/6-AAAeSwfK1pqSra/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Furniture &amp; DIY → Plumbing &amp; Fixtures → Other Plumbing &amp; Fixtures</category><ean>194343045269</ean><condition>New</condition><price>4.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045283</sku><product_name>Sliding Camera Lens Cover for Laptop, Phone, Tablet – Privacy Webcam Protector.</product_name><description>Protect your privacy with this sliding camera lens cover designed for laptops, mobile phones, tablets, and webcams. The ultra-thin design and smooth sliding mechanism make it easy to control when your camera is visible.


Product Features
✔ Instant Privacy Protection
Simply slide the camera cover to block your device camera when it is not in use. Slide it open whenever you need to use the camera.

✔ Ultra-Thin &amp; Lightweight Design
The slim profile allows your laptop lid to close properly without scratching or damaging the screen.

✔ Wide Compatibility
This camera lens cover works with most laptops, smartphones, tablets, and webcams, making it a versatile privacy solution.

✔ Strong Adhesive – No Residue
The durable adhesive keeps the cover securely attached and can be removed without leaving sticky marks.

✔ Quick &amp; Easy Installation
Just peel off the backing, align the cover over the camera lens, and press firmly. Installation only takes a few seconds.

✔ Durable Sliding Mechanism
Built with a smooth sliding design that allows easy open and close for everyday use.

✔ Multi-Pack Value
Multiple covers allow you to protect all your devices including laptops, phones, tablets, and webcams.

✔ Disclaimer
Product colours may vary slightly due to lighting and screen settings. Images are for illustration purposes only, and the actual item may vary slightly.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/SmoAAeSwJ9NpqVTP/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZGkAAeSwCTFpqVTP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TCAAAeSwFxxpqVTQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OacAAeSwmS5pqVTQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ULEAAeSwUjNpqVTP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZvwAAeSwtj1pqVTP/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Laptop &amp; Desktop Accessories Webcams</category><ean>194343045283</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.5</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045306</sku><product_name>1x REUSABLE SHOE BAG WASHING MACHINE CLEANING ZIPPER LAUNDRY BAG FOR SNEAKERS UK</product_name><description>Keep your trainers and sneakers clean effortlessly with our durable shoe washing machine bag. Designed for all types of shoes, it protects footwear while delivering a thorough wash.



Key Features:
Soft Chenille Lining: Cushions shoes during washing, protecting shape and fabric.
Durable Zipper: High-quality nylon zipper with elastic cover prevents accidental opening.
Noise Reduction: Soft padding reduces washing machine noise.
Easy to Use: Simply place shoes in the bag and machine wash. Saves time and effort!
Multi-Shoe Compatible: Trainers, sneakers, tennis shoes, casual shoes, and sports footwear.
Safe for Colours: High-quality materials prevent colour transfer; recommended to pre-wash once before first use.

Why Choose This Bag?
Whether you’re cleaning daily sneakers or your favourite trainers, this bag offers gentle yet effective cleaning while protecting both your shoes and washing machine. Perfect for anyone looking for a fast, convenient, and safe shoe cleaning solution.


Product Notes:
Colour may vary slightly due to lighting or screen display.
Size may differ by 0–2 cm (0–0.79 inches) due to manual measurement.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3LgAAeSw4-Npq9aa/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jQwAAeSwJHppq9aa/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2vcAAeSwbQhpq9aZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4lAAAeSwxONpq9aa/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qgoAAeSw0v1pq9aa/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i0YAAeSwC1Vpq9an/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Laundry Supplies Laundry Bags</category><ean>194343045306</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.59</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045337</sku><product_name>Microwave Anti Splatter Lid Cover Oven Transparent Plate Food Cover Home Kitchen</product_name><description>Keep your microwave clean and your food perfectly heated with this high-quality Microwave Splatter Guard Cover. Designed to prevent spills and splashes, this durable cover is an essential kitchen accessory for every home.

🔹 Key Features:
Mess-Free Heating:
Effectively prevents food splatters, keeping your microwave clean and odor-free.
BPA-Free &amp; Food Safe:
Made from high-quality, non-toxic plastic that is safe for everyday food use.
Built-in Steam Vent:
Allows steam to escape safely, preventing soggy food while ensuring even heating.
Transparent Design:
Crystal-clear cover lets you easily monitor your food while it cooks.
Easy to Use &amp; Clean:
Lightweight, easy to place and remove. Dishwasher</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dY0AAeSwkshprStW/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/SK0AAeSwDBBprStX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u5wAAeSwFJtprStX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KkIAAeSwAtNprStX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PXoAAeSwYs9prStW/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dcoAAeSwezhprStX/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Cookware, Dining &amp; Bar Kitchen Tools &amp; Gadgets Other Food Preparation &amp; To</category><ean>194343045337</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.83</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045344</sku><product_name>5X Magnifying Glass with Light Large Handheld Rectangular Magnifier for Reading*</product_name><description>Make reading easier with this large 5X magnifying glass. Its rectangular HD lens (7.3 × 4.4 inches) covers most pages, helping you read books, newspapers, magazines, maps, and documents clearly.



Key Features:

·         48 LEDs with 3 Modes: Choose cold, warm, or mixed light for comfortable reading anytime, day or night.

·         Portable &amp; Foldable Handle: Handle rotates 135° to hold the magnifier at the best angle. Lightweight (4.65 oz) easy to carry and perfect for long reading sessions.

·         Clear Lens: High-quality lens gives sharp, distortion-free view. Great for reading small print, crafts, stamps, coins or other hobbies. LEDs last over 100,000 hours.

·         Battery Powered: Needs 3 AAA batteries (not included) to light up the LEDs.



Package Includes:

·         1 × 5X Magnifying Glass

·         1 × User Manual

·         1 × Cleaning Cloth</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gr4AAeSwVktpN-SW/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OjoAAeSwQIRpN-SY/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RP8AAeSwFJJpN-SY/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wiAAAeSw5-ZpN-SX/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LnYAAeSwzxVpN-SW/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jswAAeSwtWZpN-SW/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Vision Care Special Purpose Glasses</category><ean>194343045344</ean><condition>New</condition><price>16.79</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045368</sku><product_name>High Pressure Air Drain Blaster Toilet Plunger Sink Kitchen Pipe Unblocker - UK</product_name><description>Remove stubborn drain blockages quickly with this powerful high pressure drain blaster. Designed for fast and effective unclogging, this reusable air plunger unblocker uses strong air compression to clear blocked toilets, sinks, showers, kitchen drains and pipe bends in minutes.

A must-have household cleaning tool, perfect for homes, flats, offices and rental properties. No need for harsh chemicals or expensive plumber call-outs.

Key Features
High Pressure Power: Delivers up to 80 PSI air pressure for fast drain cleaning
Quick Unblocking: Helps remove common clogs in approximately 2 minutes
4 Interchangeable Heads: Suitable for toilets, sinks, shower drains, bathroom outlets and U-bends
Reusable &amp; Eco Friendly: No chemicals, safe for regular household use
Comfort Grip Handle: Ergonomic trigger design for easy operation
Heavy Duty Build: Made from durable ABS plastic with strong rubber suction heads
Ideal For
Toilet blockages, clogged kitchen sinks, bathroom drains, shower waste pipes, utility room drains, wash basins and pipe bends.

Package Includes
1 x High Pressure Drain Blaster Plunger
4 x Replaceable Suction Heads
Product Specifications
Material: ABS Plastic &amp; Natural Rubber
Maximum Pressure: 80 PSI
Usage Time: Approx. 2 Minutes
Colour: As Shown
Suitable For: Toilet, Sink, Shower, Drain Pipes</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MZwAAeSw171p2zZI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/X0EAAeSwKuhp2zZF/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L4AAAeSw5Jpp2zZH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/l-MAAeSwWz1p2zZH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7pAAAeSwPZBp2zZF/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7VkAAeSwRxtp2zZH/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home, Furniture &amp; DIY → Bath → Toilets &amp; Bidets → Toilet Parts &amp; Accessories</category><ean>194343045368</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.69</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045399</sku><product_name>2-in-1 Oil Spray Bottle &amp; Dispenser Refilable BBQ Cooking Olive Oil Sprayer UK</product_name><description>Upgrade your cooking experience with this 2-in-1 refillable oil spray bottle, designed for modern kitchens and healthy cooking. This versatile 500ml oil sprayer and dispenser allows you to either spray a fine mist or pour oil smoothly, giving you better control when cooking, grilling, baking, or preparing salads. Perfect for olive oil, vegetable oil, vinegar, soy sauce, salad dressing and more, it helps reduce excess oil usage while keeping your kitchen clean and organised.


⭐ Key Features
✔ 2-in-1 Spray &amp; Pour Design – Easily switch between a fine oil mist or a controlled pour for cooking, roasting, grilling and salad dressing.
✔ Large 500ml Capacity – Generous size reduces frequent refilling and is ideal for daily kitchen use.
✔ Food-Grade Safe Materials – Made from durable BPA-free PP plastic with a silicone seal to ensure safety, durability and long-lasting performance.
✔ Leak-Proof &amp; Mess-Free – Ergonomic handle and precision nozzle help prevent spills while ensuring smooth and accurate oil distribution.
✔ Refillable &amp; Eco-Friendly – Wide bottle opening allows quick refilling without funnels. A sustainable alternative to disposable cooking oil spray cans.
✔ Multi-Purpose Kitchen Tool – Ideal for air fryers, BBQ grills, baking trays, salads, roasting vegetables, camping, picnics and everyday cooking.
✔ Healthy Oil Control – Delivers an even oil mist to help reduce oil consumption and support healthier meals.

📦 Product Specifications
Product Type: 2-in-1 Cooking Oil Sprayer &amp; Pour Dispenser
Capacity: 500ml / 16.9oz
Material: BPA-Free Food-Grade PP Plastic
Seal Material: Silicone
Colour: Clear Bottle with Spray Head
Package Includes: 1 × Refillable Oil Spray Bottle</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/HSwAAeSwO6xpsm4E/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vF4AAeSwiCBpsm4E/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/64EAAeSwAHNpsm4F/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/588AAeSw3RNpsm4H/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4uQAAeSwQ6Rpsm4F/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vG8AAeSwiCBpsm4G/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Cookware, Dining &amp; Bar Kitchen Tools &amp; Gadgets Other Food Preparation &amp; Tool</category><ean>194343045399</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045405</sku><product_name>Mobile Phone &amp; Laptop Camera Lens Cover For Privacy | Sliding Camera Protector</product_name><description>Protect your digital privacy with this ultra-thin sliding camera lens cover designed for laptops, smartphones, tablets, MacBooks, webcams and other smart devices. This compact webcam privacy cover prevents unwanted camera access while maintaining a clean and professional look for your device.

The smooth slide-open camera blocker allows you to easily cover or uncover your camera within seconds. Ideal for home, office, remote work, online meetings, or travel.

✔ Key Features
Universal Compatibility
Designed to fit most laptops, smartphones, tablets, webcams, MacBook, PC cameras and mobile devices. Slim design ensures it does not interfere with closing your laptop lid.

Strong Adhesive – No Residue
High-quality adhesive securely attaches to your device while allowing easy removal without leaving sticky marks or damage.

Quick &amp; Easy Installation
Simply peel the backing, align the cover over your camera lens and press gently. Installation takes only a few seconds.

Smooth Sliding Mechanism
Durable sliding design allows effortless open and close movement for everyday use, protecting your privacy whenever needed.

Multi-Pack Convenience
Available in multi-packs so you can protect multiple devices including phones, laptops, tablets and family devices.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tFcAAeSw59dps7lA/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vXMAAeSwyG9ps7qq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wxQAAeSwMA9ps7qp/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jIAAAeSwbQhps7qq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/K7EAAeSwk6Bps7qq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/pqkAAeSwBxdps7qr/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Laptop &amp; Desktop Accessories Webcams</category><ean>194343045405</ean><condition>New</condition><price>6.3</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045412</sku><product_name>10 Pairs Adhesive Nose Pads For Eyeglass | Anti-Slip Silicone Glasses Spectacle*</product_name><description>Make your glasses more comfortable and secure with these premium silicone adhesive nose pads. Designed for buyers looking for anti-slip nose pads for glasses, spectacles, sunglasses and reading glasses, these soft stick-on pads help stop frames from sliding down your nose.

Made from soft, skin-friendly silicone, these replacement nose pads provide extra grip and long-lasting comfort for everyday use. Perfect for replacing worn, damaged or missing nose pads on most eyewear frames.

Key Features
Soft Silicone Material – Comfortable for all-day wear
Anti-Slip Grip – Helps keep glasses securely in place
Self-Adhesive Backing – Easy peel and stick installation
Universal Fit – Suitable for most glasses and sunglasses
Durable &amp; Long Lasting – Strong adhesive and reliable use
Ideal for Slipping Glasses – Great for loose or uncomfortable frames
Specifications
Material	Soft Silicone
Colour	Clear / Black
Type	Self Adhesive / Stick On
Quantity	10 Pairs (20 Pieces)
Package Includes
✔ 10 Pairs Silicone Adhesive Nose Pads</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tZAAAeSweJZp3KBL/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fcEAAeSw8K9p3KBN/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xfIAAeSwhkpp3KBL/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G5wAAeSwJVdp3KBP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gAwAAeSwq55p3KBP/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RxYAAeSw5Ahp3KBP/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Vision Care Special Purpose Glasses</category><ean>194343045412</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.5</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045429</sku><product_name>Foldable Waterproof Travel Backpack Lightweight Rucksack Hiking Camping Bag 15L*</product_name><description>This Foldable Waterproof Travel Backpack is designed for modern travelers who value comfort, durability, and convenience. Whether you're heading for a weekend trip, hiking adventure, gym session, school, office, or business travel, this backpack is your perfect everyday companion.

Lightweight yet strong, it folds easily into a compact size, making it ideal for travel storage. Built with waterproof and tear-resistant material, it keeps your belongings safe in all weather conditions.

⭐ Key Features
Foldable Design: Easily packable and space-saving for travel convenience
Waterproof Protection: Keeps your essentials safe from rain and moisture
Ultra Lightweight: Comfortable to carry for long hours without strain
Large Capacity (Approx. 15L): Ideal for clothes, gadgets, books &amp; travel gear
Durable Build: Tear-resistant fabric for long-lasting use
Multi-Purpose: Perfect for travel, hiking, camping, sports, school &amp; office
💡 Why Choose This Backpack?
If you need a reliable, lightweight and compact travel bag that doesn’t compromise on space or durability, this backpack is the perfect choice. It is designed to give you freedom, comfort, and confidence on every journey.

📦 Specifications
Type	Foldable Backpack / Rucksack
Capacity	Approx. 15 Liters
Material	Waterproof &amp; Tear-Resistant Fabric
Usage	Travel, Hiking, Camping, School, Office, Sports</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iiQAAeSwmWZp3M5c/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/7j4AAeSw5Ahp3M5f/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LRUAAeSwC1Zp3M5g/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1lAAAeSw0Plp3M5e/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/8isAAeSwFd5p3M5d/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ShIAAeSwfLxp3M5e/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Camping &amp; Hiking Hiking Rucksacks &amp; Bags Rucksacks</category><ean>194343045429</ean><condition>New</condition><price>7.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045443</sku><product_name>Car Window Breaker Tool with Seatbelt Cutter Glass Breaker Under Water Hammer*</product_name><description>Be prepared for unexpected road emergencies with this compact and reliable car emergency escape tool. Designed for fast action in critical situations, this multi-function safety device helps you quickly break side car windows and cut jammed seat belts for a fast escape.

Featuring a spring-loaded impact mechanism and a durable tungsten steel striking tip, this tool is built to shatter tempered side windows with a single press. The built-in concealed blade allows quick seat belt cutting while keeping hands protected.

Its lightweight aluminium alloy body offers excellent durability, temperature resistance, and easy storage inside your car. Supplied with a holder base for convenient mounting on the dashboard or door pocket.

⭐ Key Features
Emergency Window Breaker: Powerful spring-loaded mechanism for quick glass breaking
Seat Belt Cutter: Hidden stainless steel blade for safe and fast belt cutting
Compact Design: Lightweight and easy to store in any vehicle
Durable Build: Strong aluminium alloy + ABS construction
Dashboard Holder Included: Easy access in emergencies
Ideal for Emergencies: Accidents, submerged vehicles, stuck seat belts
Safe Design: Protective cap and concealed blade to prevent accidental injury
🚗 Suitable For
Cars &amp; family vehicles
Taxis &amp; rideshare drivers
Vans, trucks &amp; buses
Travel emergency kits
Road safety preparedness
📏 Product Specifications
Product Type: Car Emergency Escape Tool
Material: Aluminium Alloy + ABS
Length: Approx. 93 mm
Diameter: Approx. 20 mm
Function: Window breaker + seat belt cutter
Mechanism: Spring-loaded impact system
Colour: Red / Black
Mounting: Holder base included
📦 Package Includes
1 × Car Emergency Window Breaker Tool
1 × Mounting Base</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tFQAAeSw5D5p3hy0/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/QOcAAeSwQ5pp3hy7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eykAAeSw24tp3hy3/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xJsAAeSwZLVp3hy7/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9D8AAeSwK4lp3hy1/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gDUAAeSwi0Vp3hy6/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Safety &amp; Security Accessories Safety Emergency Tools &amp; Tool Kits</category><ean>194343045443</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.89</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045450</sku><product_name>Mini Pocket Compact Folding Umbrella Rain &amp; Windproof Sun Anti UV 5 Travel Case</product_name><description>Mini Pocket Folding Umbrella with Carry Case – Compact &amp; Travel Friendly



Product Features

Compact folding umbrella designed for daily use

Sturdy rib structure to help maintain shape in windy conditions

Coated fabric designed to reduce sun exposure

Multi-layer fabric for added durability

Lightweight and easy to carry in a bag or backpack



Specifications

Available Colors: Beige, Light Blue, Pink, Purple, Dark Green, White, Black

Material: Fabric canopy with metal frame

Weight: Approx. 280g

 

Size:

Open: Approx. 50 × 88 cm

Folded: Approx. 17 × 4 cm



Package Includes:

1 × Folding Umbrella</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/utYAAeSwCQBpQP53/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/69oAAeSw4LBpQPqU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/m~4AAeSwi29pQPqS/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jRQAAeSwQzNpQPqU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AgkAAeSwk5NpQPqR/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9DkAAeSw46lpQPqT/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Accessories Umbrellas</category><ean>194343045450</ean><condition>New</condition><price>25.0</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045474</sku><product_name>10m Retractable Clothes Reel Double Washing Line Wall Mounted Indoor Outdoor UK</product_name><description>10M Retractable Double Clothes Line
Wall Mounted Outdoor &amp; Indoor Washing Line Reel | Space Saving Drying Solution

Upgrade your laundry space with this 10M Retractable Double Washing Line, designed for modern homes, flats, balconies, patios, and gardens. Perfect for indoor and outdoor drying, this wall-mounted clothes line offers a practical, durable, and space-saving solution for everyday laundry needs.

⭐ Key Features
10 Metre Double Line – Extra drying space for clothes, towels, bedding &amp; delicates
Retractable Design – Pull out when needed and retract neatly after use
Wall Mounted – Easy installation on walls, fences, posts or laundry room surfaces
Strong Locking System – Keeps lines secure, tight and prevents sagging
Weather Resistant – Suitable for UK outdoor weather conditions
Compact &amp; Space Saving – Ideal for small spaces and modern homes
📏 Product Specifications
Product Type	Retractable Clothes Line Reel
Line Length	10M Double Line
Mounting Type	Wall Mounted
Material	ABS Plastic Casing + Strong Cord
Use	Indoor / Outdoor
💡 Why Choose This Washing Line?
Perfect for balconies, patios, gardens and utility rooms
Helps reduce electricity costs by air drying clothes naturally
Prevents indoor dampness and moisture build-up
Great alternative to bulky traditional clothes lines
Ideal for daily family laundry use
🏡 Ideal For
Homes, flats, apartments, caravans, patios, gardens, laundry rooms, garages, student accommodation, and small outdoor spaces.

🚚 Fast UK Delivery
Quick dispatch • Secure packaging • Reliable UK shipping service</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5zMAAeSw-8pp4IBo/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Jz0AAeSwr0Np4IOQ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EqwAAeSwLfxp4IBo/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zyMAAeSwGgVp4IBo/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2z0AAeSwi0Vp4IBq/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Laundry Supplies Washing Lines</category><ean>194343045474</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.0</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045481</sku><product_name>4 Pcs Wall Mounted Electric Toothbrush Holder Traceless Bathroom Organizer Rack*</product_name><description>4 Pcs Wall Mounted Electric Toothbrush Holder – Traceless Bathroom Organizer Stand | Storage Rack | UK Stock
Keep your bathroom clean, hygienic, and clutter-free with this 4 Piece Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holder Set. Designed for modern homes, this space-saving bathroom organiser securely stores both electric toothbrushes and manual toothbrushes while freeing up valuable countertop space. Featuring a strong traceless adhesive backing, installation is quick and easy with no drilling, no tools, and no wall damage.

Ideal for family bathrooms, apartments, student accommodation, hotels, guest houses, and shared living spaces, this durable ABS plastic toothbrush stand offers hygienic ventilated storage that allows fast drying and improved airflow.

⭐ Key Features
Wall Mounted Space Saving Design – Keeps toothbrushes off the sink and bathroom counter for a neat and organised look.
Strong Traceless Adhesive – Easy peel-and-stick installation with no drilling required; removes cleanly without marks.
Fits Electric &amp; Manual Toothbrushes – Compatible with most electric toothbrush handles and standard toothbrushes.
Hygienic Ventilated Open Design – Promotes quick drying and better airflow to keep toothbrushes sanitary.
Waterproof &amp; Durable ABS Material – Moisture-resistant and ideal for humid bathroom conditions.
4 Piece Family Pack – Perfect for family members, shared households, and multiple users. Also available in 1 piece and 2 piece pack options to suit your needs
📊 Product Specifications
Product Type	Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holder
Quantity	Available in 1, 2 &amp; 4 Piece Options
Material	High Quality ABS Plastic
Installation	Traceless Adhesive / No Drilling
Mounting Type	Wall Mounted
Suitable For	Electric &amp; Manual Toothbrushes
Waterproof	Yes
✔ Benefits
Keeps bathroom countertops clean and tidy
Quick installation without drilling or tools
Improves hygiene with ventilated drying design
Perfect for small bathrooms and compact spaces
Long-lasting and waterproof for daily use
🏠 Ideal Uses
Perfect for home bathrooms, hotels, hostels, student dorms, rental properties, guest bathrooms, washrooms, shower areas, and vanity units. Can also be used for storing toothpaste tubes, razors, facial brushes, grooming tools, and dental accessories.

📦 Package Includes
1 × Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holder

2 × Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holders

4 × Wall Mounted Toothbrush Holders</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/epAAAeSwnKJp4Kht/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dwkAAeSwBb1p4Khs/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/liQAAeSwZK1p4Khs/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FT8AAeSwQ5pp4Khn/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KuUAAeSwuqdp4Khq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ASUAAeSwzRxp4Khp/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bath Bathroom Accessories Tumblers &amp; Toothbrush Holders</category><ean>194343045481</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.0</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045498</sku><product_name>Pillow Lap Stand Soft Phone Cushion For Laptop,Tablet &amp; IPad Multi-Angle Holder*</product_name><description>Make watching, reading and browsing more comfortable with this soft Tablet &amp; Mobile Phone Pillow Stand. Designed for use with popular devices including iPad, Samsung Galaxy Tab, Huawei MatePad and Xiaomi Mi Pad, this lightweight and supportive cushion holder keeps your screen at the perfect angle for hands-free use.

Ideal for home, office or travel, the soft sponge design rests comfortably on your lap, bed, sofa or desk while providing stable anti-slip support.




Features and further details

Product Name: Tablet Phone Pillow Stand

Brand: Unbranded

Size: See Images

Colours Available: Pink, Black, Wine Red, Grey, Blue, Green, Brown



Additional Key Feature
✔ Multi-Angle Viewing – Easily adjust to different angles for reading, streaming or video calls
✔ Soft &amp; Comfortable – Sponge pillow design for relaxed lap use
✔ Anti-Slip Stability – Secure support keeps your device in place
✔ Universal Compatibility – Suitable for most tablets and mobile phones
✔ Lightweight &amp; Portable – Easy to carry around the house or when travelling


Perfect For
Watching films &amp; Netflix in bed

Online learning &amp; Zoom calls

Reading eBooks

Cooking with recipes on screen

Gaming hands-free</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LMwAAeSwKBBpmBnc/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/K0cAAeSwYkNplC62/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4KAAAeSwK8BplDBp/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uNwAAeSwPNNplC63/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yAMAAeSwR2dplC62/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Electronics Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking Tablet &amp; eBook Reader Accs Mounts, Stands &amp; Holders</category><ean>194343045498</ean><condition>New</condition><price>18.0</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045504</sku><product_name>Nail Brushes for Cleaning Nails Nail Brushes Nailbrush Nail Scrubber | UK</product_name><description>Nail Cleaning Brush for Hands &amp; Fingernails – Scrub Brush Tool
Premium Plastic Nail Brush Set Keep your nails spotless and perfectly manicured with our high-quality hand scrubbing brushes. Designed for efficiency and comfort, these brushes are a must-have for every nail art lover and professional.
Product Highlights:
✨ Multi-Purpose: Perfect for scrubbing, cleaning dust, and removing residue after nail art or manicures.

🌈 Vibrant Mix: Comes in a beautiful assortment of 4 colors (Purple, Pink, Green, and Blue).

💪 Durable Build: Made from high-grade, sturdy plastic with soft yet effective bristles.

🧤 Ergonomic Design: Easy to grip, ensuring a deep clean without irritating your skin.

Product Specifications:
Item Type: Nail Art &amp; Hand Cleaning Brush

Material: Premium Durable Plastic

Colors: Mixed (Purple, Pink, Green, Blue)

Pack Sizes Available: 1pc / 3pcs / 10pcs / 15pcs &amp; Self Adhesive Hook is available

MAKE SURE TO CHECK THE SIZE SHOWN IN THE IMAGES BEFORE YOU BUY.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ztAAAeSw7ztp4yUX/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ypwAAeSwQOlp4yUX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uQ0AAeSwHpNp4yUZ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/uE4AAeSw9Nlp4yUa/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/niEAAeSwO6Vp4yUa/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hxgAAeSwNIpp4yW9/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Nail Care, Manicure &amp; Pedicure Nail Care Tools Manicure &amp; Pedicure Tools</category><ean>194343045504</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045535</sku><product_name>Bamboo Back Scratcher Wood Back Scraper Massager Body Itch Relief Tool UK Stock</product_name><description>Bamboo Back Scratcher Long Handle Wooden Massager Itch Relief Tool
Get quick and easy relief from hard-to-reach itches with this natural bamboo back scratcher. Crafted from strong, eco-friendly bamboo, it is lightweight, durable, and comfortable to hold.

Each piece is handmade, giving it a unique natural finish. The long handle helps you reach your back, shoulders, and other areas effortlessly—perfect for daily use or as a practical gift.

Features:

Natural bamboo – strong, durable &amp; eco-friendly

Long handle for easy reach

Lightweight and comfortable grip

Handmade with unique finish

Ideal for instant itch relief

Specifications:

Length: Approx. 42 cm (16.5”)

Head Width: Approx. 2.5 cm

Handle Width: Approx. 1.5 cm

Weight: Approx. 38 g

Package Includes:

1 x Bamboo Back Scratcher</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iLYAAeSwKhNpu5NE/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bKsAAeSwizVpu5NI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i~QAAeSwSF1pu5NH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Sp0AAeSwYC5pu5NI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TOAAAeSwqcZpu5NI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ii4AAeSwKsZpu5NG/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Massage Massagers</category><ean>194343045535</ean><condition>New</condition><price>3.08</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045559</sku><product_name>Tennis Trainer Training Practice Self-Study Rebound Balls Back Base Tool w/Ball*</product_name><description>🏆 Practice Tennis Anytime, Anywhere
This tennis trainer rebound set is designed for solo tennis practice, helping you improve your timing, coordination, and shot control without needing a partner. Ideal for use at home, garden, driveway, or training areas.

🎯 Key Benefits
✔ Helps improve shot consistency and accuracy
✔ Supports hand-eye coordination training
✔ Useful for practising forehand, backhand &amp; basic strokes
✔ Suitable for individual tennis training
✔ Can be used in small spaces
✅ Product Features
🎾 Rebound Ball with Elastic Rope – Ball returns after each hit
💎 Durable Base – Made from strong ABS material
⚖️ Fillable Base – Can be filled with water or sand for stability
🧳 Portable Design – Easy to carry and store
👌 Integrated Handle – Convenient for transport
🎯 Where &amp; How to Use
🏡 Home, garden, backyard or driveway practice
🏫 Schools, sports clubs, and training sessions
🎾 Solo practice without a partner
👨‍👩‍👧 Suitable for both adults and children
📋 Product Specifications
Material: ABS Plastic
Base Size: Approx. 21 × 21 × 5 cm
Rope Length: Approx. 4 meters
Colour: May vary
🛠️ How to Use
Fill the base with water or sand
Attach the tennis ball using the rope
Hit the ball gently and continue practice
📦 Package Includes
1 x Tennis Trainer Base
1 x Tennis Ball with Rope</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/P2MAAeSwy6tp5K~w/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/SN8AAeSwKE5p5K~y/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Jv8AAeSwsABp5K~x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YnkAAeSwBxxp5K~y/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ZpAAAeSwsL5p5K~x/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Sporting Goods Tennis Training Aids</category><ean>194343045559</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.09</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045566</sku><product_name>Double-Sided Nail Brush for Manicure &amp; Pedicure–Small Cleaning &amp; Scrubbing TooL</product_name><description>Double-Sided Nail Brush – Manicure &amp; Pedicure Cleaning Tool
Maintain clean, fresh, and healthy nails effortlessly with this premium double-sided nail cleaning brush. Perfect for daily grooming, this versatile manicure and pedicure tool helps remove dirt, oil, and buildup from nails while being gentle on the skin.

Designed for both home users and professionals, this compact nail brush combines functionality, comfort, and durability in one convenient grooming accessory.

Key Features
Dual-Sided Design: Equipped with two brush heads for multiple cleaning needs.
Firm Bristles: Ideal for deep cleaning under nails and removing stubborn dirt.
Soft Bristles: Gentle on skin and suitable for delicate nail surfaces.
Ergonomic Grip: Comfortable to hold for better control during use.
Compact &amp; Portable: Easy to carry in bags, making it travel-friendly.
Benefits
Keeps fingernails and toenails hygienic and well-maintained
Supports healthy nail care routines
Suitable for use with soap, hand wash, or nail treatments
Perfect for personal grooming or salon use
Ideal For
This nail cleaning brush is perfect for:

Manicure and pedicure routines
Professional nail technicians
Everyday personal hygiene
Travel grooming kits
Package Includes
1 × Double-Sided Nail Brush
Upgrade your nail care routine with this simple yet effective grooming tool designed to keep your nails looking neat, clean, and healthy every day.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/keIAAeSwnc1pvOZg/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/lAsAAeSwhJFpvOZe/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/kjcAAeSwSeZpvOZf/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/in4AAeSw~U5pvOZf/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fYkAAeSwhlRpvOZd/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Nail Care, Manicure &amp; Pedicure Nail Care Tools Manicure &amp; Pedicure Tools</category><ean>194343045566</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.0</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045580</sku><product_name>4-Pack Heavy-Duty Bedsheet Corner Clips – Durable Sheet Grippers for Secure Fit*</product_name><description>4 Pack Heavy Duty Bed Sheet Corner Clips – Adjustable Mattress Sheet Fasteners Grippers Straps UK
Keep your bed looking perfectly neat every night with these heavy duty bed sheet corner clips. Designed for maximum hold, these adjustable mattress sheet grippers prevent slipping, bunching, and wrinkling – giving you a smooth, hotel-quality finish.

🔥 Key Features
✔ 4 Pack Bed Sheet Straps – Complete set for all corners
✔ Heavy Duty Elastic Bands – Strong stretch for firm grip
✔ Metal Clip Fasteners – Durable clamps hold sheets securely
✔ Adjustable Length Design – Fits single, double, king &amp; super king beds
✔ Anti-Slip Sheet Holder – Keeps sheets tight all night
✔ No More Wrinkles – Smooth, tidy, hotel-style bedding
💡 Why Choose These Sheet Grippers?
These bed sheet fasteners UK are perfect for keeping your fitted sheets, flat sheets, mattress toppers, and protectors in place. The strong elastic straps combined with sturdy clips ensure your bedding stays tight even if you move during sleep.

✔ Ideal for deep mattresses &amp; thick toppers
✔ Great for restless sleepers
✔ Perfect for kids beds &amp; everyday use
✔ Suitable for home, hotels, guest rooms
📦 What’s Included
✔ 4 x Adjustable Bed Sheet Corner Clips
(Only items shown are included. No additional accessories.


⭐Upgrade Your Sleep With Perfectly Fitted Sheets - No Slipping,No Wrinkles Just Comfort. ⭐

Product Image</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zu8AAeSwDPJp5xMv/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sIMAAeSwyRppmAq2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3WcAAeSwR2dpmAq2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oGkAAeSwpCVpmAq1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vdUAAeSwn5JpmAq3/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oecAAeSwIyhpmAq2/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bedding Bedding Accessories</category><ean>194343045580</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.0</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045610</sku><product_name>Mens Running Shorts Quick-Drying Fitness Black Double Layer Gym Shorts Men Sport</product_name><description>Men’s Running Shorts Quick Dry Gym Fitness Double Layer Sports Shorts Black
Upgrade your workout gear with these men’s quick-dry running shorts, designed for maximum comfort, performance, and style. Perfect for gym training, running, jogging, fitness workouts, CrossFit, HIIT, and outdoor sports, these lightweight double layer sports shorts keep you cool and supported during every session.

🔥 Key Features:
✅ Quick-Drying Fabric: Moisture-wicking polyester keeps sweat away – ideal for intense workouts
✅ Double Layer Design: Inner compression layer offers support, coverage, and comfort
✅ Lightweight &amp; Breathable: Stay cool during running, gym sessions, and summer training
✅ Elastic Waistband Fit: True-to-size athletic fit for unrestricted movement
✅ Classic Black Sports Shorts: Stylish, versatile, and perfect for everyday wear
📏 Size Chart: 👉 Kindly check the detailed size chart provided in the description before purchasing.
Size (cm)	Waist	Hip	Inside Length	Side Length	Height (cm)	Weight (kg)
S	68	106	34.5	31	165-170	55-60
M	72	110	35.5	32	170-175	60-70
L	76	114	36.5	33	175-180	70-80
XL	80	118	37.5	34	180-185	80-90
XXL	84	122	38.5	35	185-190	90-100
NOTE: Please strictly follow the size chart to choose. Do not select according to your habit.
Size chart may have 1–3 cm difference due to manual measurement.
Height and weight are for reference only.

📋 Product Specifications:
Department: Men
Item Type: Running Shorts / Gym Shorts
Sport Type: Running, Fitness, Training, Gym
Material: Polyester
Pattern: Solid Black
Fit: True to Size
Style: Double Layer Athletic Shorts
Condition: New
🏃 Perfect For:
Running &amp; Jogging Shorts for Men
Gym &amp; Fitness Training Shorts
CrossFit &amp; HIIT Workouts
Football, Cycling &amp; Outdoor Sports
Casual Sportswear &amp; Activewear
💪 Why Choose These Men’s Sports Shorts?
These men’s athletic running shorts combine breathability, flexibility, and support to help you perform at your best. Whether you're lifting weights, going for a run, or training outdoors, these quick-dry gym shorts for men ensure maximum comfort with a modern sporty look.

👉 Add these high-performance men’s gym shorts to your wardrobe today and train in comfort &amp; style!</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WU0AAeSwh5Vp51Fw/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ogwAAeSwNBlp501S/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NRYAAeSwrURp501S/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ve4AAeSwnLZp501R/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/riMAAeSw6SNp501R/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/UDsAAeSwqBdp501R/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Men Men's Clothing Shorts</category><ean>194343045610</ean><condition>New</condition><price>19.0</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045634</sku><product_name>4D Cloud Sports Insoles Breathable Shock Absorbing Cushioned Shoe Inserts Pads</product_name><description>4D Cloud Technology Insoles – Premium Comfort &amp; Shock Absorption
Experience enhanced everyday comfort with these 4D Cloud Technology Insoles, engineered to provide soft cushioning, improved foot support, and all-day comfort. Designed for a wide range of footwear, these insoles help reduce pressure on feet during walking, running, standing, and daily activities.

✨ Key Features
4D Cloud Cushioning: High-quality PU material delivers soft, responsive comfort for daily wear
Shock Absorbing Design: Helps reduce impact on heels, feet, and joints during movement
Breathable &amp; Lightweight: Designed to help maintain airflow and reduce moisture build-up
Foot Support Comfort: Provides added stability and helps reduce foot fatigue during long use
Trim-to-Fit Flexibility: Easily cut to size for a customised and secure fit
👟 Ideal For
Running, jogging, and sports activities
Work shoes &amp; long hours of standing
Daily casual footwear use
People seeking improved foot comfort and reduced fatigue
📏 Product Details
Material: Durable PU (Polyurethane)
Technology: 4D Cloud Comfort System
Size: Adjustable / Trim to Fit Most Shoe Sizes
Gender: Unisex Design
📦 Package Includes
1 Pair (2 Insoles)

⚠️ Important Information
Insoles may require trimming for perfect fit
Slight size variation may occur due to manual cutting
This product is designed for comfort and support use in everyday footwear</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/HcEAAeSwVnNp6GcI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/J1YAAeSwpHBp6GcM/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/J1YAAeSwpHBp6GcM/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MEEAAeSw8oNp6GcL/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WJ4AAeSwCmBp6GcL/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WUgAAeSwBxxp6G2i/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>breadcrumb Health &amp; Beauty Medical &amp; Mobility Orthopaedics &amp; Supports Insoles &amp; Shoe Inserts</category><ean>194343045634</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045658</sku><product_name>Sports Wristbands Sweat Bands Gym Tennis Wrist Sweatbands 2Pcs Black 8×10cm UK</product_name><description>8×10CM Sports Wristbands Sweat Bands Tennis Gym Wrist Sweatbands Basketball Volleyball Padel Fitness Wrist Wrap UK
Keep sweat out of your eyes and off your game!

These premium sports wristbands are made from thick, absorbent terry cloth to keep your hands dry and improve grip during intense workouts and matches. Perfect for gym training, tennis, padel, running and all fitness activities.

✔ Key Benefits
Maximum Sweat Absorption – Thick towel fabric quickly soaks up sweat
Better Grip &amp; Performance – Keeps hands dry for improved control
Comfortable Stretch Fit – מתאים most wrist sizes (men &amp; women)
Secure &amp; Non-Slip – Stays in place during intense workouts
Reusable &amp; Washable – Durable for long-term use
✔ Product Details
Size: 8cm x 10cm
Material: Soft Terry Cloth Cotton Blend
Quantity: Pack of 2 Wrist Sweatbands
Colour: (Add your colour here)
✔ Perfect For
Tennis, Squash &amp; Badminton
Basketball &amp; Volleyball
Padel &amp; Racket Sports
Gym, CrossFit &amp; Weightlifting
Running, Cycling &amp; Fitness Training
✔ Why Buy From Us?
Fast UK Dispatch 🚚
High Quality Sweatbands
Trusted Seller
100% Satisfaction Guarantee</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Qe0AAeSwl6Zp6J5N/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RUAAAeSwn8tp6J5N/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OcgAAeSwDe5p6J5O/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TMoAAeSwCbZp6J5O/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aJwAAeSwUg1p6J5O/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TW4AAeSwO6Vp6J5N/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure Fitness, Running &amp; Yoga Fitness Clothing &amp; Accessories Sweatbands</category><ean>194343045658</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.0</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045665</sku><product_name>4D Sport Insoles Shock Absorbing Arch Support Comfort EVA Foam Shoe Inserts Pads</product_name><description>Premium Shock Absorbing Sport Insoles Shoe Pads – Ultimate Arch Support Comfort
Upgrade your footwear with these high-performance EVA foam insoles, designed for maximum comfort, shock absorption, and foot support. Perfect for running, walking, sports, work boots, and everyday use.


⭐ Key Features:
Advanced Shock Absorption: Reduces impact on feet, knees, and joints – ideal for running and long standing hours
Orthotic Style Arch Support: Helps improve posture and reduces foot fatigue
Breathable &amp; Odour Control: Keeps feet fresh, dry, and comfortable all day
Ultra Soft Cushioning: Provides superior comfort for daily wear
Trim to Fit Design: Easily cut to your exact shoe size
Unisex Fit: Suitable for both men and women

👟 Perfect For:
Running &amp; Sports Shoes
Trainers &amp; Sneakers
Work Boots &amp; Safety Shoes
Casual &amp; Leather Shoes
Standing Jobs &amp; Daily Walking

📦 Product Details:
Material: High-Density EVA Foam &amp; Bamboo fiber
Colour: Green
Size: EU 41–46 (Fits UK 7–12, Trimmable)
Condition: 100% Brand New
Package Includes: 1 Pair of Insoles

⚡ Benefits:
Shock absorbing insoles for running and sports
Comfort insoles for work boots and long standing
Orthotic insoles for foot pain relief
Breathable insoles with deodorising function</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5vUAAeSwkuZp6FH7/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/m~cAAeSw6SNp6FH7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u-wAAeSweFVp6FH8/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OawAAeSw7LFp6FH8/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/GAIAAeSwnSNp6FH8/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4aYAAeSwLSlp6FH8/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Medical &amp; Mobility Orthopaedics &amp; Supports Insoles &amp; Shoe Inserts</category><ean>194343045665</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.0</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045672</sku><product_name>Height Increase Insoles Men Women Invisible Heel Lift Taller Shoe Insert Pads/UK</product_name><description>Height Increase Insoles Men Women | Invisible Heel Lift Taller Shoe Insert Pads
Height Increase Insoles Men Women Invisible Heel Lift Air Cushion Shoe Inserts Adjustable Height Boost Shoe Lift Pads Cut to Fit Foot Support
Boost your height instantly and confidently with these adjustable height increase insoles. Designed for both men and women, these invisible heel lift shoe inserts provide extra height while staying completely hidden inside your shoes.

🔹 Key Features
Adjustable Height Boost: 4-layer design allows height increase from approx. 3cm to 9cm (1.18" – 3.54").
Invisible Design: Completely hidden inside shoes – perfect for everyday wear.
Air Cushion Support: Built-in air cushion helps absorb shock and improve comfort while walking.
Cut-to-Size Fit: (EU 225–270 / US approx. 5–9).Easily trim to your exact size using the guide lines on the insoles. Completely invisible when worn inside shoes.
Unisex Use: Suitable for both men and women – fits most trainers, boots, and casual shoes.
🔹 Product Details
Material: EVA &amp; Fiber (lightweight, flexible, durable)
Colour: Black
Gender: Unisex
Size Range: EU 225–270 (Adjustable &amp; Cuttable)
Condition: Brand New
Package Includes: 1 Pair of Height Increase Insoles
🔹 Why Choose These Height Increase Insoles?
These invisible height boosting insoles are perfect for anyone looking to appear taller instantly without discomfort. The multi-layer system lets you customise your height, while the air cushion base provides better shock absorption for daily walking or standing.

Ideal for use in trainers, boots, and everyday footwear. A simple and effective way to enhance your look and confidence.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PWMAAeSwK8Np6ePU/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-8EAAeSwcIBp6edN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XCkAAeSw7LZp6ePX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FGwAAeSwTU5p6ePV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dm8AAeSwrWdp6ePX/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Medical &amp; Mobility Orthopaedics &amp; Supports Insoles &amp; Shoe Inserts</category><ean>194343045672</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045689</sku><product_name>Motorcycle Helmet Rack Wall Mount Holder Hook Stand Helmet Holder,Jackets Hanger</product_name><description>Motorcycle Helmet Wall Hook – Heavy Duty ABS Wall Mounted Helmet Holder
Keep your helmet protected, organised and safely off the floor with this durable Motorcycle Helmet Wall Hook. Designed for UK homes, garages and workplaces, this sturdy wall-mounted holder helps you maximise space while preventing scratches, dents and unnecessary wear.

😤 Struggling With Helmet Clutter?
Helmets rolling around on the floor
Taking up shelf or cupboard space
Scratches and accidental impact damage
Trip hazards in hallways or entrances
Untidy garage or storage areas
This space-saving wall hook provides a simple and secure storage solution in minutes.

✅ Key Features &amp; Benefits
Wall-Mounted Design – Frees up valuable floor and shelf space
Helmet Protection – Keeps helmets safely elevated to reduce damage
Strong &amp; Stable – Dual fixing points help prevent movement or rotation
Multi-Purpose Use – Suitable for helmets, jackets, gloves, and riding gear
Perfect for UK Riders – Ideal for commuters, motorcyclists and scooter owners
💪 Durable Build Quality
Material: High-density reinforced ABS plastic
Structure: Rigid, heavy-duty construction designed for long-term use
Fixings: Rust-resistant stainless steel screws included
Mounting: Dual screw fixing for enhanced stability
Finish: Smooth, wipe-clean surface
Built to perform reliably in UK garages, sheds, flats and indoor environments.

🏠 Ideal Installation Locations
Hallway / Entrance: Convenient grab-and-go storage
Garage / Workshop: Keeps helmets away from damp or dirty surfaces
Bedroom / Study: Clean, organised display storage
Office / Workplace: Professional and secure helmet storage
🔧 Quick &amp; Easy Installation (Approx. 5 Minutes)
Mark your desired wall position
Drill pilot holes if required
Insert wall plugs (for brick or concrete)
Align hook and tighten screws securely
Test with a light load before full use
Requires only a basic drill or screwdriver.

📦 What’s Included
1 × ABS Motorcycle Helmet Wall Hook
2 × Stainless Steel Screws
📐 Product Specifications
Material	High-Density Reinforced ABS Plastic
Mount Type	Wall Mounted
Fixing Method	Screw-In Installation
Suitable For	Motorcycle Helmets, Jackets, Gloves, Bags
Cleaning	Wipe Clean with Damp Cloth
Screws	Stainless Steel (Included)
🚚 UK Shipping &amp; Customer Service
Fast UK Dispatch</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/OLwAAeSwExhpnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RZwAAeSwNBBpnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ehgAAeSwIY9pnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/QXEAAeSwxmFpnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ctAAAeSwWW9pnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/dVUAAeSwQxNpnWoJ/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Clothing, Protective Gear &amp; Merchandise Helmets &amp; Accessories Motorcycle &amp; Motorsports Helm</category><ean>194343045689</ean><condition>New</condition><price>3.79</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045696</sku><product_name>2 Pack Satin Silk Pillowcase For Hair &amp; Skin Pillow Cases Cover Bedding Pair ~UK</product_name><description>Satin Pillowcases Pack of 1 &amp; 2 – Soft, Cooling &amp; Hair Friendly ✨
Luxury Sleep • Smooth Finish • Gentle on Hair &amp; Skin

🛏️ Upgrade Your Sleep Comfort
Experience the comfort of premium satin pillowcases UK designed to provide a smooth, soft and breathable sleeping surface. Ideal for everyday use, these satin pillow covers help create a more आरामदायक and relaxing sleep environment.

🌟 Key Features
✔️ Hair Friendly Fabric – Helps reduce friction, which may minimise frizz and hair breakage
✔️ Skin Gentle Surface – Designed to help reduce sleep creases and support healthier-looking skin
✔️ Cooling &amp; Breathable – Lightweight satin helps keep you cool and comfortable
✔️ Soft &amp; Smooth Texture – Enjoy a silky, luxurious feel every night
✔️ Easy Care – Machine washable and quick drying for convenience
💎 Why Choose Satin?
Compared to cotton, satin pillowcases for hair and skin are less absorbent and help maintain natural moisture. This can support smoother hair and a more refreshed appearance.

📦 Product Details
Set Includes: 1/ 2 x Satin Pillowcases
Size: Standard UK (Approx. 50 x 75 cm)
Material: Satin Silk
Colour: Multiple options available
Available in: 1 Pack | 2 Pack"
🚚 Delivery Information
✔️ Fast &amp; reliable UK shipping
✔️ Secure packaging

💯 Customer Satisfaction
We aim to provide high-quality products and excellent service. If you are not satisfied, we offer an easy return process for your peace of mind.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eb0AAeSwzGVp6zpD/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VbMAAeSwisJp6zpC/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2Y0AAeSwBeNp6zpD/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tasAAeSwCy1p6zpE/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bedding Pillow Cases</category><ean>194343045696</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045702</sku><product_name>2 Pack Satin Silk Pillowcase For Hair &amp; Skin Luxury Soft Pillow Cases Covers |UK</product_name><description>Pack of 2 Satin Pillowcases – Luxury Soft Silk Feel Pillow Covers
Upgrade Your Sleep with Premium Satin Pillowcases for Hair &amp; Skin Care

✨ Key Features
✔ Silky Smooth Satin Fabric – Soft, breathable &amp; luxurious feel
✔ Hair Protection – Helps reduce frizz, tangles &amp; breakage
✔ Skin Friendly – Gentle on sensitive skin, helps reduce irritation
✔ Hypoallergenic Material – Ideal for all skin types
✔ Cool &amp; Comfortable – Perfect for a restful night's sleep
✔ Durable &amp; Easy Care – Long-lasting quality satin
📦 Product Details
Product Type	Satin Pillowcases (Silk Feel)
Quantity	Pack of 2 Pillow Cases
Material	High Quality Satin
Size	Approx 51 x 66 cm
Condition	Brand New
Brand
Unbranded
🎨 Available Colours
Black,  Grey, White, Rose Red, Pink, Green, Gold, Blue

💖 Benefits for Hair &amp; Skin
Our satin pillowcases are designed to provide a luxury sleep experience while helping maintain healthy hair and glowing skin. The smooth surface reduces friction, preventing hair breakage, split ends, and frizz. It also helps your skin retain moisture, reducing sleep lines and irritation.

🚚 Delivery &amp; Returns
🚚 Shipping: Free UK Mainland Delivery
💯 Guarantee: 100% Money Back Guarantee
🔄 Returns: Hassle-free returns accepted</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LMkAAeSwwelp60ns/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G1IAAeSwPmNp60nt/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LMkAAeSwwelp60ns/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Bedding Pillow Cases</category><ean>194343045702</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045733</sku><product_name>Portable Zipper Eye Glasses Sunglasses Hard Case Box Protector Large Hold | Gift</product_name><description>Glasses Box Sunglasses Case | Hard Shell Eyeglass Case with Zipper &amp; Hook
Protect your eyewear in style with this durable hard shell glasses case. Designed for everyday use, travel, and outdoor activities, this portable sunglasses case keeps your glasses safe from damage while offering convenience and modern style.


Key Features:
Durable EVA Hard Shell: Provides strong protection against drops, pressure, dust, and scratches. Ideal for protecting your sunglasses, reading glasses, and prescription eyewear.
Soft Interior Lining: Gentle inner lining prevents scratches and keeps lenses clean and mark-free.
Secure Zipper Closure: High-quality, smooth zipper ensures your glasses stay fully protected and secure at all times.
Carabiner Hook Included: Easily attach the case to backpacks, handbags, belts, or travel bags – perfect for travel, hiking, cycling, and outdoor use.
Lightweight &amp; Portable: Compact and easy to carry, making it perfect for daily use, school, office, holidays, and sports.
Fits Most Glasses: Suitable for men’s, women’s, and kids’ eyewear including sunglasses, reading glasses, blue light glasses, and more.
Stylish Colourful Design: Modern and vibrant colours to match your style.
Upgraded Model: Enhanced durability with stronger shell, improved zipper, and better overall comfort.

Why Choose This Eyeglass Case?
This protective glasses storage box is designed for maximum durability and convenience. Whether you're commuting, travelling, or enjoying outdoor activities, this hard sunglasses case with clip ensures your eyewear stays safe and easily accessible.


Package Includes:
1 Pc Portable Zipper Sunglasses Case. 
1 Pc Portable Sunglasses Cloth Bag is also available in variations — you can purchase it separately according to your requirement.

Warm Tips:
We are committed to providing the best product and customer service. If you have any issues, please contact us and we will resolve them as soon as possible.
Due to differences in monitor settings and lighting, actual colours may vary slightly from images.
Please allow a small margin of error in size due to manual measurement.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iZsAAeSwi69p7J5P/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/25IAAeSwZK1p7J5O/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/BKIAAeSwisJp7J5Q/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JOYAAeSwwSZp7J5P/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YmsAAeSw~F1p7J5O/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Health &amp; Beauty Vision Care Glasses Cases &amp; Storage</category><ean>194343045733</ean><condition>New</condition><price>8.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045757</sku><product_name>UK Motorcycle Helmet Rack Wall Mount Holder Hook Stand Helmet &amp; Jacket Hanger</product_name><description>Product Features:
Versatile Wall-Mounted Design: Perfect for motorcycle helmets, electric bicycle helmets, jackets, keys, and more. Dual-purpose design for helmet and key storage.
Premium ABS Material: Made from high-quality ABS nylon material with non-slip surface texture, strong durability, excellent toughness, and high strength.
Easy Installation: Simple drill-and-screw installation method. Utilizes wall space efficiently for better organization.
Space-Saving Solution: Ideal for home, garage, kitchen cabinet shelf, office, or showroom display. Keeps your space neat and organized.
Perfect for Electric Bicycle Helmets: Specially designed to securely hold e-bike helmets while maintaining shape and stability.
Product Specifications:
Material: Premium ABS + Nylon
Color: Black
Size: 150 x 72 mm
Installation Type: Wall Mount (Drill Installation)
Installation Method:
Select and mark the installation position.
Drill holes according to expansion tube spacing.
Insert the expansion tube into the drilled hole.
Ensure expansion tube is properly fixed inside.
Align the hook and tighten screws.
Installation complete.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yx4AAeSwlCRpqUTX/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gxQAAeSwBC5pn~n1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i2MAAeSwTi5pn~n1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mC0AAeSwYJFpn~n1/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Motors Clothing, Protective Gear &amp; Merchandise Helmets &amp; Accessories Motorcycle &amp; Motorsports H</category><ean>194343045757</ean><condition>New</condition><price>14.0</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045771</sku><product_name>2x Electrostatic Pet Hair Removal Gloves Brush | New Double-sided Grooming Glove</product_name><description>2-in-1 Electrostatic Pet Grooming &amp; Hair Removal Glove
Dog &amp; Cat Deshedding Mitt | Reusable Pet Fur Remover | Furniture Cleaner

Keep your pet’s coat healthy and your home fur-free! 🐾

This practical double-sided pet grooming glove helps lift loose fur, dust and dander while giving your cat or dog a relaxing massage. Designed with electrostatic fabric, it effectively attracts pet hair from coats, sofas, carpets, car seats and clothing.

✨ Why Choose This Grooming Glove?
✔ Dual-Action Design – One side gently grooms, the other removes trapped hair
✔ Electrostatic Technology – Helps attract and hold loose fur efficiently
✔ Soft &amp; Breathable Mesh – Comfortable fit for extended use
✔ Flexible One Size – Suitable for most hand sizes
✔ Multi-Surface Use – Ideal for pets and household fabrics
✔ Reusable &amp; Easy to Clean – Simply remove collected hair after use
📏 Product Details
Item Type	Pet Grooming Mitt / Hair Removal Glove
Colour	Black &amp; Yellow
Dimensions	Approx. 20cm x 15cm (7.9" x 5.9")
Material	Mesh Fabric &amp; Static Brush Cloth
Package Contents	1 x Pet Hair Removal Glove
🐶 Ideal For
Dog Grooming UK | Cat Grooming Brush | Pet Deshedding Tool | Pet Hair Remover for Sofa | Reusable Fur Cleaning Mitt | Puppy &amp; Kitten Grooming Accessory | Car Seat Hair Remover | Household Fabric Fur Cleaner</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/m5YAAeSwW1BpoWdV/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/i9wAAeSw0VBpoWdU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/m6oAAeSw5rppoWdU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/e2UAAeSwAg9poWdU/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jCcAAeSwrr9poWdT/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/m3wAAeSwebRpoWdV/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Dog Supplies Grooming Brushes, Combs &amp; Rakes</category><ean>194343045771</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.59</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045790</sku><product_name>Women Long Hair Luxury Satin Bonnet Night Sleep Hat Cap Silk Head Wrap Turban~UK</product_name><description>Adjustable Satin Silk Hair Bonnet For Women– Luxury Sleep Cap for Hair Protection
Upgrade your nighttime hair care routine with this premium adjustable satin silk bonnet, designed to protect your hair while you sleep. Perfect for curly hair, natural hair, braids, wigs, and long hairstyles, this soft and breathable sleep cap helps reduce frizz, tangling, and breakage.

🌙 Key Features
Adjustable Tie Band: Secure, customizable fit for all head sizes – stays in place all night.
Premium Satin Material: Smooth polyester satin reduces friction and locks in moisture.
Frizz &amp; Breakage Protection: Prevents split ends and keeps hairstyles intact.
Elegant Bow Design: Stylish look suitable for sleeping, lounging, or daily wear.
Lightweight &amp; Breathable: Comfortable for summer nights and all-season use.
Unisex &amp; Versatile: Ideal for women, men, and kids.
💆‍♀️ Benefits of Using a Satin Bonnet
This silk satin sleep cap is essential for maintaining healthy hair. Unlike cotton, satin helps retain natural oils, keeping your hair hydrated and smooth. It’s perfect for preserving curls, braids, blowouts, and protective styles.

🎯 Perfect For
Overnight hair protection
Curly, wavy, and textured hair care
Braided and protective hairstyles
Hair care routines and beauty treatments
Travel and home use
📦 Package Includes
1 x Adjustable Satin Silk Hair Bonnet 

📏 Product Specifications
Material: High-quality polyester satin
Size: One size fits most (stretchable &amp; adjustable)
Color: Multicolour (random selection)
Design: Tie strap with stylish bow
💡 Why Choose This Satin Sleep Bonnet?
✔ Keeps hair smooth, shiny, and tangle-free
✔ Reduces hair damage and moisture loss
✔ Comfortable for all-night wear
✔ Stylish, practical, and travel-friendly
✔ Ideal gift for hair care lovers</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2EsAAeSwAFFp72h2/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oxIAAeSwoJhp72h0/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/aQwAAeSw4ABp72h4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JNgAAeSw129p72h4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2EsAAeSwAFFp72h2/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Fashion Women Women's Accessories Hats</category><ean>194343045790</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.0</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>194343045739</sku><product_name>Silicone Bottle Cleaning Brush with Long Handle Flexible 360° Cup Flask Cleaner</product_name><description>360° Foldable Silicone Bottle Cleaning Brush – Long Handle Reusable Cup &amp; Glass Cleaner
Make everyday cleaning simple and effective with this 360° silicone bottle cleaning brush. Designed with a flexible foldable head and extended ergonomic handle, this reusable brush reaches deep inside bottles, flasks and narrow cups to remove residue with ease. A must-have kitchen cleaning tool for homes across the UK.

⭐ Key Features
360° All-Around Cleaning: Flexible silicone bristles reach every angle, corner and inner wall for a thorough clean.
Foldable Brush Head: Adapts to different bottle shapes and sizes for improved contact and deeper cleaning.
Long Ergonomic Handle: Effortlessly reaches the bottom of tall water bottles, travel mugs and slim containers.
Food-Grade Silicone: Safe, durable and gentle on glassware – scratch-resistant and odour-free.
Reusable &amp; Easy to Maintain: Simply rinse after use, quick drying design for long-lasting hygiene.
Multi-Purpose Use: Ideal for baby bottles, sports bottles, glass cups, flasks, tumblers and kitchen containers.
📦 Product Specifications
Material: Food-Grade Silicone + Durable Handle
Brush Design: 360° Flexible Foldable Head
Cleaning Type: Comprehensive Internal Bottle Cleaning
Reusable: Yes
Suitable For: Water Bottles, Baby Bottles, Glassware, Cups, Flasks &amp; Travel Mugs
Upgrade your kitchen cleaning routine with this practical long handle silicone bottle brush. Perfect for daily household use, keeping your reusable bottles and glassware fresh, hygienic and spotless.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/-9EAAeSwPRtpoo6w/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xuoAAeSwvHtpoo6x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/J14AAeSwcblpoo6w/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Nz8AAeSweyppoo6x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ld0AAeSwbcRpoo6w/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wvwAAeSwKOBpoo6w/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden Household &amp; Laundry Supplies Cleaning Tools Cleaning Brushes</category><ean>194343045739</ean><condition>New</condition><price>3.15</price><quantity>4</quantity></product></products>