<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><product_name>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair) Walnut</product_name><description>Key features:

    WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
    Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
    Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
    Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
    Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity

5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included


            
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mGUAAeSwTFBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/zN4AAeSw61hp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUwAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y7wAAeSwajBp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vQ8AAeSwhIJp1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Wharfedale</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9505837913481</ean><condition>New</condition><price>180.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><product_name>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</product_name><description>50‚Ä≥ Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

    50‚ÄĚ 4K Ultra HD LED TV
    LG‚Äôs Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
    Download apps through the web browser
    Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
    Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
    Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
    3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
    Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)


The built-in Smart platform, developed by LG, allows you to browse the web and download all your favourite entertainment apps, so you can stream directly to the TV. From Netflix, Prime Video and Disney Plus to YouTube and catch-up apps like BBC iPlayer and ITVx, a world of entertainment awaits.

With Freeview Play you can watch an impressive 60,000+ hours of TV and over 1,500 boxsets, across your favourite on-demand players. All for free.

With the built-in Bluetooth connectivity, you can add a Bluetooth soundbar to the TV. This means cinema sound can be enjoyed without the need for untidy cables. The built-in satellite tuner with Freesat provides access to over 170 channels with 100% channel coverage on a subscription-free basis. Plus, you‚Äôll find your favourite on-demand players all in one place. You will just need to purchase and install your own satellite dish/cabling. The ultimate flat-screen TV with its super-slim bezel and lightweight design is ideal for wall mounting and easy maneuverability


Specification
Screen Size         50‚Ä≥
Freeview Play         Yes
DVD Player         No
USB         Yes ‚Äď playback only
Contrast Ratio         5000:1
Brightness         250
Max Resolution         3840 x 2160
Speakers         2 x 8W
Smart         Yes
Max Power         120W
Energy Rating         ‚ÄėG ‚Äď 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI         3
Inputs         RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs         Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA         200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand         W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand         W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight         9.1kg</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qawAAeSwShFppWtV/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ztwAAOSwG3dm9EMH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/EqAAAOSwNORlaIbE/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/ISQAAOSwsINlaIbX/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/wfEAAOSw~FVlaIXe/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Cello</brand><category>Televisions</category><ean>9503723485349</ean><condition>New</condition><price>462.99</price><quantity>7</quantity></product><product><sku>5058048349204</sku><product_name>Coffee Machine Espresso Machine Coffee Maker Cappuccino Milk Frother 20 Bar 1.8L</product_name><description>‚úÖ 20Bar High-Pressure Extraction
Equipped with a professional high-pressure water pump, it delivers a stable 20Bar extraction pressure to instantly penetrate coffee grounds, fully releasing the aroma and oils of coffee beans. It easily  restoring the rich flavor of authentic espresso‚ÄĒevery sip rivals the quality of specialty caf√© drinks.
‚úÖ 1.8L Large-Capacity Removable Water Tank
No need for frequent refills; a full tank can make multiple cups for the whole family, easily handling daily use and small gatherings. The semi-transparent design lets you check water levels at a glance, and the detachable structure, paired with a separate drip tray, makes refilling and cleaning a breeze‚ÄĒsaving time and effort.
‚úÖ Food-Grade Stainless Steel Manufacturing
The body and core contact parts are made of food-grade stainless steel, which is corrosion-resistant, high-temperature resistant, and durable. It eliminates residual odors, ensuring every cup of coffee is pure and safe, balancing premium texture with practicality.
ūüõ†ÔłŹ All-Inclusive Accessories ¬∑ Unlock Diverse Coffee Experiences
The machine comes with a complete set of professional accessories, so you can start your home barista journey right out of the box. It balances professionalism and convenience to suit 
‚ėē Scenario Adaptation ¬∑ Perfect for Your Daily Moments
ūüĆÖ Morning Wake-Up: One-tap espresso, paired with milk for an energizing latte to chase away drowsiness and kickstart a productive day.
‚ėē Afternoon Relaxation: Brew a cup of freshly ground coffee with dessert, enjoying a moment of peaceful solitude and elevating your at-home ritual.
ūü•ā Friend Gatherings: Quick double-cup brewing and a variety of milk-based drinks let you host a cozy coffee party at home.
ūüíľ Office Energy Boost: Fast capsule brewing eliminates waiting time, providing timely energy to enhance work efficiency.
ūüďĆ Product Specifications
Extraction Pressure: 20Bar high-pressure extraction
Water Tank Capacity: 1.8L large-capacity removable water tank</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IJsAAeSwtj1pr-Co/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gDIAAeSwv5Npr-Cq/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/A7sAAeSwprxpr-Cr/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/E3sAAeSwfLxpr-Ct/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DMAAAeSwV8lpr-Cu/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FdYAAeSwC0Jpr-Cv/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Coffee Machines</category><ean>9505129206453</ean><condition>New</condition><price>97.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><product_name>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</product_name><description>About this item
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźPortable and Magical„ÄĎ-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„Äź5 Hrs Battery Life„ÄĎ-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźProtective and Gorgeous Screen„ÄĎ-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kids‚Äô eyes.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźAll Regions &amp; Multi Formats„ÄĎ-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CD¬ĪR/¬ĪRW,DVD¬ĪR/¬ĪRW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźDual Speakers &amp; Clear Sound„ÄĎ-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźEasy Operation &amp; Seamless Viewing„ÄĎ-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß„ÄźPremium Service &amp; Quick Response„ÄĎ-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

‚ėÖEye-protection LCD screen‚ėÖ: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
‚ėÖSuper High Battery‚ėÖ: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
‚ėÖResume Play‚ėÖ: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
‚ėÖGame Player‚ėÖ: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
‚ėÖMulti-Media‚ėÖ: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270¬į rotation and 180¬į flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~aoAAeSw2Rtpzi5w/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eDcAAeSwjStpzi5x/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AfoAAeSwXZ5pzi5z/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hOUAAeSwdJ9pzi51/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JmMAAeSwz5hpzi53/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>DVD Players</category><ean>9502946361596</ean><condition>New</condition><price>65.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>9501234567891</sku><product_name>2 Packs 6AH For Makita 18V Battery Li-Ion BL1830 BL1850 BL1840 BL1860B LXT400</product_name><description>Product Description


Features:

1. New and in a good condition.
2. Made of durable and reliable material, harmless to your health.
3. It is easy to use, convenient to carry with.
4. The best replacement for the old or damaged one.
5. A great assistant for electric tools.
6. Provide convenience to charge your electric tool anytime and anywhere.
7. It is suitable for Makita BL1815, BL1830, BL1835, LXT400, 194204-5, 194205-3, 194309-1.

Specifications:
Chemistry: Li-ion
Brand: For Makita
Model No.: BL1830
Condition: Brand new
Sub-Type: Replacement Battery
Voltage (V): 18V
Capacity: 6000mAh
Color: Black

 

Replace Original Makita Battery Code:

for MAKITA

194205-3, 194309-1, BL1815, BL1830, BL1840, LXT400

 

Fit Original Makita Model:

for MAKITA

for Makita BDF453SHE, for Makita BDF454Z, for Makita BHP452

for Makita BML184, for Makita BML185,

for Makita BST221Z, for Makita BTDW251Z, for Makita ML185, for Makita TD140D, for Makita TW251D

for Makita BCS550 Series:BCS550, BCS550Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BDA350, BDA350Z,

for Makita BDF451 Series:BDF451, BDF451Z,

for Makita BFR550 Series:BFR550L, BFR550Z,

for Makita BFR750 Series:BFR750, BFR750L, BFR750Z,

for Makita BFS450 Series:BFS450, BFS450RFE, BFS450Z,

for Makita BGA452 Series:BGA452, BGA452Z,

for Makita BHP451 Series:BHP451, BHP451SFE, BHP451Z,

for Makita BHP453 Series:BHP453, BHP453SHE,

for Makita BHP454 Series:BHP454, BHP454Z,

for Makita BHR202 Series:BHR202, BHR202RFE, BHR202Z,

for Makita BHR240 Series:BHR240, BHR240Z,

for Makita BHR241 Series:BHR241, BHR241Z,

for Makita BJR181 Series:BJR181, BJR181X, BJR181X1,BJR181Z,

for Makita BJR182 Series:BJR182, BJR182X, BJR182Z,

for Makita BJS130 Series:BJS130, BJS130Z,

for Makita BJV180 Series:BJV180, BJV180Z,

for Makita BPB180 Series:BPB180, BPB180Z,

for Makita BSS501 Series:BSS501, BSS501Z,

for Makita BSS610 Series:BSS610, BSS610SFE, BSS610X2,BSS610Z,

for Makita BSS611 Series:BSS611X, BSS611Z,

for Makita BTD140 Series:BTD140, BTD140SFE, BTD140Z,

for Makita BTD141 SeriesBTD141, BTD141Z,

for Makita BTD144 Series:BTD144, BTD144RFE, BTD144Z,

for Makita BTL061 Series:BTL061, BTL061Z,

for Makita BTL063 Series:BTL063, BTL063Z,

for Makita BTP140 Series:BTP140, BTP140Z,

for Makita BTW251 Series:BTW251, BTW251Z,

for Makita BTW253 Series:BTW253, BTW253Z,

for Makita BTW450 Series:BTW450, BTW450Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BUB182, BUB182Z,

for Makita BVR350 Series:BVR350, BVR350Z,

for Makita BVR450 Series:BVR450, BVR450Z,

for Makita BVR850 Series:BVR850, BVR850Z,

for Makita DF454 Series:DF454D, DF454DRFX, DF454DZ,

for Makita HP454 Series:HP454D, HP454DRFX, HP454DZ,

for Makita HR202 Series:HR202D, HR202DRFX, HR202DZK,

for Makita JR120 Series:JR120D, JR120DRF, JR120DZK,

for Makita ML184 Series:ML184(FlashLight), ML184,

for Makita MR100 Series:MR100, MR100W,

for Makita PB108 Series:PB108D, PB108DRFX, PB108DZ,

for Makita TD144 Series:TD144DRFX, TD144DZ,

for Makita TD251 Series:TD251DRFX, TD251DZ


Package Includes:
2 x 6000mAh Batter</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u6MAAeSwuXxorCS3/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/mSMAAeSwlBZorCS4/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L5AAAeSwJR5orCS5/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/40UAAeSw~YporCS7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/xAgAAeSwOV5orCS7/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/krIAAeSwHEtorCS-/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Power Tool Accessories</category><ean>9503120424496</ean><condition>New</condition><price>31.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092475</sku><product_name>Bluetooth FM Transmitter Car Kit MP3 Player USB Charger Handsfree Adapter UK</product_name><description>Upgrade your driving experience with this multifunctional Car Charger Bluetooth adapter. Combining hands-free calling, music streaming, and rapid charging, it‚Äôs the perfect companion for every journey. Designed with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology, it delivers high-speed charging while keeping your devices connected safely.


‚≠ź Key Features
Bluetooth 5.0 Connectivity: Stable, fast pairing with smartphones for calls, music, and navigation audio.
FM Transmitter Function: Stream your favorite playlists directly to your car stereo via FM radio.
Dual USB Fast Charging Ports: Supports rapid charging for multiple devices simultaneously.
MP3 Player Support: Play music from USB drives or SD cards effortlessly.
Hands-Free Calling: Clear audio with built-in microphone ensures safe driving.
Compact &amp; Universal Design: Fits all standard car cigarette lighter sockets and works with most vehicles.

ūüďä Technical Specs
Bluetooth Version: 5.0
Input: DC 12-24V
Output: 5V/2.4A per USB port
Frequency Range: 87.5‚Äď108MHz
Compatible Formats: MP3/WMA/WAV
LED Display: Shows FM frequency and device info

ūüí° Benefits
Charge your phone and other devices quickly with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology.
Enjoy seamless music streaming without tangled wires.
Stay safe with hands-free calling while driving.
Compact design keeps your dashboard neat and organized.

ūüéĮ Ideal For
Daily commuters who need fast device charging and music on the go.
Road trips and long drives requiring hands-free calls and entertainment.
Anyone who wants to upgrade an older car stereo to Bluetooth functionality.
Drivers with multiple devices needing simultaneous fast charging.

ūüĆź Vast Applications
Cars, SUVs, trucks, and other vehicles with cigarette lighter sockets.
Listening to music or podcasts from smartphones, USB drives, or SD cards.
Hands-free calls during work commutes, rideshare driving, or family trips.
Charging smartphones, tablets, GPS devices, power banks, and other USB devices.
Enhancing older car stereos with FM broadcasting and Bluetooth connectivity.</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2FkAAeSwnNZpbks~/s-l960.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/4QAAAeSwYPtpbktl/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/v18AAeSw40tpbkth/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1jgAAeSwTb5pbks9/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qZ0AAeSwLmtpbktK/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Mx8AAeSwGJ5pbktO/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9506451246540</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097401</sku><product_name>Mini Pocket Umbrella Folding Compact Rain Windproof Anti UV 5 Folding Travel UK</product_name><description>Stay protected in every season with this sleek and ultra-portable Mini Pocket Compact Fold Umbrella. Designed for modern lifestyles, it combines Rain Windproof durability with Anti UV protection, making it the perfect everyday travel essential.


‚≠ź Key Features
ūüĆß Rain Windproof Design ‚Äď Strong frame for reliable performance in wind &amp; rain
‚ėÄÔłŹ Anti UV Protection ‚Äď Helps block harmful sun rays on hot days
ūüĎú Ultra Compact &amp; Pocket Size ‚Äď Easy to carry anywhere, anytime
‚ö° Quick Open &amp; Fold ‚Äď Simple, hassle-free operation
ūüéí Travel Case Included ‚Äď Clean and convenient storage
ūüí™ Durable Build ‚Äď Premium materials for long-term use

ūüďŹ Technical Specifications
Type: 5-Fold Compact Umbrella
Material: Waterproof Fabric + Reinforced Metal Frame
Function: Rainproof, Windproof, Anti UV
Folded Size: Approx. 15‚Äď18 cm
Open Diameter: Approx. 90‚Äď95 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Included: Protective Travel Case

ūüĆć Ideal For
ūüĆß Rainy Days ‚Äď Stay dry during sudden showers
‚ėÄÔłŹ Super Sunny Days ‚Äď Reliable shade with Anti UV protection
ūüćā Autumn &amp; Winter ‚Äď Handles wet and windy conditions
ūüĆł Spring Showers ‚Äď Perfect for unpredictable weather
ūüĆě Summer Heat ‚Äď Use as a portable sunshade
ūüĆ¶ All-Season Use ‚Äď One umbrella for every condition

ūüĒĄ Vast Application of Usage
Designed to make your life easier, this umbrella is perfect for:

ūüö∂ Daily Use ‚Äď Commuting, school runs, office travel
ūüõć Shopping Trips ‚Äď Stay comfortable while out and about
‚úąÔłŹ Travel &amp; Holidays ‚Äď Compact size fits easily in luggage
ūüöó On-the-Go Protection ‚Äď Keep in your car or bag for emergencies
ūüéČ Outdoor Events ‚Äď Festivals, sports days, gatherings
ūüŹē Outdoor Activities ‚Äď Walking, hiking, camping
ūüĎ®‚ÄćūüĎ©‚ÄćūüĎß For Everyone ‚Äď Suitable for men, women, and kids
ūüĎČ No confusion, no hassle ‚ÄĒ one simple solution for all your weather needs


ūüéĮ Why Choose This Umbrella?
‚úĒ Dual-purpose Rain Windproof &amp; Anti UV protection
‚úĒ Compact, lightweight, and easy to carry
‚úĒ Reliable in all weather conditions
‚úĒ Practical design for everyday convenience

ūüöÄ Benefits You‚Äôll Love
Stay dry and protected anytime, anywhere
Enjoy peace of mind with all-in-one weather protection
Carry effortlessly without bulk
Dependable performance you can trust</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U-oAAeSwf8Fp43cb/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/XGwAAeSwv5dp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YaQAAeSw8Zdp43cb/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/eIUAAeSwzmBp43ca/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/NRgAAeSwo41p43cZ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fYwAAeSwpHRp43ca/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9508011803422</ean><condition>New</condition><price>18.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097418</sku><product_name>Bike Seat Cover Soft Gel Saddle Bicycle Padded Cushioned Extra Comfort UK</product_name><description>Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover Padded Cushion Saddle ‚Äď Universal Fit for Maximum Comfort ūüöī
Upgrade your cycling experience with this premium Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover, designed to deliver exceptional Padded Comfort on every ride. Whether commuting, exercising, or riding long distances, enjoy a smoother, pain-free journey.

‚≠ź Key Features
Soft Gel Padding ‚Äď Advanced cushioning absorbs shock and reduces pressure
Padded Comfort Design ‚Äď Extra-thick padding for long rides
Secure Anti-Slip Fit ‚Äď Non-slip base with adjustable drawstring
Breathable Design ‚Äď Airflow channel reduces heat and moisture
Water-Resistant ‚Äď Protects from sweat and light rain
Universal Fit ‚Äď Fits most standard bike saddles
ūüíé Premium Quality &amp; Material
High-grade soft gel with high-density memory foam
Premium Lycra fabric ‚Äď breathable and stretchable
Reinforced stitching for durability
Anti-slip textured base for stability
Maintains shape after long-term use
ūüďź Technical Specifications
Material: Soft Gel + High-Density Foam + Lycra Fabric
Size: Approx. 27.5 x 17 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Compatibility: Fits most bike saddles
Installation: Easy slip-on with drawstring
ūüéĮ Ideal For
Daily commuters and city cyclists
Long-distance and endurance riders
Indoor cycling and spin classes
Mountain and road biking
Beginners needing extra comfort
ūüĆć Vast Applications
Road bikes ‚Äď long-distance comfort
Mountain bikes ‚Äď shock absorption
City bikes ‚Äď daily commuting
Exercise bikes ‚Äď home workouts
Hybrid bikes ‚Äď mixed terrain
Leisure cycling ‚Äď casual rides
Travel &amp; touring ‚Äď portable comfort
‚úÖ Benefits
Ride longer without discomfort
Reduces pressure on sensitive areas
Improves performance and endurance
Quick installation ‚Äď no tools needed</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/r~QAAeSwYytp4Och/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/gOoAAeSweFVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WMIAAeSwcSpp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/MF0AAeSw2rlp4Oci/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/M7MAAeSwDeVp4Och/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Ob0AAeSwFbNp4Oci/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9507281117582</ean><condition>New</condition><price>9.99</price><quantity>3</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097500</sku><product_name>Anti Mosquito Insect &amp; Bug Repellent Bracelet Bands Silicone Wristband 1- 20 PK</product_name><description>‚≠ź Key Features
Effective Mosquito Protection ‚Äď Helps repel mosquitoes and insects naturally
Safe &amp; DEET-Free ‚Äď Infused with natural plant-based essential oils
Adjustable &amp; Flexible Fit ‚Äď Comfortable silicone design for adults and children
Long-Lasting Use ‚Äď Provides extended protection for hours
Portable &amp; Easy ‚Äď Wear on wrist, ankle, or attach anywhere
Multiple Colors ‚Äď Fun and vibrant options
Value Packs ‚Äď Available in 1‚Äď20 PCS options
ūüďä Technical Specifications
Material: High-quality silicone
Active Ingredients: Natural essential oils (citronella, eucalyptus, etc.)
Size: One-size-fits-most (adjustable)
Usage Time: Several hours per band (varies by environment)
Application: Wrist, ankle, bags, strollers
Pack Options: 1, 5, 10, 15, or 20 pieces
‚úÖ Benefits
No sprays, no skin irritation, no mess
Family-friendly for kids and adults
Lightweight, waterproof, and travel-ready
Great alternative to traditional repellents
ūüéĮ Ideal For
Camping, hiking, fishing, and outdoor adventures
Travel, holidays, and picnics
Gardening, BBQs, and sports activities
Everyday use at home or school
ūüĆć Vast Applications of Usage
Outdoor: camping, trekking, cycling, beach trips
Home &amp; garden: backyard, lawn work, evening relaxation
Kids: school, playgrounds, daycare
Travel: airports, hotels, tropical destinations
Work: fishing, farming, construction, warehouses
Pet walks: parks, trails, wooded areas
Daily use: shopping, commuting, casual outings
ūüöö Free Shipping
Fast &amp; reliable delivery
Secure packaging for safe arrival
No extra charges</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jS0AAeSwJyRp2OwQ/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/tpgAAeSw1rlp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/3rAAAeSwFh9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AyQAAeSwe5tp2OwQ/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/qOsAAeSwF7Vp2OwR/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1ZcAAeSw2L9p2OwR/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9507022871471</ean><condition>New</condition><price>13.99</price><quantity>2</quantity></product><product><sku>404834097517</sku><product_name>Juicer Lemon Squeezer Citrus Juice Hand Held Stainless Steel Fruit Orange</product_name><description>Key Features
Perfect Squeeze Technology ‚Äď Extracts maximum juice with minimal effort
Durable Stainless Steel Build ‚Äď Rust-resistant and long-lasting
Ergonomic Handle Design ‚Äď Comfortable grip for easy squeezing
No Seeds, No Mess ‚Äď Built-in filter keeps juice smooth
Easy to Clean ‚Äď Dishwasher safe and quick rinse cleaning
Used for Variety of Fruits ‚Äď Ideal for lemons, limes, and small oranges
ūüďź Technical Specifications
Material: Premium Stainless Steel
Type: Handheld Manual Juicer
Color: Silver
Size: Compact &amp; portable
Weight: Lightweight yet durable
Cleaning: Dishwasher safe
ūüí° Benefits
Saves time compared to manual squeezing
Extracts more juice with less waste
Keeps hands clean and irritation-free
Ideal for home, bars, and restaurants
Compact for easy storage and travel
ūüéĮ What It Is Ideal For
Making fresh lemon and lime juice
Preparing cocktails and refreshing drinks
Adding flavor to salads, marinades, and dishes
Baking desserts and pastries
Daily kitchen and professional use
ūüĆć Vast Applications of Usage
Beverages ‚Äď lemon water, smoothies, iced tea
Cooking ‚Äď seafood, chicken, sauces, vegetables
Salads ‚Äď fresh citrus dressings
Baking ‚Äď cakes, tarts, desserts
Bar use ‚Äď cocktails like margaritas &amp; mojitos
Natural cleaning ‚Äď eco-friendly lemon solutions
DIY beauty ‚Äď skincare and hair remedies
Outdoor use ‚Äď picnics, camping, travel</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bLYAAeSweM9p34ep/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1dQAAeSwJk1p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/hMsAAeSwtV5p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/cB0AAeSweFVp34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/w4UAAeSw9G5p34eq/s-l960.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/fAMAAeSwcE5p34eq/s-l960.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9507518788036</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>4048340975905</sku><product_name>EMERGENCY HAMMER CAR WINDOW BREAKER SEATBELT CUTTER BREAK GLASS ESCAPE SAFETY UK</product_name><description>EMERGENCY HAMMER Car Window Breaker &amp; Seatbelt Cutter ‚Äď Essential Vehicle Escape Safety Tool (UK Stock)

Be fully prepared for unexpected emergencies with this high‚ÄĎquality EMERGENCY HAMMER featuring a WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER. Designed for rapid response, this compact yet durable tool can make a critical difference when seconds matter.


‚≠ź Key Features
‚úĒ 2-in-1 Emergency Design ‚Äď Heavy-duty window breaker &amp; seatbelt cutter in one compact tool
‚úĒ Hardened Steel Hammer Head ‚Äď Instantly shatters side windows in emergency situations
‚úĒ Sharp Concealed Blade ‚Äď Quickly cuts jammed or locked seatbelts
‚úĒ Non-Slip Anti-Skid Handle ‚Äď Firm grip for safe and controlled use
‚úĒ High-Visibility Red Body ‚Äď Easy to locate in stressful situations
‚úĒ Protective Mounting Bracket ‚Äď Secure and convenient storage within reach
‚úĒ Compact &amp; Lightweight ‚Äď Fits glove box, door pocket, or centre console

ūüĒß Technical Specifications
Material: High-carbon hardened steel hammer head
Handle: Durable ABS with anti-slip grip
Blade: Stainless steel concealed safety blade
Length: Approx. 17cm
Weight: Approx. 130‚Äď150g
Colour: Red
Condition: Brand New
Stock Location: UK

ūüĆć Vast Application of Usage
This EMERGENCY HAMMER is suitable for a wide range of vehicles and emergency situations:

ūüöó Private cars &amp; family vehicles
ūüöē Taxis, Uber &amp; ride-share vehicles
ūüöö Vans, trucks &amp; delivery fleets
ūüöĆ Buses &amp; minibuses
ūüöź Motorhomes &amp; caravans
ūüöď Emergency &amp; service vehicles
ūüö§ Boats &amp; marine vehicles
ūüŹĘ Workplace fleet vehicles
ūüéí Travel safety kits &amp; roadside emergency kits
Perfect for emergencies involving:

Vehicle submersion in water
Electrical or central locking failure
Car fires
Severe collisions
Jammed doors after impact

ūüõ° Key Benefits
‚úĒ Enables fast escape when doors cannot be opened
‚úĒ Cuts seatbelts instantly to prevent entrapment
‚úĒ Provides peace of mind for drivers and passengers
‚úĒ A small investment for potentially life-saving protection

ūüď¶ Package Includes
1 √ó EMERGENCY HAMMER
1 √ó Mounting Bracket</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VkAAAeSw8Udp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rFoAAeSwxGxp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rJwAAeSwJQ1p0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/CcEAAeSw7mhp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vb4AAeSwAVRp0Pz1/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/T8EAAeSwQHtp0Pz2/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9501531055567</ean><condition>New</condition><price>5.99</price><quantity>4</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092499</sku><product_name>Strong Vacuum Suction Cup Hook Shower Towel-Holder Hooks for Bathroom Kitchen UK</product_name><description>ūüĒ• PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Organise your space easily with these Vacuum Suction Cup Hooks, designed to provide a strong hold without drilling or damaging your walls. Made from premium 304 stainless steel, these hooks are perfect for bathrooms, kitchens, and home organisation.

With powerful suction grip and a modern design, they securely hold towels, bags, and accessories on smooth surfaces while keeping your space neat and clutter-free.

‚≠ź KEY FEATURES
‚úÖ No Drilling Required ‚Äď Easy installation without tools or wall damage
‚úÖ Strong Suction Power ‚Äď Holds up to approx. 15 lbs (6.8 kg)
‚úÖ Waterproof &amp; Rustproof ‚Äď Ideal for bathroom and kitchen use
‚úÖ Durable Stainless Steel ‚Äď Corrosion-resistant and long-lasting
‚úÖ Modern Design ‚Äď Matches any home d√©cor style
‚úÖ Reusable &amp; Removable ‚Äď Easy to reposition without marks
‚úÖ Anti-Slip Hook ‚Äď Secure grip for hanging items safely
ūüďč PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Suction Cup Hook
Material	304 Stainless Steel
Installation	Vacuum Suction (No Drill)
Load Capacity	Up to 15 lbs (approx.)
Colour Options	Silver, Black, Gold, White
Use	Bathroom, Kitchen, Home Organisation
ūüéĮ IDEAL FOR
‚úĒ Towels &amp; bath accessories
‚úĒ Kitchen utensils
‚úĒ Handbags &amp; keys
‚úĒ Clothes &amp; hats
‚úĒ Shower accessories
ūüď¶ PACKAGE OPTIONS
‚úĒ 1 √ó Hook
‚úĒ 2 √ó Hooks (Value Pack)
‚ö†ÔłŹ INSTALLATION TIPS
Suitable for smooth surfaces only (tiles, glass, metal, wood)
Not suitable for painted or rough walls
Press firmly and wait 24 hours before use
ūüĒ• MULTI-BUY OFFERS
ūüíį Buy More Save More
ūüíį Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AH0AAeSwhHJp3luF/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/LO0AAeSwQOlp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/sWwAAeSwYOtp3luH/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VpwAAeSw7T5p3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/KxoAAeSwKuRp3luG/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/foQAAeSwibJp3luG/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9508228050809</ean><condition>New</condition><price>22.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092505</sku><product_name>Mens Body Shaper Compression Vest Slimming Shirt Tank Chest Belly Men's Waist UK</product_name><description>ūüĒ• PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a more confident look instantly with this Men‚Äôs Slimming Compression Vest, designed to shape your chest, flatten your stomach, and support better posture. Made from a breathable stretch fabric, this vest provides firm compression while remaining comfortable for all-day wear.

Perfect for daily wear, gym workouts, or under clothing for a slimmer appearance. Lightweight, flexible, and discreet under shirts for everyday confidence.

‚≠ź KEY FEATURES
‚úÖ Instant Slimming Effect ‚Äď Flattens belly and shapes chest
‚úÖ Compression Fit Design ‚Äď Supports posture and core
‚úÖ Breathable Fabric ‚Äď Comfortable for all-day wear
‚úÖ Seamless Under Clothing ‚Äď Invisible under shirts
‚úÖ High Elastic Material ‚Äď Flexible body-contouring fit
‚úÖ Lightweight &amp; Comfortable ‚Äď Ideal for daily or sports use
‚úÖ Multi-Purpose Wear ‚Äď Gym, running, work, or casual wear
ūüďč PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Men‚Äôs Compression Vest / Body Shaper
Material	Polyester
Fabric Type	Breathable Stretch
Style	Sleeveless Vest
Fit	Slim Compression Fit
Colours	Black, White
Sizes	M, L, XL, XXL
Pattern	Solid
Care	Machine Washable
Condition	New 
ūüďĆ SIZE TIP
Choose one size up for a more comfortable fit.

ūüéĮ IDEAL FOR
‚úĒ Daily wear under shirts
‚úĒ Gym &amp; fitness training
‚úĒ Running, cycling, workouts
‚úĒ Body shaping &amp; posture support
‚úĒ Confidence boosting appearance
ūüď¶ PACKAGE INCLUDES
‚úĒ 1 √ó Men‚Äôs Compression Vest
ūüĒ• MULTI-BUY OFFERS
ūüíį Buy More Save More
ūüíį Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rCoAAeSwmlFp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/1hUAAeSwT05p4QUL/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jHwAAeSweM9p4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FWcAAeSwvsRp4QUN/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/iPwAAeSwLqJp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/TP0AAeSwqZVp4QUM/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9502858210400</ean><condition>New</condition><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity></product><product><sku>404834092512</sku><product_name>5 Pack Womens Sexy Knickers Underwear Ladies Lace Panties Seamless Briefs Pants</product_name><description>ūüĒ• PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Refresh your essentials with this 5 Pack Women‚Äôs Cotton Lace Briefs Set, designed for everyday comfort with a stylish feminine touch. Made from a soft cotton-rich stretch fabric, these knickers offer breathable comfort, flexible fit, and delicate lace trim.

Perfect for daily wear, work, travel, or casual comfort, these briefs combine practicality with elegant style while providing a smooth and comfortable fit under clothing.

‚≠ź KEY FEATURES
‚úÖ 5 Pack Value Set ‚Äď Includes 5 assorted colours/styles
‚úÖ Soft Cotton Rich Fabric ‚Äď Comfortable and breathable feel
‚úÖ 100% Cotton Crotch Lining ‚Äď Extra freshness and hygiene
‚úÖ Low Waist Design ‚Äď Modern flattering fit
‚úÖ Stretch Material ‚Äď Flexible comfort for all-day wear
‚úÖ Lace Trim Finish ‚Äď Elegant, feminine detail
‚úÖ Lightweight &amp; Breathable ‚Äď Ideal for everyday use
‚úÖ Comfort Fit Brief Style ‚Äď Smooth under clothing
ūüé® COLOUR OPTIONS
ūüĆą Mixed Colour Packs Available

ūüďĆ Due to monitor and lighting differences, actual colours may vary slightly from images.

ūüďč PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women‚Äôs Knickers / Briefs
Style	Low Waist Briefs
Material	95% Cotton / 5% Spandex
Crotch Fabric	100% Cotton
Decoration	Lace Trim
Pattern	Solid Colours
Fit	Regular Stretch Fit
Sizes Available	M, L, XL
Quantity	5 Pieces Set
ūüďŹ SIZE GUIDE
ūüďĆ Asian sizing may run smaller than UK/EU sizes. Please consider choosing one size up for best comfort.

M ‚Äď Suitable for Small
L ‚Äď Suitable for Medium
XL ‚Äď Suitable for Large
ūüď¶ PACKAGE INCLUDES
‚úĒ 5 √ó Women‚Äôs Cotton Lace Briefs (Mixed / Selected Colours)
ūüéĮ PERFECT FOR
‚úĒ Everyday wear
‚úĒ Work &amp; office use
‚úĒ Travel
‚úĒ Comfortable daily essentials
‚úĒ Gift idea
ūüĒ• MULTI-BUY OFFERS
ūüíį Buy More Save More
ūüíį Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><image_url>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C4EAAeSwE2Fp421f/s-l1600.jpg</image_url><additional_image_urls>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/L6QAAeSwyXBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/G2AAAeSwPw9p421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WsMAAeSwXCBp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/FoIAAeSwrHRp421f/s-l1600.jpg,https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/snkAAeSwX9xp421h/s-l1600.jpg</additional_image_urls><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Other</category><ean>9507250333601</ean><condition>New</condition><price>16.99</price><quantity>4</quantity></product></products>