<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<products><product><sku>505873497501</sku><name>Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers (Pair) Walnut</name><description>Key features:

    WhatHiFi 5-Star bookshelf speakers
    Exceptional value for money with advanced features for the price point
    Curved braced cabinets help to eliminate vibrations and dissipate standing waves
    Gold-plated bi-wire connection separates high and low frequencies for enhanced clarity
    Dual reflex ports enhance overall bass response and clarity

5-year warranty &amp; 30-day money-back guarantee included


            
Overview:
The Wharfedale Diamond 9.1 Bookshelf Speakers are clear and precise with unmatched sound reproduction at their level. They boast curved braced cabinets that not only allude to the premium aesthetic qualities of higher-priced speakers but also help to reduce unwanted cabinet vibrations and dissipate derogatory standing waves that can negatively affect your sound. The five-inch Kevlar mid/bass driver and one-inch textile tweeter work effortlessly together offering sparkling highs and full controlled lows revealing details in your favourite tracks that may have previously gone unheard. The gold-plated bi-wireable binding posts a trait usually only found at higher price ranges ensure complete versatility in your set-up and will benefit those who aim to achieve a precise and clean sound where high and low frequencies blend harmoniously without a fight for air space.</description><brand>Wharfedale</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|Home Audio &amp; HiFi Separates|Speakers &amp; Subwoofers</category><price>180.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/yUsAAeSw93Np1kAI/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>504048423208</sku><name>Cello C50WS4K 50" inch Smart WiFi WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV Freeview Play FRAMELESS</name><description>50″ Smart WebOS 4K Ultra HD TV with Freeview Play and Frameless Bezel

    50” 4K Ultra HD LED TV
    LG’s Smart operating system, WebOS Hub built-in
    Download apps through the web browser
    Freeview HD by Aerial &amp; also a Satellite tuner built-in with Freesat
    Bluetooth connectivity (easily add a Bluetooth soundbar)
    Freeview Play with 100 channels and 20,000 hours of free on-demand content
    3 x HDMI inputs for your external devices and consoles
    Can be wall mounted (200mm x 100mm bracket &amp; 4 pcs M5 X8 not included)


The built-in Smart platform, developed by LG, allows you to browse the web and download all your favourite entertainment apps, so you can stream directly to the TV. From Netflix, Prime Video and Disney Plus to YouTube and catch-up apps like BBC iPlayer and ITVx, a world of entertainment awaits.

With Freeview Play you can watch an impressive 60,000+ hours of TV and over 1,500 boxsets, across your favourite on-demand players. All for free.

With the built-in Bluetooth connectivity, you can add a Bluetooth soundbar to the TV. This means cinema sound can be enjoyed without the need for untidy cables. The built-in satellite tuner with Freesat provides access to over 170 channels with 100% channel coverage on a subscription-free basis. Plus, you’ll find your favourite on-demand players all in one place. You will just need to purchase and install your own satellite dish/cabling. The ultimate flat-screen TV with its super-slim bezel and lightweight design is ideal for wall mounting and easy maneuverability


Specification
Screen Size         50″
Freeview Play         Yes
DVD Player         No
USB         Yes – playback only
Contrast Ratio         5000:1
Brightness         250
Max Resolution         3840 x 2160
Speakers         2 x 8W
Smart         Yes
Max Power         120W
Energy Rating         ‘G – 71 watts on working and 0.5 watt standby power consumption
HDMI         3
Inputs         RF Antenna, HDMI X3, CVBS, USB x 2, RJ45
Outputs         Digital Audio Out, Earphone Out
VESA         200mm x 100mm
Dimension w/stand         W 1110 x H 733 x D 268 mm
Dimensions w/o stand         W 1110 x H 644 x D 34 mm
Weight         9.1kg</description><brand>Cello</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|TVs</category><price>462.99</price><quantity>7</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/DOkAAeSwt3BpwSw9/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>5058048349204</sku><name>Coffee Machine Espresso Machine Coffee Maker Cappuccino Milk Frother 20 Bar 1.8L</name><description>✅ 20Bar High-Pressure Extraction
Equipped with a professional high-pressure water pump, it delivers a stable 20Bar extraction pressure to instantly penetrate coffee grounds, fully releasing the aroma and oils of coffee beans. It easily  restoring the rich flavor of authentic espresso—every sip rivals the quality of specialty café drinks.
✅ 1.8L Large-Capacity Removable Water Tank
No need for frequent refills; a full tank can make multiple cups for the whole family, easily handling daily use and small gatherings. The semi-transparent design lets you check water levels at a glance, and the detachable structure, paired with a separate drip tray, makes refilling and cleaning a breeze—saving time and effort.
✅ Food-Grade Stainless Steel Manufacturing
The body and core contact parts are made of food-grade stainless steel, which is corrosion-resistant, high-temperature resistant, and durable. It eliminates residual odors, ensuring every cup of coffee is pure and safe, balancing premium texture with practicality.
🛠️ All-Inclusive Accessories · Unlock Diverse Coffee Experiences
The machine comes with a complete set of professional accessories, so you can start your home barista journey right out of the box. It balances professionalism and convenience to suit 
☕ Scenario Adaptation · Perfect for Your Daily Moments
🌅 Morning Wake-Up: One-tap espresso, paired with milk for an energizing latte to chase away drowsiness and kickstart a productive day.
☕ Afternoon Relaxation: Brew a cup of freshly ground coffee with dessert, enjoying a moment of peaceful solitude and elevating your at-home ritual.
🥂 Friend Gatherings: Quick double-cup brewing and a variety of milk-based drinks let you host a cozy coffee party at home.
💼 Office Energy Boost: Fast capsule brewing eliminates waiting time, providing timely energy to enhance work efficiency.
📌 Product Specifications
Extraction Pressure: 20Bar high-pressure extraction
Water Tank Capacity: 1.8L large-capacity removable water tank</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home, Furniture &amp; DIY|Appliances|Coffee, Tea &amp; Espresso Makers|Espresso &amp; Cappuccino Machines</category><price>97.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/IJsAAeSwtj1pr-Co/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>4049023423478</sku><name>11.5" Portable DVD Player with 9.5" Large HD Swivel Screen High Volume Speaker</name><description>About this item
👨‍👩‍👧【Portable and Magical】-- Compact design makes it easy to carry out with you. Take it on your road trip and get double surprises both on and off the screen. portable DVD player can be easily swiveled as a tablet and mounted to the car headrest, brings tons of fun for your journey.
👨‍👩‍👧【5 Hrs Battery Life】-- Upgraded battery capacity to 2500mAh, you and your family can watch 1-2 movies without any worries. Our portable DVD player for car provide a certificated AC power adapter and car charger in the package, no more worries about the battery dying out when you are out.
👨‍👩‍👧【Protective and Gorgeous Screen】-- portable DVD player for kids adopts the HD Eye-protective Screen, and refuses the recycled screen, aiming at alleviating eye fatigue caused by the long use, more comfortable and protective screen for your kids’ eyes.
👨‍👩‍👧【All Regions &amp; Multi Formats】-- Supports CD,DVD,VCD,SVCD,CD±R/±RW,DVD±R/±RW from all region (Blu-ray and pirated discs are not supported); DVD player portable also support multi-media files via USB and SD Card (16-32GB), such as VOB, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMA, JPEG.
👨‍👩‍👧【Dual Speakers &amp; Clear Sound】-- Portable dvd player with screen equipped with two high-power speakers, which makes the volume louder. There is a 3.5mm earphone jack on the right side of the portable dvd players so that you can get a concentrated and clearer sound for your private viewing.
👨‍👩‍👧【Easy Operation &amp; Seamless Viewing】-- DVD player has a simple operating system and a convenient remote control, making it an ideal companion for the kids and elderly. Never miss out on exciting plots, the Break-point memory function can ensure seamless connection of the plot.
👨‍👩‍👧【Premium Service &amp; Quick Response】-- We are committed to providing the best after-sales service to our customers. If you have any questions, concerns, or issues with the your device, we are here to help you 24 hours a day.

★Eye-protection LCD screen★: DVD player provide a 800*480 Swivel Screen with 270 degrees rotation and 180 degrees flip. The portable player can be swiveled as a tablet to attache to the car backseat to play.
★Super High Battery★: Upgrade battery capacity to 2 times as the original ones, ensures the 5 hours play time. Not enough? Free car charger provided in the package.
★Resume Play★: Support break-point memory function, make it possible to start from where you left at last time, no need to start again.
★Game Player★: This DVD player is more than a DVD player, we provide a free game controller in our package, kids also can use this to play 180 kinds of retro games, such as super Mario etc. Note: customer need do download game cd by yourself.
★Multi-Media★: Directly play in formats: CD, DVD, CD-R/RW, DVD-R/+R, DVD+RW/-RW, VCD, SVCD; USB and SD Card supported: MP3/WMA/WAV, JPEG, MPEG2/AVI, TXT.


The new version of portable DVD player.
3 years in portable DVD player make us understand your needs better and make prodcuts more better.

Your Home Cinema always with You:
Our Portable DVD Player has a built-in USB port that allows you to enjoy your favorite movies while travelling, camping, sightseeing,you can also copy your CD files to USB or SD card.
Improved battery:
Improved 2000mAh Lithium battery extend the play time to 5 hours,even the adapter was left at home,do not need to worry about losing battery power whilst watching a movie.

Break Point memory:
Break Point memory function make it possible to start from where you end at last time.
Sync to your TV Screen:
With the included AV cable, it's available to transmit the screen from DVD player to your TV to enjoy a bigger and clearer screen.
Fantastic Swivel Screen: portable DVD player with 9.5 inch 270° rotation and 180° flip screen make it possible to attach to the car headrest and make you enjoy your time when you are on boring road trip.

Package Including:
1x Portable DVD player
1x AV cable
1x Remote controller
1x Power adapter
1x Car charger
1x User manual</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Sound &amp; Vision|DVD, Blu-ray &amp; Home Cinema|DVD &amp; Blu-ray Players</category><price>65.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PnMAAeSw5yJpzi5u/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>9501234567891</sku><name>2 Packs 6AH For Makita 18V Battery Li-Ion BL1830 BL1850 BL1840 BL1860B LXT400</name><description>Product Description


Features:

1. New and in a good condition.
2. Made of durable and reliable material, harmless to your health.
3. It is easy to use, convenient to carry with.
4. The best replacement for the old or damaged one.
5. A great assistant for electric tools.
6. Provide convenience to charge your electric tool anytime and anywhere.
7. It is suitable for Makita BL1815, BL1830, BL1835, LXT400, 194204-5, 194205-3, 194309-1.

Specifications:
Chemistry: Li-ion
Brand: For Makita
Model No.: BL1830
Condition: Brand new
Sub-Type: Replacement Battery
Voltage (V): 18V
Capacity: 6000mAh
Color: Black

 

Replace Original Makita Battery Code:

for MAKITA

194205-3, 194309-1, BL1815, BL1830, BL1840, LXT400

 

Fit Original Makita Model:

for MAKITA

for Makita BDF453SHE, for Makita BDF454Z, for Makita BHP452

for Makita BML184, for Makita BML185,

for Makita BST221Z, for Makita BTDW251Z, for Makita ML185, for Makita TD140D, for Makita TW251D

for Makita BCS550 Series:BCS550, BCS550Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BDA350, BDA350Z,

for Makita BDF451 Series:BDF451, BDF451Z,

for Makita BFR550 Series:BFR550L, BFR550Z,

for Makita BFR750 Series:BFR750, BFR750L, BFR750Z,

for Makita BFS450 Series:BFS450, BFS450RFE, BFS450Z,

for Makita BGA452 Series:BGA452, BGA452Z,

for Makita BHP451 Series:BHP451, BHP451SFE, BHP451Z,

for Makita BHP453 Series:BHP453, BHP453SHE,

for Makita BHP454 Series:BHP454, BHP454Z,

for Makita BHR202 Series:BHR202, BHR202RFE, BHR202Z,

for Makita BHR240 Series:BHR240, BHR240Z,

for Makita BHR241 Series:BHR241, BHR241Z,

for Makita BJR181 Series:BJR181, BJR181X, BJR181X1,BJR181Z,

for Makita BJR182 Series:BJR182, BJR182X, BJR182Z,

for Makita BJS130 Series:BJS130, BJS130Z,

for Makita BJV180 Series:BJV180, BJV180Z,

for Makita BPB180 Series:BPB180, BPB180Z,

for Makita BSS501 Series:BSS501, BSS501Z,

for Makita BSS610 Series:BSS610, BSS610SFE, BSS610X2,BSS610Z,

for Makita BSS611 Series:BSS611X, BSS611Z,

for Makita BTD140 Series:BTD140, BTD140SFE, BTD140Z,

for Makita BTD141 SeriesBTD141, BTD141Z,

for Makita BTD144 Series:BTD144, BTD144RFE, BTD144Z,

for Makita BTL061 Series:BTL061, BTL061Z,

for Makita BTL063 Series:BTL063, BTL063Z,

for Makita BTP140 Series:BTP140, BTP140Z,

for Makita BTW251 Series:BTW251, BTW251Z,

for Makita BTW253 Series:BTW253, BTW253Z,

for Makita BTW450 Series:BTW450, BTW450Z,

for Makita BDA350 Series:BUB182, BUB182Z,

for Makita BVR350 Series:BVR350, BVR350Z,

for Makita BVR450 Series:BVR450, BVR450Z,

for Makita BVR850 Series:BVR850, BVR850Z,

for Makita DF454 Series:DF454D, DF454DRFX, DF454DZ,

for Makita HP454 Series:HP454D, HP454DRFX, HP454DZ,

for Makita HR202 Series:HR202D, HR202DRFX, HR202DZK,

for Makita JR120 Series:JR120D, JR120DRF, JR120DZK,

for Makita ML184 Series:ML184(FlashLight), ML184,

for Makita MR100 Series:MR100, MR100W,

for Makita PB108 Series:PB108D, PB108DRFX, PB108DZ,

for Makita TD144 Series:TD144DRFX, TD144DZ,

for Makita TD251 Series:TD251DRFX, TD251DZ


Package Includes:
2 x 6000mAh Batter</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home, Furniture &amp; DIY|DIY Tools &amp; Workshop Equipment|Power Tool &amp; Air Tool Accessories|Power Tool Batteries</category><price>31.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/u6MAAeSwuXxorCS3/s-l1600.jpg</image></product><product><sku>9501234567891</sku><name>Bluetooth FM Transmitter Car Kit MP3 Player USB Charger Handsfree Adapter UK</name><description>Upgrade your driving experience with this multifunctional Car Charger Bluetooth adapter. Combining hands-free calling, music streaming, and rapid charging, it’s the perfect companion for every journey. Designed with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology, it delivers high-speed charging while keeping your devices connected safely.


⭐ Key Features
Bluetooth 5.0 Connectivity: Stable, fast pairing with smartphones for calls, music, and navigation audio.
FM Transmitter Function: Stream your favorite playlists directly to your car stereo via FM radio.
Dual USB Fast Charging Ports: Supports rapid charging for multiple devices simultaneously.
MP3 Player Support: Play music from USB drives or SD cards effortlessly.
Hands-Free Calling: Clear audio with built-in microphone ensures safe driving.
Compact &amp; Universal Design: Fits all standard car cigarette lighter sockets and works with most vehicles.

📊 Technical Specs
Bluetooth Version: 5.0
Input: DC 12-24V
Output: 5V/2.4A per USB port
Frequency Range: 87.5–108MHz
Compatible Formats: MP3/WMA/WAV
LED Display: Shows FM frequency and device info

💡 Benefits
Charge your phone and other devices quickly with Fast Charger BT 5.0 technology.
Enjoy seamless music streaming without tangled wires.
Stay safe with hands-free calling while driving.
Compact design keeps your dashboard neat and organized.

🎯 Ideal For
Daily commuters who need fast device charging and music on the go.
Road trips and long drives requiring hands-free calls and entertainment.
Anyone who wants to upgrade an older car stereo to Bluetooth functionality.
Drivers with multiple devices needing simultaneous fast charging.

🌐 Vast Applications
Cars, SUVs, trucks, and other vehicles with cigarette lighter sockets.
Listening to music or podcasts from smartphones, USB drives, or SD cards.
Hands-free calls during work commutes, rideshare driving, or family trips.
Charging smartphones, tablets, GPS devices, power banks, and other USB devices.
Enhancing older car stereos with FM broadcasting and Bluetooth connectivity.</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Electronics

Portable Audio &amp; Headphones
Portable Audio Accessories
Transmitters</category><price>9.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/2FkAAeSwnNZpbks~/s-l960.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834097401</sku><name>Mini Pocket Umbrella Folding Compact Rain Windproof Anti UV 5 Folding Travel UK</name><description>Stay protected in every season with this sleek and ultra-portable Mini Pocket Compact Fold Umbrella. Designed for modern lifestyles, it combines Rain Windproof durability with Anti UV protection, making it the perfect everyday travel essential.


⭐ Key Features
🌧 Rain Windproof Design – Strong frame for reliable performance in wind &amp; rain
☀️ Anti UV Protection – Helps block harmful sun rays on hot days
👜 Ultra Compact &amp; Pocket Size – Easy to carry anywhere, anytime
⚡ Quick Open &amp; Fold – Simple, hassle-free operation
🎒 Travel Case Included – Clean and convenient storage
💪 Durable Build – Premium materials for long-term use

📏 Technical Specifications
Type: 5-Fold Compact Umbrella
Material: Waterproof Fabric + Reinforced Metal Frame
Function: Rainproof, Windproof, Anti UV
Folded Size: Approx. 15–18 cm
Open Diameter: Approx. 90–95 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Included: Protective Travel Case

🌍 Ideal For
🌧 Rainy Days – Stay dry during sudden showers
☀️ Super Sunny Days – Reliable shade with Anti UV protection
🍂 Autumn &amp; Winter – Handles wet and windy conditions
🌸 Spring Showers – Perfect for unpredictable weather
🌞 Summer Heat – Use as a portable sunshade
🌦 All-Season Use – One umbrella for every condition

🔄 Vast Application of Usage
Designed to make your life easier, this umbrella is perfect for:

🚶 Daily Use – Commuting, school runs, office travel
🛍 Shopping Trips – Stay comfortable while out and about
✈️ Travel &amp; Holidays – Compact size fits easily in luggage
🚗 On-the-Go Protection – Keep in your car or bag for emergencies
🎉 Outdoor Events – Festivals, sports days, gatherings
🏕 Outdoor Activities – Walking, hiking, camping
👨‍👩‍👧 For Everyone – Suitable for men, women, and kids
👉 No confusion, no hassle — one simple solution for all your weather needs


🎯 Why Choose This Umbrella?
✔ Dual-purpose Rain Windproof &amp; Anti UV protection
✔ Compact, lightweight, and easy to carry
✔ Reliable in all weather conditions
✔ Practical design for everyday convenience

🚀 Benefits You’ll Love
Stay dry and protected anytime, anywhere
Enjoy peace of mind with all-in-one weather protection
Carry effortlessly without bulk
Dependable performance you can trust</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion
Women
Women's Accessories
Umbrellas</category><price>18.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/U-oAAeSwf8Fp43cb/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834097418</sku><name>Bike Seat Cover Soft Gel Saddle Bicycle Padded Cushioned Extra Comfort UK</name><description>Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover Padded Cushion Saddle – Universal Fit for Maximum Comfort 🚴
Upgrade your cycling experience with this premium Soft Gel Bike Seat Cover, designed to deliver exceptional Padded Comfort on every ride. Whether commuting, exercising, or riding long distances, enjoy a smoother, pain-free journey.

⭐ Key Features
Soft Gel Padding – Advanced cushioning absorbs shock and reduces pressure
Padded Comfort Design – Extra-thick padding for long rides
Secure Anti-Slip Fit – Non-slip base with adjustable drawstring
Breathable Design – Airflow channel reduces heat and moisture
Water-Resistant – Protects from sweat and light rain
Universal Fit – Fits most standard bike saddles
💎 Premium Quality &amp; Material
High-grade soft gel with high-density memory foam
Premium Lycra fabric – breathable and stretchable
Reinforced stitching for durability
Anti-slip textured base for stability
Maintains shape after long-term use
📐 Technical Specifications
Material: Soft Gel + High-Density Foam + Lycra Fabric
Size: Approx. 27.5 x 17 cm
Weight: Lightweight &amp; portable
Compatibility: Fits most bike saddles
Installation: Easy slip-on with drawstring
🎯 Ideal For
Daily commuters and city cyclists
Long-distance and endurance riders
Indoor cycling and spin classes
Mountain and road biking
Beginners needing extra comfort
🌍 Vast Applications
Road bikes – long-distance comfort
Mountain bikes – shock absorption
City bikes – daily commuting
Exercise bikes – home workouts
Hybrid bikes – mixed terrain
Leisure cycling – casual rides
Travel &amp; touring – portable comfort
✅ Benefits
Ride longer without discomfort
Reduces pressure on sensitive areas
Improves performance and endurance
Quick installation – no tools needed</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure

Cycling
Bike Accessories
Saddle Covers</category><price>9.99</price><quantity>3</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/r~QAAeSwYytp4Och/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834097500</sku><name>Anti Mosquito Insect &amp; Bug Repellent Bracelet Bands Silicone Wristband 1- 20 PK</name><description>⭐ Key Features
Effective Mosquito Protection – Helps repel mosquitoes and insects naturally
Safe &amp; DEET-Free – Infused with natural plant-based essential oils
Adjustable &amp; Flexible Fit – Comfortable silicone design for adults and children
Long-Lasting Use – Provides extended protection for hours
Portable &amp; Easy – Wear on wrist, ankle, or attach anywhere
Multiple Colors – Fun and vibrant options
Value Packs – Available in 1–20 PCS options
📊 Technical Specifications
Material: High-quality silicone
Active Ingredients: Natural essential oils (citronella, eucalyptus, etc.)
Size: One-size-fits-most (adjustable)
Usage Time: Several hours per band (varies by environment)
Application: Wrist, ankle, bags, strollers
Pack Options: 1, 5, 10, 15, or 20 pieces
✅ Benefits
No sprays, no skin irritation, no mess
Family-friendly for kids and adults
Lightweight, waterproof, and travel-ready
Great alternative to traditional repellents
🎯 Ideal For
Camping, hiking, fishing, and outdoor adventures
Travel, holidays, and picnics
Gardening, BBQs, and sports activities
Everyday use at home or school
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Outdoor: camping, trekking, cycling, beach trips
Home &amp; garden: backyard, lawn work, evening relaxation
Kids: school, playgrounds, daycare
Travel: airports, hotels, tropical destinations
Work: fishing, farming, construction, warehouses
Pet walks: parks, trails, wooded areas
Daily use: shopping, commuting, casual outings
🚚 Free Shipping
Fast &amp; reliable delivery
Secure packaging for safe arrival
No extra charges</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure

Camping &amp; Hiking
Outdoor Survival Equipment
Insect Nets</category><price>13.99</price><quantity>2</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jS0AAeSwJyRp2OwQ/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834097517</sku><name>Juicer Lemon Squeezer Citrus Juice Hand Held Stainless Steel Fruit Orange</name><description>Key Features
Perfect Squeeze Technology – Extracts maximum juice with minimal effort
Durable Stainless Steel Build – Rust-resistant and long-lasting
Ergonomic Handle Design – Comfortable grip for easy squeezing
No Seeds, No Mess – Built-in filter keeps juice smooth
Easy to Clean – Dishwasher safe and quick rinse cleaning
Used for Variety of Fruits – Ideal for lemons, limes, and small oranges
📐 Technical Specifications
Material: Premium Stainless Steel
Type: Handheld Manual Juicer
Color: Silver
Size: Compact &amp; portable
Weight: Lightweight yet durable
Cleaning: Dishwasher safe
💡 Benefits
Saves time compared to manual squeezing
Extracts more juice with less waste
Keeps hands clean and irritation-free
Ideal for home, bars, and restaurants
Compact for easy storage and travel
🎯 What It Is Ideal For
Making fresh lemon and lime juice
Preparing cocktails and refreshing drinks
Adding flavor to salads, marinades, and dishes
Baking desserts and pastries
Daily kitchen and professional use
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Beverages – lemon water, smoothies, iced tea
Cooking – seafood, chicken, sauces, vegetables
Salads – fresh citrus dressings
Baking – cakes, tarts, desserts
Bar use – cocktails like margaritas &amp; mojitos
Natural cleaning – eco-friendly lemon solutions
DIY beauty – skincare and hair remedies
Outdoor use – picnics, camping, travel</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden

Appliances
Small Kitchen Appliances
Juicers &amp; Presses</category><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/bLYAAeSweM9p34ep/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834097593</sku><name>10m Retractable Clothes Reel Double Washing Line Wall Mounted Outdoor</name><description>Key Features
10M Double Washing Line – Provides ample drying space for clothes, towels, and bedding
Retractable Design – Extends when needed and neatly retracts to save space
Wall Mounted Convenience – Easy to install on walls, fences, or posts
Durable &amp; Weather-Resistant – Built to withstand outdoor conditions
Secure Locking Mechanism – Keeps the line tight and prevents sagging
Compact Storage – Keeps spaces tidy and clutter-free
📊 Technical Specifications
Line Length: 10 meters (double line)
Type: Retractable Clothes Reel
Installation: Wall Mounted
Material: High-quality ABS casing + strong line cord
Usage: Indoor &amp; Outdoor
Color: Varies by stock
Mounting Accessories: Included
💡 Benefits
Saves space compared to traditional clotheslines
Keeps laundry neat and off the ground
Perfect for small spaces like balconies and patios
Helps reduce indoor moisture
Easy to use and maintain
🏡 Ideal For
Homes with limited outdoor space
Apartments, balconies, and patios
Gardens, garages, and laundry rooms
Everyday family laundry drying needs
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Drying clothes, towels, bedsheets, and delicates
Indoor drying during rainy seasons
Outdoor use in gardens or backyards
Camping, caravans, and temporary setups
Utility rooms and shared laundry areas</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden

Household &amp; Laundry Supplies
Laundry Supplies
Washing Lines</category><price>14.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PzEAAeSweFVp1mhN/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>4048340975905</sku><name>EMERGENCY HAMMER CAR WINDOW BREAKER SEATBELT CUTTER BREAK GLASS ESCAPE SAFETY UK</name><description> EMERGENCY HAMMER Car Window Breaker &amp; Seatbelt Cutter – Essential Vehicle Escape Safety Tool (UK Stock)

Be fully prepared for unexpected emergencies with this high‑quality EMERGENCY HAMMER featuring a WINDOW BREAKER &amp; SEATBELT CUTTER. Designed for rapid response, this compact yet durable tool can make a critical difference when seconds matter.


⭐ Key Features
✔ 2-in-1 Emergency Design – Heavy-duty window breaker &amp; seatbelt cutter in one compact tool
✔ Hardened Steel Hammer Head – Instantly shatters side windows in emergency situations
✔ Sharp Concealed Blade – Quickly cuts jammed or locked seatbelts
✔ Non-Slip Anti-Skid Handle – Firm grip for safe and controlled use
✔ High-Visibility Red Body – Easy to locate in stressful situations
✔ Protective Mounting Bracket – Secure and convenient storage within reach
✔ Compact &amp; Lightweight – Fits glove box, door pocket, or centre console

🔧 Technical Specifications
Material: High-carbon hardened steel hammer head
Handle: Durable ABS with anti-slip grip
Blade: Stainless steel concealed safety blade
Length: Approx. 17cm
Weight: Approx. 130–150g
Colour: Red
Condition: Brand New
Stock Location: UK

🌍 Vast Application of Usage
This EMERGENCY HAMMER is suitable for a wide range of vehicles and emergency situations:

🚗 Private cars &amp; family vehicles
🚕 Taxis, Uber &amp; ride-share vehicles
🚚 Vans, trucks &amp; delivery fleets
🚌 Buses &amp; minibuses
🚐 Motorhomes &amp; caravans
🚓 Emergency &amp; service vehicles
🚤 Boats &amp; marine vehicles
🏢 Workplace fleet vehicles
🎒 Travel safety kits &amp; roadside emergency kits
Perfect for emergencies involving:

Vehicle submersion in water
Electrical or central locking failure
Car fires
Severe collisions
Jammed doors after impact

🛡 Key Benefits
✔ Enables fast escape when doors cannot be opened
✔ Cuts seatbelts instantly to prevent entrapment
✔ Provides peace of mind for drivers and passengers
✔ A small investment for potentially life-saving protection

📦 Package Includes
1 × EMERGENCY HAMMER
1 × Mounting Bracket</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Motors

Safety &amp; Security Accessories
Safety
Emergency Tools &amp; Tool Kits</category><price>11.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/VkAAAeSw8Udp0Pz1/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091102</sku><name>Hair Trap Shower Bath Plug Hole Waste Catcher Stopper Drain Sink Strainer UK</name><description>Hair Trap Shower Bath Plug Hole Waste Catcher – Stopper Drain Sink Strainer
Keep your drains clean and clog-free with this practical and efficient Plug Hole Waste Catcher. Designed to trap hair, food particles, and debris before they cause blockages, this versatile Stopper Drain Sink Strainer is a must-have for every home.


⭐ Key Features
Effective Hair &amp; Debris Trap – Catches hair, soap residue, and waste to prevent clogged drains
Dual Function Design – Works as both a Plug Hole Waste Catcher and a Stopper Drain Sink Strainer
Universal Fit – Suitable for most sinks, bathtubs, and shower plug holes
Durable &amp; Flexible Material – Made from high-quality silicone or TPR for long-lasting use
Easy to Clean – Simply remove, rinse, and reuse in seconds
Anti-Slip Design – Securely stays in place without shifting during use

📏 Technical Specifications
Material: Silicone / TPR (Thermoplastic Rubber)
Diameter: Approx. 10–11 cm (fits standard drains)
Design: Flat or dome-shaped with raised edges
Color Options: Varies (e.g., white, grey, blue, black)
Application: Bathroom, kitchen, laundry sinks

✅ Benefits
Prevents costly plumbing blockages
Maintains smooth water drainage
Saves time on cleaning and maintenance
Hygienic and reusable solution
Ideal for everyday household use

🎯 Ideal For
Showers and bathtubs
Bathroom and kitchen sinks
Laundry tubs
Homes with pets or long hair</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden
Bath
Bathroom Accessories
Drain Stoppers &amp; Strainers</category><price>7.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/oPEAAeSwUl5pzTPy/s-l960.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091201</sku><name>Electric Portable Powered Drill Pump Oil Fluid Water Transfer Pumps Self Priming</name><description>Key Features
Drill Powered Design – Connects to most electric drills for fast pumping
Self Priming Function – Smooth operation without manual priming
Multi-Fluid Compatibility – Works with water, oil, diesel, and more
Durable Construction – Built for long-lasting use
Portable &amp; Lightweight – Easy to carry and store
Standard Hose Fit – Compatible with common hose sizes
📊 Technical Specifications
Type: Drill Pump (Self Priming)
Power Source: Electric Drill (not included)
Material: High-strength plastic + metal shaft
Flow Rate: Approx. 20–30 L/min
Inlet/Outlet: Approx. 16mm
Fluids: Water, oil, diesel, non-corrosive liquids
✅ Benefits
Saves time compared to manual transfer
No electricity needed—use your drill
Reduces mess with controlled flow
Ideal for emergencies and everyday tasks
🎯 Ideal For
Homeowners and DIY users
Garden irrigation tasks
Automotive fluid changes
Aquariums, pools, and tanks
Workshops and construction sites
🌍 Vast Applications of Usage
Automotive – oil, coolant, and fuel transfer
Home – draining water and tanks
Gardening – irrigation and water transfer
Aquariums – tank cleaning and water changes
Pools &amp; spas – draining and refilling
Workshops – handling light oils and fluids
Marine – boat water removal and fuel transfer
Construction – removing water from work areas
📦 Package Includes
1 × Electric Portable Drill Pump</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden
Garden &amp; Patio
Ponds &amp; Water Features
Pond &amp; Fountain Pumps</category><price>13.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/vf4AAeSwV3Rpy7Ab/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091508</sku><name>2x Headphone Adapter Small to Big 3.5mm to 6.35mm 1/4 Inch Jack Audio Adaptor UK</name><description>Description:

Can be paired to any enabled devices,such as mobile phone, laptops, speaker andaudio transmitter.

Make music in the audio equipment play by wirelesseasy to install on your car

360 degree grip treads help easy plugging and unplugging.Great for speaker use for stereo channel microphone connectingThanks for your understandings.

Specification Model: 6.5/3.5 Female Hole



Plug Type: 6.35 Male To 3.5 Female



Plug Life: 10000



Electroplating Process: Gold Plating



Material: Zinc Alloy

Use temperature range:0-60(°C)

Rated load:5(VA)



Notes:-

Due to the difference between different monitors, the picturesmay not reflect the actual color of the item.Compare the detail sizes with yours, please allow 1-3cm errordue to manual measurement.Thanks for your understandings.

Package Includes
2 × 6.35mm Male to 3.5mm Female Audio Adapter

Important Notes
Due to differences in monitor settings, the actual product color may vary slightly from images.

Please allow 1–3 cm measurement difference due to manual measurement.

Thank you for your understanding.</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Electronics
Sound &amp; Vision
TV &amp; Home Audio Accessories
Audio Cables &amp; Adapters</category><price>8.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/JTYAAeSwRL1py63A/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091706</sku><name>2x Bicycle Handle Bar Grips Double Lock On BMX MTB Mountain Bike Cycle Grip UK</name><description>Description:


Color: Black, Red, White, Silver, Blue, Gold
Weight: 122g(About)
Application: Handlebars with an outer diameter of about 2.2cm
Material: Lock ring: Aluminum alloy; Grip: TPR rubber; Inner tube: High-strength plastic
Size: Length: 13cm; Outer diameter: 3cm; Inner diameter: 2.2cm


NOTE:Due to different lighting/camera conditions, there may be some color difference between the actual product and the picture. Please carefully understand before placing an order!


Features:
* Anti-skid design
* Ergonomic grip shape is molded to work with your body
* Comfort grip feeling, anti-slip design. Relieve your fatigue and hands pain for long distance cycling!
* Fast and accurately to remove and install
* Two screws fixed, easy to install.</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Sports, Hobbies &amp; Leisure

Cycling
Bike Components &amp; Parts
Handlebar Grips, Tape &amp; Pads</category><price>12.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/V8QAAeSwqj5pyoPx/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091805</sku><name>40 CD DVD Carry Case Disc Storage Holder CD Sleeve Wallet Ideal Car Lot</name><description>Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder

Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.

Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver
Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder
Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.
Portable 40pcs Capacity Disc CD DVD VCD Wallet Storage Organizer Case Holder

Features:
1. High quality materials are selected for outstanding shape design to provide the best protection for the optical disc.
2. Good protection to avoid moisture and dust invasion.
3. The inner pages made of special materials can effectively prevent the disc from being scratched.
4. PP environmental protection material, no pollution to the environment, protect your CD.
5. Compact structure improves storage capacity and saves space effectively.
6. Compact and lightweight, easy to carry.

Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver

Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.
Specifications:
Capacity: can hold 40pcs Disc
Color: Red, Blue, Black, White, Silver
Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.
Note:
Please allow 1-3mm differs due to manual measurement.
Due to the different display and different light, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thanks for your understanding.




1 x DVD CD Storage Case</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Electronics

Drives, Storage &amp; Blank Media
Blank Media &amp; Accessories
Media Cases, Sleeves &amp; Wallets</category><price>12.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/YpYAAeSwoNZpynTn/s-l960.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834091812</sku><name>130cm Leather Bag Strap – Replacement for Shoulder or Crossbody Bags</name><description>Description:

Item Type:Bag Belt
Material:Artificial PU Leather 
Width:1.8cm
Length :130cm Adjustable
Color: Black, Dark Blue, Coffee, Brown, Light brown, Red, Pink, White
Description:
100% brand new and high quality
Using PU leather made of material, feel are very good,
Strong and durable, work is also fine.
You can now make their own special hands-on bag.

Note:
Transition: 1cm=10mm=0.39inch
No retail package.
Please allow 1-2cm error due to manual measurement. pls make sure you do not mind before you bid.
Due to the difference between different monitors, the picture may not reflect the actual color of the item. Thank you!

Package includes:
1 x Shoulder strap(other accessories demo in the picture is not included.)</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion
Women
Women's Bags &amp; Handbags</category><price>9.99</price><quantity>0</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/Lx4AAeSwmFBpynDM/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834092499</sku><name>Strong Vacuum Suction Cup Hook Shower Towel-Holder Hooks for Bathroom Kitchen UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Organise your space easily with these Vacuum Suction Cup Hooks, designed to provide a strong hold without drilling or damaging your walls. Made from premium 304 stainless steel, these hooks are perfect for bathrooms, kitchens, and home organisation.

With powerful suction grip and a modern design, they securely hold towels, bags, and accessories on smooth surfaces while keeping your space neat and clutter-free.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ No Drilling Required – Easy installation without tools or wall damage
✅ Strong Suction Power – Holds up to approx. 15 lbs (6.8 kg)
✅ Waterproof &amp; Rustproof – Ideal for bathroom and kitchen use
✅ Durable Stainless Steel – Corrosion-resistant and long-lasting
✅ Modern Design – Matches any home décor style
✅ Reusable &amp; Removable – Easy to reposition without marks
✅ Anti-Slip Hook – Secure grip for hanging items safely
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Suction Cup Hook
Material	304 Stainless Steel
Installation	Vacuum Suction (No Drill)
Load Capacity	Up to 15 lbs (approx.)
Colour Options	Silver, Black, Gold, White
Use	Bathroom, Kitchen, Home Organisation
🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Towels &amp; bath accessories
✔ Kitchen utensils
✔ Handbags &amp; keys
✔ Clothes &amp; hats
✔ Shower accessories
📦 PACKAGE OPTIONS
✔ 1 × Hook
✔ 2 × Hooks (Value Pack)
⚠️ INSTALLATION TIPS
Suitable for smooth surfaces only (tiles, glass, metal, wood)
Not suitable for painted or rough walls
Press firmly and wait 24 hours before use
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>Home &amp; Garden
Household Accessories &amp; Supplies
Storage Solutions
Wall Hooks &amp; Door Hangers</category><price>22.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/AH0AAeSwhHJp3luF/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834092505</sku><name>Mens Body Shaper Compression Vest Slimming Shirt Tank Chest Belly Men's Waist UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a more confident look instantly with this Men’s Slimming Compression Vest, designed to shape your chest, flatten your stomach, and support better posture. Made from a breathable stretch fabric, this vest provides firm compression while remaining comfortable for all-day wear.

Perfect for daily wear, gym workouts, or under clothing for a slimmer appearance. Lightweight, flexible, and discreet under shirts for everyday confidence.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Instant Slimming Effect – Flattens belly and shapes chest
✅ Compression Fit Design – Supports posture and core
✅ Breathable Fabric – Comfortable for all-day wear
✅ Seamless Under Clothing – Invisible under shirts
✅ High Elastic Material – Flexible body-contouring fit
✅ Lightweight &amp; Comfortable – Ideal for daily or sports use
✅ Multi-Purpose Wear – Gym, running, work, or casual wear
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Men’s Compression Vest / Body Shaper
Material	Polyester
Fabric Type	Breathable Stretch
Style	Sleeveless Vest
Fit	Slim Compression Fit
Colours	Black, White
Sizes	M, L, XL, XXL
Pattern	Solid
Care	Machine Washable
Condition	New 
📌 SIZE TIP
Choose one size up for a more comfortable fit.

🎯 IDEAL FOR
✔ Daily wear under shirts
✔ Gym &amp; fitness training
✔ Running, cycling, workouts
✔ Body shaping &amp; posture support
✔ Confidence boosting appearance
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Men’s Compression Vest
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offers above for the latest deals</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion
Men
Men's Clothing
Underwear</category><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/rCoAAeSwmlFp4QUN/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku>404834092512</sku><name>5 Pack Womens Sexy Knickers Underwear Ladies Lace Panties Seamless Briefs Pants</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Refresh your essentials with this 5 Pack Women’s Cotton Lace Briefs Set, designed for everyday comfort with a stylish feminine touch. Made from a soft cotton-rich stretch fabric, these knickers offer breathable comfort, flexible fit, and delicate lace trim.

Perfect for daily wear, work, travel, or casual comfort, these briefs combine practicality with elegant style while providing a smooth and comfortable fit under clothing.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ 5 Pack Value Set – Includes 5 assorted colours/styles
✅ Soft Cotton Rich Fabric – Comfortable and breathable feel
✅ 100% Cotton Crotch Lining – Extra freshness and hygiene
✅ Low Waist Design – Modern flattering fit
✅ Stretch Material – Flexible comfort for all-day wear
✅ Lace Trim Finish – Elegant, feminine detail
✅ Lightweight &amp; Breathable – Ideal for everyday use
✅ Comfort Fit Brief Style – Smooth under clothing
🎨 COLOUR OPTIONS
🌈 Mixed Colour Packs Available

📌 Due to monitor and lighting differences, actual colours may vary slightly from images.

📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Women’s Knickers / Briefs
Style	Low Waist Briefs
Material	95% Cotton / 5% Spandex
Crotch Fabric	100% Cotton
Decoration	Lace Trim
Pattern	Solid Colours
Fit	Regular Stretch Fit
Sizes Available	M, L, XL
Quantity	5 Pieces Set
📏 SIZE GUIDE
📌 Asian sizing may run smaller than UK/EU sizes. Please consider choosing one size up for best comfort.

M – Suitable for Small
L – Suitable for Medium
XL – Suitable for Large
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 5 × Women’s Cotton Lace Briefs (Mixed / Selected Colours)
🎯 PERFECT FOR
✔ Everyday wear
✔ Work &amp; office use
✔ Travel
✔ Comfortable daily essentials
✔ Gift idea
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion

Women's Clothing
Lingerie &amp; Nightwear
Knickers</category><price>16.99</price><quantity>4</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/C4EAAeSwE2Fp421f/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Laptop Sleeve Case NoteBook Pouch Bag for Macbook Air Pro 11" 13" 14" 15" UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Keep your laptop safe and stylish with this Black Laptop Sleeve Bag, designed for everyday protection and portability. Suitable for many popular laptop brands including Lenovo, Dell, HP, Xiaomi, Asus, Acer, MacBook Air &amp; MacBook Pro.

Featuring a soft padded interior, secure zip closure, and slim lightweight design, this laptop case is ideal for work, travel, school, commuting, or daily use.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
✅ Multi-Size Options Available – Fits 11", 13", 14", 15", 15.6" laptops
✅ Protective Padded Design – Helps protect against scratches and bumps
✅ Smooth Zip Closure – Secure and easy access
✅ Slim Lightweight Sleeve – Easy to carry alone or inside backpack
✅ Soft Interior Lining – Gentle on laptop surfaces
✅ Classic Black Colour – Professional modern look
✅ Unisex Design – Suitable for men and women
✅ Perfect for Travel &amp; Work – Great for office, college, commuting
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Laptop Sleeve / Carry Case
Colour	Multi
Material	Cotton / Soft Fabric
Closure Type	Zipper
Style	Slim Sleeve Case
Gender	Unisex
Pattern	Solid
📏 INTERNAL SIZE GUIDE
📌 Please ensure your laptop dimensions are smaller than internal measurements.

11 / 12 Inch: 300 × 205 × 20 mm
13 Inch: 320 × 235 × 20 mm
14 / 15 Inch: 340 × 250 × 20 mm
15.6 Inch: 360 × 280 × 20 mm
💻 COMPATIBLE WITH
✔ MacBook Air / Pro
✔ Lenovo Laptops
✔ Dell Notebooks
✔ HP Laptops
✔ Xiaomi Notebooks
✔ Asus / Acer / Many Others
📦 PACKAGE INCLUDES
✔ 1 × Black Laptop Sleeve Bag
🔥 MULTI-BUY OFFERS
💰 Buy More Save More
💰 Quantity discounts available
Check offer section above for latest deals</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Electronics
Computers/Tablets &amp; Networking
Laptop &amp; Desktop Accessories
Laptop Cases &amp; Bags</category><price>12.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/PsAAAeSwaENp4534/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Push to Open System Damper Buffer Cabinet Drawer Hinge Heavier Catch Heavy Duty</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Upgrade your cabinets and drawers with this Push to Open Magnetic Catch Set. Simply press the door to latch or unlatch – no handles or knobs required. Creates a clean, seamless, modern look for your kitchen, wardrobe, or furniture.

Built-in magnet ensures a secure, tight close, preventing doors from drifting open. The adjustable 1/4" stroke makes installation easy and forgiving.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Push to Open Design – One-touch open/close, no knobs or handles needed
🔹 Magnetic Holding Force – Keeps doors tightly closed, prevents drifting
🔹 Adjustable Stroke (1/4 inch) – Easier installation with alignment tolerance
🔹 Soft Closer Rebound – Smooth, quiet operation
🔹 Universal Fit – Works for cabinets, drawers, wardrobes, cupboards, and furniture doors
🔹 Durable Construction – High-quality materials for long-lasting use
🔹 Multiple Quantities – Choose from 3, 5, or 10 pieces per set
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Push to Open Magnetic Catch / Damper
Function	Push-to-open &amp; soft close rebound
Magnetic Force	Built-in magnet for secure closing
Adjustable Stroke	Approx. 1/4 inch (6-7mm)
Application	Cabinet doors, drawers, wardrobes, cupboards, furniture
Colour	As shown in pictures (typically silver/black/white – check your variant)
Size	As shown in pictures (standard cabinet catch size)
Package Options	3pcs, 5pcs, or 10pcs per set</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden

DIY Materials
Cabinet Hardware
Cabinet Catches &amp; Latches</category><price>23.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/9PAAAeSwfqVp52vi/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Portable Zipper Eye Glasses Hard Case Sunglass Reading Cover Box Protector Gift</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Keep your glasses safe and stylish with this Fashion Denim Fabric Glasses Case. Made from high-quality cotton denim, this soft-shell case features a smooth zipper closure and a trendy patchwork pattern. Perfect for sunglasses, reading glasses, or prescription eyewear.

The lightweight yet protective design prevents scratches, dust, and damage while you're on the go. A must-have accessory for anyone who wants to keep their glasses organized and protected.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Premium Denim Fabric – High-quality cotton, soft yet durable
🔹 Zipper Closure – Secure, smooth-gliding zipper keeps glasses safely inside
🔹 Scratch Protection – Soft interior lining prevents lens scratches
🔹 Fashion Patchwork Design – Trendy and unisex style for men and women
🔹 Universal Size – Fits most sunglasses, reading glasses, and prescription eyewear
🔹 Lightweight &amp; Portable – Easy to carry in purse, backpack, or pocket
🔹 Great Gift Idea – Perfect for glasses wearers, travelers, or fashion lovers
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Soft Shell Eyeglasses Case / Sunglasses Pouch
Material	Denim Fabric (Cotton) – No high-concerned chemicals
Closure	Zipper
Pattern Type	Patchwork
Dimensions (approx.)	Length: 16cm (6.3″), Width: 6cm (2.4″), Height: 3.5cm (1.4″)
Weight	Approx. 106g (3.7 oz)
Gender	Unisex
Brand	UNBRANDED
Origin	China
Package Included	1 × Eyeglasses Box / Case</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Health &amp; Beauty
Vision Care
Glasses Cases &amp; Storage</category><price>5.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/y90AAeSwKuRp55JU/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>2X Clay Bar Cloth Clay Cloth Washing Towel For Car Paint Detailing Cleaning UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Transform your car detailing routine with this Magic Clay Towel. Unlike traditional clay bars, this dual-sided cleaning cloth covers a wider area and cleans faster – using only clean water or foam. The microfiber side lifts dirt while the clay side removes bonded contaminants like oxidation, water spots, ferrous powder, light rust, brake dust, and bird droppings.

Save up to 70% of your detailing time. Reusable multiple times – simply rinse with water and store in a cool, dry place. Will not damage your car's paint or shine.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Only Requires Clean Water – No soaps or chemicals needed for most jobs
🔹 Dual-Sided Design – Microfiber side for general wiping, clay side for stubborn contamination
🔹 Removes Tough Stains – Heavy oxidation, rainwater stains, ferrous powder, light rust, brake dust,etc
🔹 Wider Coverage – Cleans a larger area faster than a traditional clay bar
🔹 Saves 70% Time &amp; Effort – Complete car detailing in as little as 10 minutes
🔹 Reusable Multiple Times – Rinse with water after use – won't melt or deteriorate
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Magic Clay Towel / Car Decontamination Cloth
Special Features	Car cleaning – removes oxidation, water spots, brake dust, bird droppings
Material	Microfiber + Polymer clay composite
Model Options	Fine clay towel (gentle) / Medium clay towel (more aggressive)
Colour	Blue
Size	Approx. 30 × 30 cm (11.81 × 11.81 inches)
Weight	Approx. 130g (4.6 oz)
Package Included	1 × Clay Towel</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden

Household &amp; Laundry Supplies
Cleaning Tools
Cleaning Towels &amp; Cloths</category><price>10.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/5w4AAeSwcM9p6OnK/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Army Military Style Baseball Cadet Cap Hat Cadet Combat Fishing-Baseball-Cap UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Step out in retro style with this Washed Denim Flat Top Hat. Inspired by vintage military and fishing caps, this hat features an old-wash jeans look, a firm flat top (bib style), and a comfortable fit for both men and women. The tatting weaving craft adds durability and texture, while the 360° brim offers excellent sun protection for outdoor adventures.

Perfect for fishing, hiking, gardening, travel, or daily casual wear. Designed to fit larger heads comfortably, with a unisex European-inspired silhouette.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 Retro Washed Denim Look – Old wash jeans style with a vintage, casual vibe
🔹 Flat Top (Bib) Design – Classic military/fishing hat silhouette – holds its shape
🔹 Sun Protection – Full brim helps shield face and neck from UV rays
🔹 Tatting Weaving Craft – Durable, textured fabric for long-lasting wear
🔹 Unisex &amp; Big Head Friendly – Comfortable fit for men and women, accommodates larger head sizes
🔹 Four Seasons Use – Breathable cotton/polyester blend suitable for spring, summer, autumn, winter
🔹 European Trend Style – Fashion-forward accessory for outdoor or city wear
🔹 Easy Care – Do not machine wash, bleach, or iron – spot clean only
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Item Type	Military Style Hat / Flat Top Cap / Fishing Hat
Material	Cotton / Polyester blend (as per style)
Craft of Weaving	Tatting
Feature	Sun protection
Applicable Scene	Outdoor, casual, fishing, travel, daily wear
Applicable Season	Four seasons (spring, summer, autumn, winter)
Gender	Men (unisex – also fits women)
Department Name	Adult unisex
Colour	Multicolored (washed denim effect – as pictured)
Style	Casual, Retro, European Trend
Size (approx.)	28 × 18 × 11 cm (11″ × 7″ × 4.3″)
Number of pieces	1 hat
Care Instructions	Do not machine wash / Do not bleach / Do not iron – spot clean only</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion
Men
Men's Accessories
Hats</category><price>8.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/~HIAAeSwjCJp6hNW/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Heavy Duty Waterproof Garden Patio Furniture Cover for Rattan Table Cube Outdoor</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Protect your outdoor furniture from sun, rain, dust, and dirt with this High-Quality Outdoor Furniture Cover. Crafted from durable polyester and cotton, this cover offers reliable UV protection and weather resistance, keeping your terrace, garden chairs, and tables looking like new.

Available in over 200 sizes – find the perfect fit for your garden furniture. The modern, sleek design adds a touch of elegance to your outdoor space while providing heavy-duty protection.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 UV Protection – Shields furniture from harmful sun rays, preventing fading and cracking
🔹 Dust Barrier – Keeps outdoor furniture clean and ready to use at any moment
🔹 Water-Resistant Material – Polyester/cotton blend repels light rain and moisture
🔹 Customizable Fit – Available in over 200 sizes (see full list below)
🔹 Modern Style – Sleek, elegant design complements any terrace or garden
🔹 Durable Construction – Crafted for longevity and resistance to weather elements
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Product Type	Outdoor Furniture Cover – Garden Chair/Table Protector
Material	Polyester / Cotton blend
Features	UV, dust, water-resistant (light rain)
Status	Eco-friendly
Style	Modern, sleek, elegant
Available Sizes	200+ options (see dropdown/variations)
Colour	As pictured
📏 AVAILABLE SIZES (SELECT YOUR FIT)
Choose from the following dimensions (Length × Width × Height in cm):

40×40×40	80×80×80	85×85×80	90×90×90
68×68×120	110×110×70	120×90×76	120×120×74
120×120×140	120×60×90	120×95×75	123×123×74
123×61×72	126×126×74	130×70×70	130×130×75
135×135×75	140×140×140	140×90×60	145×85×80
145×90×105	150×150×75	152×104×71	154×90×76
155×95×68	160×160×80	170×94×70	180×120×74
180×150×80	190×125×80	190×66×89	200×160×70
200×160×80	200×200×120	200×200×85	205×90×60</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Home &amp; Garden
Garden &amp; Patio
Garden &amp; Patio Furniture
Outdoor Furniture Covers</category><price>47.99</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/RqQAAeSwPIZp7NLP/s-l1600.webp</image></product><product><sku /><name>Womens Magic High Waist Slimming Underwear Knickers Briefs Firm Tummy Control UK</name><description>🔥 PRODUCT DESCRIPTION
Achieve a smooth, sculpted silhouette with these Seamless High Waist Shaping Panties. Designed for all-day comfort, they offer tummy control, butt lifting, and a breathable fit – perfect for daily wear, postpartum recovery, or special occasions. The seamless knit construction prevents visible panty lines, while the nylon/elastane blend moves with your body.

Antibacterial and moisture-absorbing fabric keeps you fresh, and the high-waist design provides gentle compression without discomfort. Available in multiple sizes from XS to 4XL.

⭐ KEY FEATURES
🔹 High Waist Tummy Control – Firm but gentle shaping for a flatter stomach
🔹 Butt Lifter Design – Lifts and shapes your peach buttock naturally
🔹 Seamless Knit Fabric – No visible panty lines under tight clothing
🔹 Breathable &amp; Comfortable – Nylon/elastane blend for all-day wear
🔹 Antibacterial + Moisture-Absorbing – Keeps you dry and fresh
🔹 Maternity &amp; Postpartum Friendly – Gentle support for new mums
🔹 Easy to Wash – Machine washable, durable fabric
🔹 Multiple Sizes – XS-S, M-L, XL-XXL, 3XL, 4XL (see size chart)
📋 PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS
Item Type	High Waist Shaping Panties / Body Shaper
Material	Nylon + Elastane (knitted, seamless)
Colour	---
Abdominal Support	Yes – high waist compression
Butt Lifting	Yes – shapes the peach buttock
Special Features	Antibacterial, moisture-absorbing, seamless, breathable
Season	All seasons
Gender	Women / Maternity
Age Range	12+ years, maternity
Model Number	1102</description><brand>Unbranded</brand><category>

Fashion

Women's Clothing
Lingerie &amp; Nightwear
Shapewear</category><price>14.49</price><quantity>5</quantity><image>https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/jsoAAeSwDeVp740B/s-l1600.webp</image></product></products>